<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-01-01</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 3.1 percent in the third quarter of 1997 after increasing 3.3 percent in the second quarter, and the price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.3 percent after increasing 0.8 percent. Corporate profits increased $32.2 billion in the third quarter after increasing $15.5 billion in the second, reflecting a step-up in the profits of domestic nonfinancial corporations.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0198bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-01-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-01-02</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Third Quarter 1997</Title>
        <Author>Harlan W. King, Christopher L. Bach</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit increased to $42.2 billion in the third quarter of 1997 from $37.9 billion in the second quarter. The increase was accounted for by an increase in the deficit on goods; changes in the other principal components of the current account were small. In the capital account, outflows for U.S. assets abroad increased $101.6 billion after increasing $90.9 billion, and inflows for foreign assets in the United States increased $169.5 billion after increasing $143.0 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/BPA/1998/0198bop.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-01-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-01-03</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory­Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/1998/0198niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-01-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-01-04</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>1998 Release Dates for BEA Estimates</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/BEAWIDE/1998/0198rd.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-01-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-02-01</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Price Indexes for Selected Semiconductors, 1974–96</Title>
        <Author>Bruce T. Grimm</Author>
        <Description>In the most recent comprehensive revision of the NIPA's, BEA introduced new quality-adjusted price indexes for semiconductors. This article discusses these indexes, which incorporated the results from hedonic regressions based on performance characteristics of seven types of memory chips and two lines of microprocessors and which are designed to address the biases that are associated with conventional measures of real output for high-tech goods. As was noted when they were first introduced, the effect of incorporating the new price indexes into the NIPA's was to steepen the rate of decline in the prices of exports and imports of semiconductors and to raise the rates of real growth.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0298od.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Measurement of real output and prices</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-02-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-02-02</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 4.3 percent in the fourth quarter of 1997,up from a 3.1-percent increase in the third quarter. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.5 percent after increasing 1.3 percent. For the year 1997, real GDP grew 3.8 percent, the highest growth rate since 1988. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.7 percent, the slowest increase since 1964. The personal saving rate declined to 3.8 percent, the lowest rate since 1939.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0298bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-02-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-02-03</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Personal Income by State and Region, Third Quarter 1997</Title>
        <Author>Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>Personal income in the Nation increased $77.8 billion, or 1.1 percent, in the third quarter of 1997. Most of the increase was accounted for by the Southeast, Far West, and Mideast regions. Utah, Washington, and Idaho had the fastest growth in personal income in the third quarter.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/REGIONAL/perinc/1998/0298rea.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-02-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-03-01</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Gross Product by Industry Price Measures, 1977–96</Title>
        <Author>Robert E. Yuskavage</Author>
        <Description>Price measures of gross product originating (GPO) by industry can be used to compare price changes across industries and to compute industry contributions to the change in GDP prices. For example, the largest contributors to the 2.3-percent increase (annual rate) in the GDP price index in 1992–96 were the services industry group and the finance, insurance, and real estate industry group (0.7 percentage point each). Unit-cost measures by industry can be used to identify the sources of GPO price change among the cost components of GPO. For example, the labor cost per unit of real GPO declined in 1992–96 for the mining and the durable goods manufacturing industries and was unchanged for the wholesale trade industry.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/Inputout/1998/0398gpo.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Gross product by industry</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-03-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-03-02</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>A Guide to the NIPA's</Title>
        <Author>Eugene P. Seskin, Robert P. Parker</Author>
        <Description>BEA presents a compilation of information that will help users to better understand the NIPA's. This guide provides the definitions of the major aggregates and components; discusses the measures of real output and prices; explains how production is classified and how the NIPA's are presented; describes the statistical conventions that are used; and lists the principal source data and methods used to prepare the estimates of GDP.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0398niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-03-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-03-03</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Daniel Larkins, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>The &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate of real GDP indicates a 3.9-percent increase in the fourth quarter of 1997, 0.4 percentage point lower than the &quot;advance&quot; estimate; a large downward revision to net exports and smaller downward revisions to government spending and consumer spending were only partly offset by a large upward revision to business inventory investment. Despite these revisions, real GDP growth still shows an acceleration from a 3.1-percent increase in the third quarter. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.4 percent, about the same pace as in the third quarter.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0398bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-03-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-03-04</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Federal Budget Estimates, Fiscal Year 1999</Title>
        <Author>Kurt S. Bersani, Ann M. Groszkiewicz</Author>
        <Description>Each year, BEA prepares a &quot;translation&quot; of the administration's budget that puts the budget's receipts and outlays on a basis that is consistent with the framework of the NIPA's. In the NIPA framework, the Federal current deficit would be $9.9 billion in fiscal year 1999; the administration's budget shows a $9.5 billion surplus. The difference primarily results from the difference in the treatment of government investment in fixed assets; the consumption of fixed capital that is included in the NIPA's is greater than the investment that is excluded.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/1998/0398gd.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Federal budget estimates</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-03-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-04-01</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Transportation Satellite Accounts for 1992</Title>
        <Author>Bingsong Fang, Xiaoli Han, Ann M. Lawson, Sherlene K.S. Lum</Author>
        <Description>The new satellite accounts for U.S. transportation integrate information from a variety of sources to present a more comprehensive picture of the role of transportation in the U.S. economy. The new transportation satellite accounts (TSA's) are based on and are an extension of the 1992 benchmark input-output (I-O) accounts. The TSA's expand the definition of transportation activities to include transportation services by businesses for their own use, and they show more accurately the total use of these services across industries. Under the expanded TSA definition, the value added of transportation industries represents 5.0 percent of GDP in 1992, compared with the 3.1-percent share shown in the I-O accounts.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/Inputout/1998/0498io.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Satellite accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-04-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-04-02</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>The Domestic Orientation of Production and Sales by U.S. Manufacturing Affiliates of Foreign Companies</Title>
        <Author>William J. Zeile</Author>
        <Description>Detailed industry data on the production of foreign-owned U.S. manufacturing affiliates and of domestically owned manufacturing firms show that in most industries, domestic content tends to account for the dominant share of output. However, the shares for U.S. affiliates tend to be lower than those for domestically owned firms across the detailed industries, and the difference at the aggregate level increases rather than decreases when industry mix is held constant. In most industries, U.S. affiliates and domestically owned manufacturers both tend to sell most of their output in the United States, but the domestic-market shares of sales for U.S. affiliates tend to be higher than those for domestically owned firms.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/FDINVEST/1998/0498iid.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-04-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-04-03</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Ralph W. Morris, Daniel Larkins, Benyam Tsehaye</Author>
        <Description>The &quot;final&quot; estimate of real GDP indicates a 3.7-percent increase in the fourth quarter of 1997, 0.2 percentage point lower than the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate; downward revisions to consumer spending and net exports more than offset an upward revision to business fixed investment. Corporate profits decreased $9.2 billion in the fourth quarter after increasing $32.2 billion in the third; the downturn was accounted for by the profits of domestic nonfinancial corporations. The Federal Government current deficit increased $1.3 billion, to $12.1 billion, in the fourth quarter; the State and local government current surplus decreased $1.3 billion, to $110.1 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0498bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-04-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-04-04</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>State and Local Government Fiscal Position in 1997</Title>
        <Author>Florence Campi, David F. Sullivan</Author>
        <Description>The current surplus of State and local governments increased $2.5 billion, to $107.8 billion, in 1997. Receipts and current expenditures both increased at about the same pace as they had in 1996. For 1998, available information suggests some acceleration in both receipts and current expenditures and little change in the current surplus.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0498gd.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, State and local government fiscal position</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-04-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-04-05</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Fourth Quarter and Year 1997</Title>
        <Author>Christopher L. Bach</Author>
        <Description>In the fourth quarter of 1997, the U.S. current-account deficit increased to $45.6 billion from $43.1 billion in the third quarter; a decrease in the deficit on goods was more than offset by an increase in net unilateral transfers, a decrease in the surplus on services, and an increase in the deficit on investment income. In the capital account, outflows for U.S. assets abroad decelerated $14.0 billion in the fourth quarter, while inflows for foreign assets in the United States decelerated only $1.4 billion. For the year 1997, the U.S. current-account deficit increased to $166.4 billion from $148.2 billion in 1996; a shift to a deficit on investment income and an increase in the deficit on goods more than offset an increase in the surplus on services and a decrease in net unilateral transfers. In the capital account, outflows for U.S. assets abroad accelerated $74.5 billion in 1997, while inflows for foreign assets in the United States accelerated $142.9 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/BPA/1998/0498bop.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-04-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-04-06</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory­-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/1998/0498niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-04-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-05-01</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>U.S. economic activity continued to increase strongly in the first quarter of 1998, and prices paid by U.S. residents did not increase for the first time in over 40 years. The &quot;advance&quot; estimate of real GDP shows a 4.2-percent increase, up from a 3.7-percent increase in the fourth quarter of 1997. The price index for gross domestic purchases was unchanged after increasing 1.4 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0598bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-05-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-05-02</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Personal Income and Per Capita Personal Income by State and Region, 1997</Title>
        <Author>Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>Preliminary estimates of U.S. personal income show a 5.7-percent increase in 1997; Texas had the fastest increase, at 7.9 percent, and North Dakota had the only decline, at -1.3 percent. Per capita personal income for the Nation was $25,598 in 1997; Connecticut had the highest per capita income, at $36,263, and Mississippi had the lowest, at $18,272.From1989 to 1997, per capita income by region resumed a long-term trend of convergence toward the U.S. average, a trend that had been interrupted from 1979 to 1989.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/REGIONAL/perinc/1998/0598rea.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Per capita personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-05-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-05-03</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Local Area Personal Income, 1969–96</Title>
        <Author>Wallace K. Bailey</Author>
        <Description>BEA has released new estimates for 1996 and revised estimates for 1969–95 of personal income for counties, metropolitan areas, and BEA economic areas. For metropolitan areas, Las Vegas, NV-AZ, had the fastest growth in personal income from 1995 to 1996; it had also been the fastest growing area from 1990 to 1995.Yuma,AZ, was the only metropolitan area that had a decline in personal income growth from 1995 to 1996; it had been the fastest growing area from 1994 to 1995. The local area estimates incorporate the results of the revision to the annual estimates of State personal income that was released in September 1997.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/REGIONAL/perinc/1998/0598rem.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Local area personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-05-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-06-01</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Daniel Larkins, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff, Benyan Tsehaye</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 4.8 percent in the first quarter of 1998 after increasing 4.2 percent in the fourth quarter of 1997; the price index for gross domestic purchases was unchanged after increasing 1.4 percent. Corporate profits increased $4.4 billion in the first quarter after decreasing $9.2 billion in the fourth. For the year 1997, property income's rate of return for domestic nonfinancial corporations increased to 9.8 percent, the highest in nearly 30 years. The fiscal position of the Federal Government shifted from a current deficit of $12.1 billion in the fourth quarter to a current surplus of $49.0 billion in the first quarter, the first surplus in nearly 30 years; the State and local government current surplus decreased $2.5 billion, to $107.6 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0698bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-06-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-06-02</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Gross State Product by Industry, 1977–96</Title>
        <Author>Richard M. Beemiller, George K. Downey</Author>
        <Description>BEA's estimates of gross state product (GSP) have been updated to reflect the most recent annual revisions of the NIPA's, of the national estimates of gross product by industry, and of the estimates of State personal income. In 1996, real GSP increased in all States except Alaska and Hawaii; the five States with the fastest growth rates were Utah, Nevada, Delaware, Oregon, and New Hampshire. In 1996, the five States with the largest shares of nominal GSP were California, New York, Texas, Illinois, and Florida. From 1989 to 1996, the per capita GSP estimates by region show the same trend of convergence toward the U.S. average that was evident in the estimates of per capita personal income by region.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/REGIONAL/GSP/1998/0698rea.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Gross state product</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-06-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-06-03</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: New Investment in 1997 and Affiliate Operations in 1996</Title>
        <Author>Mahnaz Fahim-Nader, William J. Zeile</Author>
        <Description>Outlays by foreign investors to acquire or establish businesses in the United States decreased from a record $79.9 billion in 1996 to $70.8 billion in 1997, the first decrease since 1992; the decrease reflected a reduction in the number of very large investments and a sharp decline in new investment from Japan. In 1996, most measures of the operations of U.S. affiliates of foreign companies increased. The gross product of affiliates increased 5 percent after increasing 3 percent in 1995, and employment by affiliates increased 1 percent after increasing 2 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/FDINVEST/1998/0698iid.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, New Investment and Affiliate Operations</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-06-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-06-04</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Subject Guide: Volume 78 (1998), Numbers 1–6</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/BEAWIDE/1998/0698sg.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-06-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-06-05</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Errata: National Income and Product Accounts</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0698err.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-06-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-07-01</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Travel and Tourism Satellite Accounts for 1992</Title>
        <Author>Sumiye Okubo, Mark A. Planting</Author>
        <Description>The new satellite accounts for U.S. travel and tourism present a comprehensive picture of the importance of travel and tourism in the U.S. economy. The travel and tourism satellite accounts (TTSA's) are developed from the 1992 benchmark input-output accounts, but they integrate information from a variety of public and private sources. According to the TTSA's, travel and tourism activities accounted for 4.6–5.3 percent of total demand in the U.S. economy, for 1.9–2.2 percent of value added, and for 3.2–3.7 percent of employment.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/Inputout/1998/0798ied.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Satellite accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-07-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-07-02</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Revised Estimates for 1986–97</Title>
        <Author>Christopher L. Bach</Author>
        <Description>This year's annual revision of the balance of payments accounts incorporates major improvements to the investment income, capital, services, and goods accounts. The investment income accounts incorporate newly available results of the U.S. Treasury Department's benchmark survey of foreign portfolio investment in the United States for 1994, final results of the U.S. Treasury Department's benchmark survey of U.S. portfolio investment abroad for 1994, revised estimates of banks' income receipts and payments on foreign-currency-denominated claims and liabilities, and the results of BEA's benchmark survey of U.S. direct investment abroad for 1994. In addition, several types of transactions are reclassified. The revised estimate of the U.S. current-account balance for 1997 is -$155.2 billion, compared with the previously published estimate of -$166.4 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/BPA/1998/0798bpr.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-07-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-07-03</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Ralph W. Morris, Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>The &quot;final&quot; estimate of real GDP indicates a 5.4-percent increase in the first quarter of 1998, 0.6 percentage point higher than the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate issued last month. The upward revision was largely due to upward revisions to the change in nonfarm business inventories, to exports, and to nonresidential structures. Corporate profits increased $9.6 billion in the first quarter after decreasing $9.2 billion in the fourth; profits of domestic nonfinancial corporations and profits from the rest of the world turned up, but profits of domestic financial corporations increased less than in the fourth quarter.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0798bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-07-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-07-04</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>The International Investment Position of the United States in 1997</Title>
        <Author>Russell B. Scholl</Author>
        <Description>The net international investment position of the United States became more negative in 1997: On a current-cost basis, it changed from $767.1 billion to $1,223.6 billion, and on a market-value basis, it changed from $743.7 billion to $1,322.5 billion. The change in both positions was primarily attributable to large net capital inflows, particularly for U.S. securities and U.S. banking, and to a net negative exchange rate adjustment that resulted from the appreciation of the U.S. dollar against most foreign currencies.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/BPA/1998/0798iip.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international investment position</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-07-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-07-05</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Direct Investment Positions for 1997: Country and Industry Detail</Title>
        <Author>Sylvia E. Bargas</Author>
        <Description>In 1997, the U.S. direct investment position valued at historical cost increased 11 percent, reflecting record equity capital outflows and reinvested earnings that were only partly offset by negative currency translation adjustments. By country, the largest increases were with the United Kingdom, the Netherlands, and Canada. The foreign direct investment position in the United States valued at historical cost increased 15 percent, as a result of record capital inflows that reflected strength in equity capital, intercompany debt, and reinvested earnings. By country, the largest increases were with the Netherlands, Germany, and Canada.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/FDINVEST/1998/0798dip.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Direct investment positions: Country and industry detail</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-07-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-07-06</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, First Quarter 1998</Title>
        <Author>Anthony J. DiLullo</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit increased $2.2 billion, to $47.2 billion, in the first quarter of 1998. An increase in the deficit on goods and services was partly offset by decreases in the balance on investment income and in net unilateral transfers. In the capital account, capital outflows decreased sharply, but capital inflows decreased even more sharply. U.S. assets abroad increased $44.7 billion after increasing $123.4 billion, and foreign assets in the United States increased $90.9 billion after increasing $220.5 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/BPA/1998/0798bop.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-07-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-07-07</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/1998/0798niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-07-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-08-01</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Annual Revision of the National Income and Product Accounts: Annual Estimates, 1995–97, and Quarterly Estimates, 1995:I–1998:I</Title>
        <Author>Eugene P. Seskin</Author>
        <Description>The revised NIPA estimates show somewhat faster economic growth and a somewhat slower increase in prices than were shown by the previously published estimates. Over the period covered by the revisions, the average growth rate of real GDP was revised up 0.3 percentage point to 3.4 percent, and the average increase in the price index for gross domestic purchases was revised down 0.3 percentage point to 1.8 percent. Personal saving (and the personal saving rate) was revised down substantially, and undistributed corporate profits and the State and local government surplus or deficit were revised up substantially. The annual revisions reflect the incorporation of regular source data and the introduction of the following major changes in methodology: A redefinition affecting dividends paid by regulated investment companies (mutual funds); new source data for several types of consumer services; geometric-mean-type consumer price indexes for deflation of detailed components of personal consumption expenditures (PCE); and several new price measures—primarily producer price indexes and international price indexes—for deflation of PCE, fixed investment, exports and imports, and government spending.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0898niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-08-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-08-02</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 1.4 percent in the second quarter of 1998 after increasing 5.5 percent in the first quarter; the deceleration was primarily accounted for by a sharp downturn in inventory investment and by a slowdown in investment in producers' durable equipment. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 0.4 percent in the second quarter after decreasing 0.2 percent in the first.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0898bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-08-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-08-03</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Personal Income by State and Region, First Quarter 1998</Title>
        <Author>Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>Personal income in the Nation increased $112.0 billion, or 1.6 percent, in the first quarter of 1998; the largest increase was in the Southeast region, which accounted for 25 percent of the growth. By State, the fastest growth in personal income was in Alaska, South Carolina, Massachusetts, Colorado, and Arizona. The slowest growth was in North Dakota, Delaware, Vermont, and Arkansas.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/REGIONAL/perinc/1998/0898rea.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-08-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-08-04</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>National Income and Product Accounts Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0898nipa.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-08-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-08-05</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Annual NIPA Revision: Revised Estimates for 1982–94</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0898nip2.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-08-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-08-06</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>GDP and Other Major NIPA Series, 1929–97</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0898nip3.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-08-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-09-01</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Daniel Larkins, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff, Laura M. Bilenki</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 1.6 percent in the second quarter of 1998 after increasing 5.5 percent in the first quarter; the price index for gross domestic purchases increased 0.4 percent after decreasing 0.2 percent. Corporate profits decreased $9.5 billion in the second quarter after increasing $8.4 billion in the first. In the second quarter, the Federal Government current surplus increased $13.8 billion, to $72.6 billion, and the State and local government current surplus decreased $5.4 billion, to $134.8 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0998bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-09-09</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-09-02</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Multinational Companies: Operations in 1996</Title>
        <Author>Raymond J. Mataloni, Jr.</Author>
        <Description>The operations of U.S. multinational companies (MNC's) continued to grow relatively rapidly in 1996: Worldwide gross product of U.S. parent companies and their majority-owned foreign affiliates (MOFA's) increased 7 percent, employment increased 2 percent, and capital expenditures increased 5 percent. Gross product of both U.S. parents and their MOFA's grew 7 percent in 1996. From 1989 to 1996, U.S.-MNC gross product was mainly accounted for by U.S. parents, but the share that was accounted for by MOFA's edged up from 23 percent to 25 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/USINVEST/1998/0998mnc.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. multinational companies</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-09-09</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-09-03</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Customer Satisfaction Report</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/BEAWIDE/1998/0998cust.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-09-09</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-09-04</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Annual NIPA Revision: Newly Available Table</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0998nipa.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-09-09</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-09-05</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Updated Summary NIPA Methodologies</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/0998niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-09-09</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-09-06</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Fixed Reproducible Tangible Wealth in the United States: Revised Estimates for 1995–97 and Summary Estimates for 1925–97</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/1998/0998wlth.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Fixed reproducible tangible wealth in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-09-09</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-09-07</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: Detail for Historical &amp; ;Cost Position and Related Capital and Income Flows, 1997</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey H. Lowe</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/FDINVEST/1998/0998fdi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-09-09</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-10-01</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>State Personal Income, Revised Estimates for 1982–97</Title>
        <Author>Wallace K. Bailey</Author>
        <Description>The annual estimates of State personal income for 1995–97 were revised to incorporate the results of the recent annual revision of the national income and product accounts (NIPA's), as well as newly available State-level source data; in addition, the State estimates were revised back to 1982 to incorporate the NIPA redefinition of personal dividend income. The revisions to the State estimates generally reflected the downward revisions to the national estimates; among the States, the relative rates of change in personal income and the relative rankings of State per capita personal income changed little.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/REGIONAL/perinc/1998/1098rem.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-10-08</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-10-02</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Ralph W. Morris, Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 1.8 percent in the second quarter of 1998, according to the &quot;final&quot; estimate; the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate issued last month had shown a 1.6-percent increase. The largest upward revision was to consumer spending. Corporate profits decreased $8.6 billion in the second quarter after increasing $8.4 billion in the first; profits of domestic nonfinancial corporations decreased after no change, and profits of domestic financial corporations and from the rest of the world turned down.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/1098bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-10-08</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-10-03</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Second Quarter 1998</Title>
        <Author>Douglas B. Weinberg</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit increased $9.8 billion, to $56.5 billion, in the second quarter of 1998. A substantial increase in the deficit on goods and an increase in the deficit on investment income more than offset a small increase in the surplus on services and a small decrease in net unilateral transfers. In the capital account, capital outflows increased less than capital inflows. U.S. assets abroad increased $97.5 billion after increasing $45.6 billion, and foreign assets in the United States increased $163.4 billion after increasing $95.5 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/BPA/1998/1098bop.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-10-08</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-10-04</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Sales and Purchases of Private Services: U.S. Cross­Border Transactions in 1997 and Sales by Affiliates in 1996</Title>
        <Author>Michael A. Mann, Laura L.Brokenbaugh, Sylvia E. Bargas</Author>
        <Description>In 1997, U.S. cross-border sales (exports) of private services increased less than U.S. cross-border purchases (imports) of private services. In 1996,sales of services in the United States by U.S. affiliates of foreign companies increased less than sales of services abroad by foreign affiliates of U.S. companies. Nevertheless, the U.S. continued to register sizable surpluses on both cross-border and affiliate services transactions, reflecting the U.S. comparative advantage in the provision of services</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/INTSERV/1998/1098srv.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international sales and purchases of private services</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-10-08</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-10-05</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Annual NIPA Revision: Newly Available Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/1098nipa.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-10-08</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-10-06</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory­-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, 1994:IV–1998:II</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/1998/1098niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-10-08</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-10-07</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Direct Investment Abroad: Detail for Historical-­Cost Position and Related Capital and Income Flows, 1997</Title>
        <Author>Mark W. New, Laura A. Downey, Javier J. Hodge, Marie K. Laddomada, Sherry Lee, Leila C. Morrison, Gary M. Solamon, Dwayne Torney, Marie Colosimo, Arnold Gilbert, Jeffrey H. Lowe</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/USINVEST/1998/1098iid.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-10-08</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-11-01</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Manufacturing Earnings in BEA Component Economic Areas, 1996</Title>
        <Author>G. Andrew Bernat, Jr.</Author>
        <Description>Among BEA component economic areas (CEA's), the CEA's with the highest average manufacturing earnings per job are those that have a greater proportion of manufacturing jobs, have a large, well-educated workforce, and have higher concentrations of industry clustering. The results from a regression analysis show that industry mix is the most important factor associated with average manufacturing earnings per job and that the education level of the workforce and the extent of industry clustering are also significant.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/REGIONAL/perinc/1998/1198cea.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-11-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-11-02</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>U.S. economic activity picked up in the third quarter of 1998: Real GDP increased 3.3 percent after increasing 1.8 percent in the second quarter. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 0.5 percent after increasing 0.4 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/1198bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-11-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-11-03</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Motor Vehicles, Model Year 1998</Title>
        <Author>Ralph W. Morris</Author>
        <Description>In model year 1998, sales of motor vehicles increased to 15.7 million units from 15.4 million units in model year 1997. The increase was more than accounted for by another strong increase in sales of new trucks, which reached a record 7.6 million units. Sales of new cars declined for the fourth consecutive year.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/1998/1198cbad.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Motor vehicles</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-11-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-11-04</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Comparison of BEA Estimates of Personal Income and IRS Estimates of Adjusted Gross Income: New Estimates for 1996 and Revised Estimates for 1982--95</Title>
        <Author>Thae S. Park</Author>
        <Description>BEA's measure of personal income and the IRS measure of adjusted gross income are reconciled through a series of adjustments for definitional differences between the two measures. This year's reconciliation reflects the recent annual revision of the NIPA's, including the redefinition of dividend payments and the incorporation of revised IRS tabulations of capital gains distributions.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/1998/1198gd.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Comparison of BEA personal income and IRS adjusted gross income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-11-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-11-05</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Gross Product by Industry, 1995--97</Title>
        <Author>Sherlene K.S. Lum, Brian C. Moyer</Author>
        <Description>The estimates of gross product by industry for 1995--96 have been revised to incorporate the results of this year's annual revision of the NIPA's and newly available source data, and new estimates for 1997 have been prepared. In 1997, durable goods manufacturing and services were the largest contributors to the 3.9-percent increase in real GDP; finance, insurance, and real estate and services were the largest contributors to the 1.9-percent increase in the GDP price index.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/Inputout/1998/1198gpo.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Gross product by industry</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-11-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-11-06</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Reconciliation of the U.S.-Canadian Current Account, 1996 and 1997</Title>
        <Author>Anthony J. DiLullo, Hugh Henderson</Author>
        <Description>For both 1996 and 1997, the reconciliation of the U.S.-Canadian current account results in a U.S. current-account deficit with Canada that is larger than the deficit shown in the U.S. published accounts. The annual reconciliation shows how the current-account estimates would appear if both countries used the same definitions, methodologies, and data sources.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/BPA/1998/1198bop.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Reconciliation of the U.S. Canadian current account</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-11-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-11-07</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Personal Income by State and Region, Second Quarter 1998</Title>
        <Author>Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>Personal income in the Nation increased $78.0 billion, or 1.1 percent, in the second quarter of 1998. By region, the largest increase was in the Southeast, which accounted for 22 percent of the growth. By State, the fastest growth in personal income was in Nevada, Arizona, South Carolina, Utah, and Vermont. The slowest growth was in South Dakota, Hawaii, New Jersey, and Michigan</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/REGIONAL/perinc/1998/1198rea.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-11-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-12-01</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Reliability of the Quarterly and Annual Estimates of GDP and Gross Domestic Income</Title>
        <Author>Bruce T. Grimm, Robert P. Parker</Author>
        <Description>An analysis of the reliability of the current quarterly estimates of real GDP since 1983 shows that they almost always provide the correct indication of the direction of change in U.S. economic activity. About three-fourths of the time, the current quarterly estimates correctly indicate whether the pace of U.S. economic activity is picking up or slowing down and whether it is deviating from its long-term growth trend. More than two-thirds of the time, the current quarterly estimates correctly identify the cyclical turning points in U.S. economic activity, and when they have &quot;missed,&quot; it has never been by more than one quarter.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/1298od.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Other information</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-12-09</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-12-02</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Investment in New Structures and Equipment in 1992 by Using Industries</Title>
        <Author>Belinda Bonds, Tim Aylor</Author>
        <Description>The 1992 capital flow table is a supplementary table to the 1992 benchmark input-output (I-O) accounts that shows the flows of new structures and equipment to the private industries that purchased or leased them in 1992. The capital flow table can be used in conjunction with tables from the I-O accounts to identify the markets for new structures and equipment, and it can be used to estimate the output by commodity that is required to support a change in new investment or to estimate the effects of an industry's purchase of new structures and equipment on the outputs of all industries.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/Inputout/1998/1298io.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Input-output accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-12-09</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-12-03</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Daniel Larkins, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff, Melissa C. Wilson, Laura M. Bilenki</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 3.9 percent in the third quarter of 1998 after increasing 1.8 percent in the second quarter; the price index for gross domestic purchases increased 0.5 percent after increasing 0.4 percent. Corporate profits increased $3.3 billion in the third quarter after decreasing $8.6 billion in the second. The Federal Government current surplus increased $18.7 billion, to $93.1 billion, in the third quarter, and the State and local government current surplus increased $8.7 billion, to $150.0 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/1998/1298bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-12-09</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-12-04</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Federal Personal Income Tax Liabilities and Payments, 1995--96</Title>
        <Author>Thae S. Park</Author>
        <Description>According to newly available BEA estimates of Federal personal income tax liabilities, liabilities exceeded payments by $5.0 billion in 1995, and payments exceeded liabilities by $1.1 billion in 1996. These estimates incorporate the results of the annual NIPA revision that was released in July and newly available tax return data from the Internal Revenue Service.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/1998/1298fpi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Federal personal income tax liabilities and payments</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-12-09</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-12-05</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>An Ownership-Based Disaggregation of the U.S. Current Account, 1982--96</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey H. Lowe</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/BPA/1998/1298iid.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Other information</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-12-09</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-12-06</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>Subject Guide: Volume 78 (1998)</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/BEAWIDE/1998/1298sg.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-12-09</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-78-12-07</ID>
        <Volume>78</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>1998</Year>
        <Title>1999 Release Dates for BEA Estimates</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/BEAWIDE/1998/1298rd.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>1998-12-09</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
