<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-01-01</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Final Estimates for the Third Quarter of 2002</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 4.0 percent in the third quarter, according to the &quot;final&quot; estimate, up from a 1.3-percent increase in the second quarter. The &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate issued a month ago had also shown a 4.0- percent increase. Corporate profits decreased $14.0 billion (1.8 percent at a quarterly rate) in the third quarter, about the same decrease as in the two preceding quarters.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/01January/0103BSF.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-01-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/01January/0103BSF.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-01-02</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, 2002:III</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>Four tables present the latest quarterly and monthly estimates of real inventories and sales for manufacturing and trade and of real inventories by stage of fabrication for manufacturing.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/01January/0103ISR.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-01-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/01January/0103ISR.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-01-03</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Preview of the Revised NIPA Estimates for 1997: Effects of Incorporating the 1997 Benchmark I-O Accounts and Proposed Definitional and Statistical Changes</Title>
        <Author>Stephanie H. McCulla, Carol E. Moylan</Author>
        <Description>BEA has prepared preliminary revised estimates of GDP for 1997 that reflect the newly available 1997 benchmark input-output accounts. These estimates, along with a number of definitional and other statistical changes that BEA is considering, will be incorporated in the upcoming comprehensive revision of the NIPA's.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/01January/0103NIPAs%26IO.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-01-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/01January/0103RevisedNIPA.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-01-04</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>An Ownership-Based Framework of the U.S. Current Account, 1989-2001</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey H. Lowe</Author>
        <Description>BEA has updated its ownership-based current account with revised estimates for 1995-99, new detailed estimates for 2000, and new summary estimates for 2001. The ownership-based framework supplements BEA's international transactions accounts by highlighting the participation of multinational companies in international markets for goods and services both through cross-border trade and through sales by locally established affiliates.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/01January/0103CurrentAcct.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-01-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-01-05</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Third Quarter 2002</Title>
        <Author>Douglas B. Weinberg, Patricia E. Abaroa</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit was little changed, at $127.0 billion, in the third quarter, as a decrease in the deficit on income more than offset an increase in the deficit on goods, a decrease in the surplus on services, and an increase in net outflows for unilateral current transfers. Net financial inflows stepped up sharply to $172.4 billion, reflecting a shift in financial flows for U.S.-owned assets abroad to net inflows from net outflows.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/01January/0103ita.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-01-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/international/bp_web/</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-02-01</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Advance Estimates for the Fourth Quarter of 2002</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>The irregular pattern of U.S. economic growth continued in the fourth quarter of 2002: Real GDP increased 0.7 percent after increases of 4.0 percent in the third quarter, 1.3 percent in the second quarter, and 5.0 percent in the first quarter. The fourth-quarter deceleration reflected a slowdown in consumer spending and downturns in inventory investment and exports. U.S. inflation stepped up but remained in the moderate range: The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.8 percent after increasing 1.2 percent in the third quarter.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/02February/0203BSA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-02-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/02February/0214BSA.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-02-02</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>BEA's International Accounts</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>BEA's international accounts present estimates of the transactions between U.S. and foreign residents and estimates of the value of accumulated stocks of U.S.-owned assets abroad and of foreign-owned assets in the United States. BEA also collects, processes, and provides comprehensive data on international services and on U.S. direct investment abroad and foreign direct investment in the United States. In addition, BEA conducts a variety of research and analytical activities in support of the international accounts.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/02February/0203ITAinserts.pdf</URL>
        <Category>General</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-02-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-02-03</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Personal Income by State, Third Quarter 2002</Title>
        <Author>G. Andrew Bernat, Jr, John R. Kort</Author>
        <Description>The growth in personal income for the Nation slowed to 0.9 percent in the third quarter of 2002 from 1.2 percent in the second quarter. In half of the States, personal income grew at least as fast in the third quarter as in the second, but several large States--including California, New York, Texas, and Illinois--were among the States whose growth slowed in the third quarter. Growth ranged from 1.5 percent in Montana to 0.5 percent in Michigan.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/02February/0203SPI.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-02-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-03-01</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Preliminary Estimates for the Fourth Quarter of 2002</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 1.4 percent in the fourth quarter of 2002, according to the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate, after increasing 4.0 percent in the third quarter. The &quot;advance&quot; estimate issued last month had shown a 0.7-percent increase in the fourth quarter. The upward revision was mainly attributable to an upward revision to inventory investment. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.6 percent after increasing 1.2 percent. The advance estimate had shown a 1.8-percent increase.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/03March/0303BPS.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-03-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/03March/0303BPS.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-03-02</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Federal Budget Estimates, Fiscal Year 2004</Title>
        <Author>Claire G. Pitzer, Benyam Tsehaye</Author>
        <Description>Each year, BEA prepares an adjusted presentation of the administration's budget estimates (as presented in Budget of the United States Government, Fiscal Year 2004) that is consistent with the framework of the NIPA's. The fiscal year relationships derived from the budget estimates are then used in preparing BEA's current quarterly estimates of Federal Government receipts and expenditures. For fiscal year 2004, the Federal current deficit on the NIPA basis is estimated at $301.2 billion, compared with the deficit of $307.4 billion in the administration's budget.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/03March/0303FedBudget.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Federal budget estimates</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-03-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/03March/0303FedBudget.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-03-03</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>BEA's Regional Accounts</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>BEA's regional accounts present estimates of State personal income, of personal income for counties, metropolitan areas, and BEA economic areas, and of gross state product. These estimates are consistent with the estimates of personal income and gross domestic product that are presented in BEA's national income and product accounts. BEA also prepares regional economic multipliers that can be used to estimate the effects of the changes in the output of one or more industries in an area on the output, employment, and labor earnings in the other industries in the area.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/03March/0303Regionalinserts.pdf</URL>
        <Category>General</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-03-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-04-01</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Final Estimates for the Fourth Quarter of 2002</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Raymen G. Labella</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 1.4 percent in the fourth quarter of 2002, according to the &quot;final&quot; estimate, the same increase as shown in the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate issued last month. Corporate profits increased $25.1 billion (3.2 percent at a quarterly rate) in the fourth quarter. The Federal Government current deficit increased $37.2 billion, to $247.7 billion, and the state and local government current deficit decreased $4.1 billion, to $50.6 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/04April/0403BSF.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-04-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/04April/0403BSF.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-04-02</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, 2002:IV</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>Four tables present the latest quarterly and monthly estimates of real inventories and sales for manufacturing and trade and of real inventories by stage of fabrication for manufacturing.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/04April/0403ISR.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-04-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/04April/0403inventories.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-04-03</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Income and Outlays of Households and of Nonprofit Institutions Serving Households</Title>
        <Author>Charles Ian Mead, Clinton P. McCully, Marshall B. Reinsdorf</Author>
        <Description>As part of the upcoming comprehensive revision of the NIPA's, BEA plans to introduce two new annual tables. The first table shows income and outlays of households separately from those of nonprofit institutions serving households. The second table reconciles the new estimates for nonprofit institutions serving households with the Internal Revenue Service estimates for nonprofit institutions. Preliminary estimates for 1992-2001 prepared by BEA indicate that the decline in the personal saving rate from 1992 to 1998 was entirely attributable to a decline in household saving, but the decline from 1998 to 2001 was attributable to declines in both household saving and saving by nonprofit institutions serving households.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/04April/0403household.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-04-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/04April/0403household.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-04-04</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Fourth Quarter and Year 2002</Title>
        <Author>Christopher L. Bach</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/04April/0403ITA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-04-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/international/bp_web/</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-05-01</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Advance Estimates for the First Quarter of 2003</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>U.S. production continued to grow slowly in the first quarter of 2003: Real GDP increased 1.6 percent after increasing 1.4 percent in the fourth quarter of 2002. Growth in consumer spending and government spending was weak, and private investment, exports, and imports all declined. Inflation stepped up: The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 3.6 percent after increasing 1.8 percent. Most of the step-up was attributable to a jump in energy prices.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/05May/0503BSA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-05-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/05May/0503BSA.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-05-02</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Gross Domestic Product by Industry for 2002</Title>
        <Author>Robert E. Yuskavage, Erich H. Strassner</Author>
        <Description>In mid-April, BEA released estimates of real GDP by industry for 2002, the first time the real estimates have been released on an accelerated basis. According to these estimates, real GDP in private services-producing industries led the broad-based economic growth in 2002. Growth in wholesale and retail trade and in electric, gas, and sanitary services was particularly strong. Real GDP in private goods-producing industries also grew in 2002, following a slight decline in 2001. The upswing primarily reflected an upturn in nondurable-goods manufacturing.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/05May/0503GDPbyIndy.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Industry, Industry Accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-05-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/05May/GDPbyInd.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-05-03</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>State Personal Income and Per Capita Personal Income, 2002</Title>
        <Author>G. Andrew Bernat, Jr.</Author>
        <Description>Growth in per capita personal income slowed in 34 states in 2002, reflecting the slowdown in growth in per capita personal income for the Nation to 1.7 percent from 2.2 percent in 2001. Growth rates ranged from more than 4.0 percent in North Dakota, Montana, and Louisiana to less than 0.5 percent in Nevada and Texas. The slowdown in the growth in per capita personal income for the Nation reflected a slowdown in the growth in personal income, primarily in net earnings but also in dividend, interest, and rental income. By industry, earnings in both farms and manufacturing declined.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/05May/0503SPI.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-05-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-05-04</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Local Area Personal Income, 1999-2001</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey L. Newman</Author>
        <Description>BEA recently released the results of this year's annual revision of personal income for counties, metropolitan areas, and BEA economic areas. These estimates incorporate the results of the most recent annual revision of state personal income and newly available county-level source data. In 2001, the gap in personal income growth rates for urban and rural areas narrowed to its smallest amount since 1996. Personal income in metropolitan areas increased 3.4 percent, and personal income in nonmetropolitan areas in-creased 2.9 percent. Despite a decline in 2001, the San Francisco, CA, metropolitan area again had the highest per capita personal income, at $57,714. Of the counties with population exceeding 50,000, Loudoun County, VA, had the fastest growth in personal income, at 12.5 percent. New York County (Manhattan), NY, again had the highest per capita personal income, at $92,984.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/05May/0503LAPI.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Local area personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-05-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-06-01</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Preliminary Estimates for the First Quarter of 2003</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Michelle D. Robinson</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 1.9 percent in the first quarter of 2003, according to the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimates, after increasing 1.4 percent in the fourth quarter of 2002. The &quot;advance&quot; estimates issued last month had shown a 1.6-percent increase. Corporate profits increased $7.9 billion (1.0 percent at a quarterly rate) in the first quarter. The Federal Government current deficit increased $18.4 billion, to $266.1 billion, and the state and local government current deficit increased $16.3 billion, to $66.9 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/06June/0603BSP.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-06-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/06June/0603BSP.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-06-02</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Preview of the 2003 Comprehensive Revision of the National Income and Product Accounts: Changes in Definitions and Classifications</Title>
        <Author>Brent R. Moulton, Eugene P. Seskin</Author>
        <Description>The upcoming comprehensive revision will feature a number of changes in definitions and classifications that update the NIPA's in order to better portray U.S. economic activity. These changes will address data gaps and other short-comings, will improve consistency and integration with other accounts, and will improve consistency with international guidelines. The major definitional changes are as follows: Recognize the implicit services provided by property and casualty insurance and provide a more appropriate treatment of insured losses, allocate a portion of the implicit services of commercial banks to borrowers, recognize explicitly the services produced by general government and treat government purchases of goods and services as intermediate inputs, and broaden the definition of national income to include all net incomes earned in production.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/06June/0603NIPArevs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-06-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-06-03</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Receipts and Expenditures of State Governments and of Local Governments, 1959-2001</Title>
        <Author>Bruce E. Baker</Author>
        <Description>Newly available estimates that separate receipts and expenditures of state gov-ernments from those of local governments facilitate long-term analyses of each level of government. Over the past four decades, receipts and expenditures at all levels of government--Federal, state, and local--grew relative to the growth of the overall economy. For state governments, expenditures--particularly those for Medicaid--grew faster than receipts, so that by 2001, states ran a record deficit of $64.0 billion. For local governments, receipts and expenditures grew at about the same pace. Local governments ran a surplus throughout the period; in 2001, the surplus was $32.6 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/06June/0603%20Rcpt%26Exp.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-06-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/06June/Stategov't.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-06-04</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: New Investment in 2002</Title>
        <Author>Thomas W. Anderson</Author>
        <Description>Outlays by foreign direct investors to acquire or establish businesses in the United States were $52.6 billion in 2002, down 64 percent from 2001 and 84 percent below the record $335.6 billion in 2000. The drop in 2002 reflected continuing weakness in the U.S. economy and in many foreign economies and a falloff in merger and acquisition activity worldwide.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/06June/0603FDUIS.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-06-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/06June/FDIUS.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-06-05</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Gross State Product by Industry, 1999-2001</Title>
        <Author>Sharon D. Panek, Ndidi O. Obidoa</Author>
        <Description>New estimates of gross state product (GSP) confirm that the slowdown in U.S. economic growth in 2001 was widespread. Real GSP declined in 20 states, and it decelerated in an additional 26 states. Manufacturing declined in 40 states. Of the 10 states with the largest declines in real GSP, manufacturing contributed the most to the declines in all of them except Alaska. Revisions to the GSP estimates for 1999 and 2000 were generally small. The revised estimates incorporate the results of the most recent annual revisions of state personal income and of the national income and product accounts and newly available state-level source data.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/06June/0603GSP.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Gross state product by industry</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-06-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Appendices</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/06June/AppendAB.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-06-06</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Subject Guide for the January-June 2003 Issues</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/06June/0603SbjGuide.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-06-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-07-01</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Final Estimates for the First Quarter of 2003</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 1.4 percent in the first quarter of 2003, according to the &quot;final&quot; estimates, the same increase as in the fourth quarter of 2002. The &quot;preliminary&quot; first-quarter estimates issued a month ago had shown a 1.9-percent increase. The downward revision to GDP was largely accounted for by a downward revision to inventory investment. Corporate profits increased $20.4 billion (2.6 percent at a quarterly rate) in the first quarter, an upward revision of $12.5 billion from the estimates issued a month ago.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/07July/0703bsf.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-07-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/07July/0703bsf.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-07-02</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, 2003:I</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>Four tables present the latest quarterly and monthly estimates of real inventories and sales for manufacturing and trade and of real inventories by stage of fabri-cation for manufacturing.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/07July/0703ISR.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-07-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-07-03</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>The International Investment Position of the United States at Yearend 2002</Title>
        <Author>Elena L. Nguyen</Author>
        <Description>In 2002, the net international investment position of the United States became more negative, whether measured on a current-cost basis or on a market-value basis. The net position at current cost was -$2,387.2 billion at yearend 2002, compared with -$1,979.9 billion (revised from the previous estimate of -$1,948.1 billion) at yearend 2001. The increase in the negative position was mainly due to large net foreign purchases of U.S. securities, a shift by U.S. investors to net sellers of foreign securities, and large declines in stock market prices that lowered the value of U.S.-owned assets abroad more than the value of foreign-owned assets in the United States.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/07July/0703ITAInvest.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international investment position</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-07-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/07July/0703ITAInvest.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-07-04</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Direct Investment Positions for 2002: Country and Industry Detail</Title>
        <Author>Maria Borga</Author>
        <Description>In 2002, growth in the historical-cost position of U.S. direct investment abroad (USDIA) picked up, while the historical-cost position of foreign direct investment in the United States (FDIUS) declined for the first time since at least 1946. The 10-percent increase in the USDIA position reflected strong reinvested earnings and a shift from inflows to outflows on intercompany debt transactions. The 1-percent decrease in the FDIUS position reflected financial restructuring and writedowns of investments, reduced requirements by existing U.S. affiliates for financing by their foreign parents, and a sharp slowdown in new investment by foreign parents.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/07July/0703DirectInvest.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Direct investment positions: Country and industry detail</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-07-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-07-05</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Annual Revision of the U.S. International Accounts, 1992-2002</Title>
        <Author>Christopher L. Bach</Author>
        <Description>Each year, estimates in the U.S. international transactions accounts and in the U.S. international investment position accounts are revised to incorporate statistical and methodological changes and regularly available source data. This year, major statistical changes include the incorporation of the results of the U.S. Treasury Department's Benchmark Survey of U.S. Portfolio Investment Abroad as of December 31, 2001; of the results of BEA's Benchmark Survey of U.S. Direct Investment Abroad for 1999; and of newly available detail from the U.S. Treasury Department's statistical collection system. In addition, a major definitional change has been made to the estimates of insurance services. Finally, BEA has greatly improved the presentation in the international transactions accounts of the estimates of direct investment and of banking, nonbanking, and securities transactions.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/07July/0703ITAAnnualRev.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-07-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/international/bp_web</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-07-06</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>How BEA Aligns and Augments Source Data From the U.S. Treasury Department for Inclusion in the International Transactions Accounts</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>The estimates of financial-account flows in BEA's international transactions accounts (ITA's) are built up from data collected by the U.S. Treasury Department. BEA makes numerous adjustments to the Treasury data in order to align the data with balance of payments concepts and to close gaps in coverage. To provide users with a clearer picture of these adjustments, BEA has prepared three tables that show the relationship between the ITA estimates and the Treasury data.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/07July/0703SpecialNote.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-07-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/07July/0703SpecialNote.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-07-07</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, First Quarter 2003</Title>
        <Author>Douglas B. Weinberg, Patricia E. Abaroa</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit increased $7.5 billion, to $136.1 billion, in the first quarter. About half of the increase was accounted for by an increase in the deficit on goods, but decreases in the surpluses on services and on income and an increase in net outflows for unilateral current transfers also contributed. Net recorded financial inflows decreased $39.8 billion, as financial outflows for U.S.-owned assets abroad increased and financial inflows for foreign-owned assets in the United States decreased.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/07July/0703ITAQuarterly.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-07-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/international/bp_web</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-08-01</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Advance Estimates for the Second Quarter of 2003</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>U.S. production stepped up in the second quarter of 2003: Real GDP increased 2.4 percent after increasing 1.4 percent in the first quarter. Federal spending on national defense and consumer spending on durable goods both turned up. Inflation slowed sharply: The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 0.3 percent after increasing 3.4 percent. The slowdown was largely attributable to a downturn in energy prices.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/08August/0803BSA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-08-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/08August/0803bsa.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-08-02</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Preview of the 2003 Comprehensive Revision of the National Income and Product Accounts: New and Redesigned Tables</Title>
        <Author>Nicole Mayerhauser, Shelly Smith, David F. Sullivan</Author>
        <Description>The upcoming comprehensive revision will feature significant changes in the presentation of the NIPA's. These changes are designed to make it easier for data users to locate information and to improve the comparability of the NIPA's with other U.S. accounts, such as BEA's input-output accounts and the Federal Reserve Board's flow of funds accounts, and with the accounts of other nations. Among the major changes are the following: An updated presentation of the NIPA summary accounts that shows the composition of production and the distribution of incomes earned in production, new and redesigned tables that reflect changes in definitions and classifications, new tables that highlight percent changes and contributions to percent change, and a new organization and numbering system for the NIPA tables.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/08August/0803NIPA-Preview.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-08-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-08-03</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Information Technology and Productivity: The Case of the Financial Sector</Title>
        <Author>Lawrence R. Klein, Cynthia Saltzman, Vijaya G. Duggal</Author>
        <Description>It is widely held that infusions of information technology beginning in the 1980s and intensifying in the 1990s have raised the overall productivity of the U.S. economy and spurred economic growth. In this article, Nobel laureate Lawrence Klein and Cynthia Saltzman and Vijaya Duggal, both professors at Widener University in Pennsylvania, present the results of their study of the impact of information technology on the financial sector, one of the first sectors to use computer services on a large scale and for a prolonged period. Using data from BEA's benchmark and annual input-output accounts, the authors confirm the large and prolonged contributions of information technology to the productivity gains in the finance sector.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/08August/0803IT-Prod.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Industry, Industry Accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-08-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-08-04</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Affiliates of Foreign Companies: Operations in 2001</Title>
        <Author>William J. Zeile</Author>
        <Description>The current-dollar gross product of U.S. nonbank affiliates of foreign companies fell 6 percent in 2001, the first decrease since annual data on affiliate operations became available in 1977. The U.S. affiliate share of U.S. gross domestic product in private industries dropped from a record 6.9 percent in 2000 to 6.4 percent in 2001, reversing a 5-year uptrend. The downturn in the gross product of U.S. affiliates reflected a sharp drop in new foreign investment and a combination of foreign selloffs of U.S. affiliates and of reductions in ongoing affiliate production.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/08August/0803USAffiliates.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-08-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-08-05</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>State Personal Income: First Quarter 2003 and Revised 2002</Title>
        <Author>G. Andrew Bernat, Jr., Robert L. Brown, John R. Kort</Author>
        <Description>Growth in personal income picked up in 39 states in the first quarter of 2003, reflecting the acceleration in growth in personal income for the Nation to 0.9 percent from 0.6 percent in the fourth quarter of 2002. The majority of the fastest growing states were in either the Plains region or the Rocky Mountain region, where growth was particularly rapid in natural resources and mining. As a result of the incorporation of newly available and revised source data on wages and salaries, the estimate of the U.S. total of state personal income for 2002 was revised down $31.2 billion, to $8,891.1 billion. New York had the largest downward revision to personal income.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/08August/0803SPI.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-08-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-09-01</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Preliminary Estimates for the Second Quarter of 2003</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Michelle D. Robinson</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 3.1 percent in the second quarter of 2003, according to the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimates, after increasing 1.4 percent in the first quarter. The &quot;advance&quot; estimates issued last month had shown a 2.4-percent increase in the second quarter. Corporate profits increased $88.3 billion (10.8 percent at a quarterly rate) in the second quarter. The Federal Government current deficit increased $108.1 billion, to $383.4 billion, and the state and local government current deficit decreased $51.4 billion, to $15.5 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/09September/0903bsp.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-09-22</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/09September/0903bsp.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-09-02</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Preview of the 2003 Comprehensive Revision of the National Income and Product Accounts: Statistical Changes</Title>
        <Author>Carol E. Moylan, Brooks B. Robinson</Author>
        <Description>The upcoming comprehensive revision will feature a number of statistical changes that improve the quality of the NIPA estimates by incorporating data from new sources and by introducing new methods and techniques. The major source data include the 1997 benchmark input-output accounts, the 1997 economic censuses, and regular source data that would normally be incorporated in an annual revision of the NIPAs. The major methodological changes include the following: Convert the industry estimates of income and employment to a NAICS basis; employ new methods for estimating dealers' margins and net purchases of used vehicles in motor vehicle output; incorporate a new adjustment for stock options into the estimates of corporate profits; and incorporate several new price indexes, including new price indexes for nonresidential structures and for photocopying equipment.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/09September/0903NIPAPreview.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-09-22</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-09-03</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Measuring the Services of Commercial Banks in the NIPAs: Changes in Concepts and Methods</Title>
        <Author>Dennis J. Fixler, Marshall B. Reinsdorf, George M. Smith</Author>
        <Description>As part of the upcoming NIPA comprehensive revision, the measure of banks' implicit financial services will be changed to allocate a portion of these services to borrowers; currently, all of these services are allocated to depositors. The implicit services to borrowers will be measured as the difference between the average interest rate paid by borrowers and a risk-free &quot;reference rate,&quot; and the implicit services to depositors will be measured as the difference between the &quot;reference rate&quot; and the average interest rate paid to depositors. As a result of this change, the imputed output of banks will be reduced, and GDP and gross domestic income will be reduced even more.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/09September/0903banking.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-09-22</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-09-04</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: Detail for Historical-Cost Position and Related Capital and Income Flows, 2002</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey H. Lowe</Author>
        <Description>These estimates, which incorporate two major changes in industry classification, show the geographic and industrial composition of foreign companies' investment in the United States and the related capital, income, and services flows.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/09September/0903fdius.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-09-22</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-09-05</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Direct Investment Abroad: Detail for Historical-Cost Position and Related Capital and Income Flows, 2002</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey H. Lowe</Author>
        <Description>These estimates, which incorporate the results of BEA's 1999 benchmark survey of U.S. direct investment abroad, show the geographic and industrial composition of U.S. companies' investment abroad and the related capital, income, and services flows.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/09September/0903usdia.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-09-22</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/09September/0903usdia.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-09-06</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Schedule of BEA News Releases in 2004</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/bea/newsrel/2004rd.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-09-22</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-10-01</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Final Estimates for the Second Quarter of 2003</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 3.3 percent in the second quarter, according to the final estimates. Last month, the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimates had shown a 3.1-percent increase. The upward revision was mainly accounted for by inventory investment and residential investment. Corporate profits increased $80.6 billion (9.9 percent at a quarterly rate) in the second quarter, a downward revision of $7.7 billion from the estimate released a month ago.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/10October/1003bsf.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-10-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/10October/1003bsf.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-10-02</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, 2003:II</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>Four tables present the latest quarterly and monthly estimates of real inventories and sales for manufacturing and trade and of real inventories by stage of fabrication for manufacturing.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/10October/1003ISR.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-10-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-10-03</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Measuring the Services of Property-Casualty Insurance in the NIPAs: Changes in Concepts and Methods</Title>
        <Author>Baoline Chen, Dennis J. Fixler</Author>
        <Description>As part of the upcoming comprehensive revision of the NIPAs, the measure of the services of property and casualty insurance will be changed in order to recognize the implicit services that are funded by investment income, to adopt a treatment of insured losses that is more consistent with the economic behavior of the insurer, and to change the treatment of reinsurance. As a result of this change, the average annual output of property-casualty insurance has significantly increased, and the large swings in the measured services that are caused by catastrophes are eliminated.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/10October/1003Insurance2.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-10-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-10-04</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Second Quarter 2003</Title>
        <Author>Patricia E. Abaroa, Renee M. Sauers</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit increased $7.5 billion, to $136.1 billion, in the second quarter. About half of the increase was accounted for by an increase in the deficit on goods, but decreases in the surpluses on services and on income and an increase in net outflows for unilateral current transfers also contributed. Net recorded financial inflows decreased $39.8 billion, as financial outflows for U.S.-owned assets abroad increased and financial inflows for foreign-owned assets in the United States decreased.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/10October/1003ITA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-10-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/international/bp_web/</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-10-05</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Services: Cross-Border Trade in 2002 and Sales Through Affiliates in 2001</Title>
        <Author>Maria Borga, Michael Mann</Author>
        <Description>In 2002, U.S. exports of private services increased 1 percent to $279.5 billion, and U.S. imports of services increased 2 percent to $205.2 billion. The modest recovery reflected pickups in economic activity in the United States and in many foreign countries. In 2001, the most recent year for which data are available, sales of private services abroad by foreign affiliates of U.S. companies increased 5 percent to $432.1 billion, and sales of private services in the United States by U.S. affiliates of foreign companies increased 7 percent to $366.9 billion. Growth slowed from 2000 because of the slow worldwide economic growth in 2001 and the end of the exceptionally high levels of cross-border mergers and acquisitions.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/10October/1003intlserv.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international services</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-10-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/international/1001serv/intlserv.htm#description</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-11-01</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Advance Estimates for the Third Quarter of 2003</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>The pace of U.S. production accelerated in the third quarter of 2003. Real GDP increased 7.2 percent after increasing 3.3 percent in the second quarter. The acceleration reflected an improved trade balance and strong consumer spending. Inflation was moderate: The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.9 percent after increasing 0.4 percent, partly reflecting an upturn in energy prices.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/11November/1103BSA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-11-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/11November/1103bsa.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-11-02</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Chained-Dollar Indexes: Issues, Tips on Their Use, and Upcoming Changes</Title>
        <Author>J. Steven Landefeld, Brent R. Moulton, Cindy M. Vojtech</Author>
        <Description>This article discusses the advantages of using chain-weighted indexes and the challenges of using chained dollars. It outlines BEA's plans to address these issues as part of the 2003 comprehensive revision of the NIPAs, and it provides suggestions for using chained dollars so that biases and errors are minimized in forecasting and in other applications in which the components of GDP are aggregated.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/11November/1103%20Chain-dollar.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-11-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-11-03</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Business Investment by Industry in the U.S. Economy for 1997</Title>
        <Author>Douglas S. Meade, Stanislaw J. Rzeznik, Darlene C. Robinson-Smith</Author>
        <Description>The capital flow table shows the destination of the new capital investment in equipment, software, and structures by the industries that purchased or leased these capital goods and services. It provides a detailed view of the investment of 180 commodities for 123 industries on the basis of the North American Industry Classification System. This table supplements the use table from the 1997 benchmark input-output accounts that shows private fixed investment by detailed commodity for each industry.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/11November/1103%20Investment.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Industry, Industry Accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-11-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/bea/newsrel/flow1997.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-11-04</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Reconciliation of the U.S.-Canadian Current Account, 2001 and 2002</Title>
        <Author>Patricia Abaroa, Edward Dozier, Denis Caron</Author>
        <Description>Each year, the U.S. and Canadian current-account estimates are reconciled using a common set of definitions, methodologies, and data sources. On the reconciled basis, the U.S. current-account deficits with Canada are larger than those shown in the U.S.-published accounts. For 2001, the deficit on the reconciled basis is $39.1 billion, and the U.S.-published deficit is $28.1 billion. For 2002, the reconciled deficit is $38.0 billion, and the published deficit is $30.4 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/11November/1103%20CurrentAcct.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-11-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-11-05</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Multinational Companies: Operations in 2001</Title>
        <Author>Raymond J. Mataloni, Jr.</Author>
        <Description>The worldwide value added in production by U.S. multinational companies decreased 7.7 percent in 2001, reflecting decreases in production by both U.S. parent companies and their majority-owned foreign affiliates. Despite the decreases in production, these companies continued to increase their capital spending. By industry, the decrease in production was most pronounced in the manufacture of durable goods, such as motor vehicles and computers, due to weak demand. By area, the decreases were most pronounced in Africa and in Latin America and Other Western Hemisphere.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/11November/1103multinational.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-11-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-11-06</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>State Personal Income: Second Quarter 2003</Title>
        <Author>G. Andrew Bernat, Jr.</Author>
        <Description>Personal income for the Nation grew 0.8 percent in the second quarter of 2003, about the same as in the first quarter. Reflecting the above-average growth in natural resources and mining, 4 of the 10 fastest growing states were in the Plains region, and 2 of the 10 were in the Rocky Mountain region. In 21 states and the District of Columbia, net earnings, the largest of the three major components of personal income, grew faster in the second quarter than in the first quarter.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/11November/1103%20SPI.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-11-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-12-01</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>Initial Results of the 2003 Comprehensive Revision of the National Income and Product Accounts</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>On December 10, 2003, BEA released revised estimates for 1929-2002 from the 12th comprehensive revision of the accounts. According to the revised estimates, between 1992 and 2002, real GDP grew at an average annual rate of 3.2 percent, the same rate as previously estimated. Consumer spending and residential investment increased slightly more than previously estimated, but exports and government spending increased slightly less. The pace of the current expansion was revised down slightly: From the third quarter of 2001 to the second quarter of 2003, the growth rate of real GDP was revised from 2.7 percent to 2.6 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/12December/1203NIPARev03.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-12-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/bea/newsrel/2003cr.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-12-02</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>The Effects of Revisions to Seasonal Factors on Revisions to Seasonally Adjusted Estimates: The Case of Exports and Imports</Title>
        <Author>Dennis J. Fixler, Bruce T. Grimm, Anne E. Lee</Author>
        <Description>Seasonal adjustments are used to remove the effects of recurring patterns of economic activity, such as increased consumer spending during the holidays. This study examines the importance of revisions to the underlying seasonally unadjusted data for the exports and imports of goods and services in BEA's international transactions accounts, relative to the effects of revisions to seasonal factors.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/12December/1203Effects.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-12-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-83-12-03</ID>
        <Volume>83</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2003</Year>
        <Title>The Reliability of the State Personal Income Estimates</Title>
        <Author>Robert L. Brown, Bruce T. Grimm, Marian B. Sacks</Author>
        <Description>A recent study by BEA found that the quarterly estimates of state personal income are reliable indicators of whether a state's economy is expanding or contracting, whether a state's economy is accelerating or decelerating, and whether a state's economy is growing at rates that are above, below, or near long-term trend. As a result, the estimates present a consistent picture of a state's economic growth.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2003/12December/1203ReliableSPI.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2003-12-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
