<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-01-01</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 2.1 percent in the third quarter of 1996, down from a 4.7- percent increase in the second quarter. Real GNP increased 1.6 percent in the third quarter. Corporate profits increased $5.4 billion in the third quarter, about half as much as in the second; profits of domestic non-financial corporations increased less than in the second quarter, and profits of domestic financial corporations turned down.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0197bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-01-08</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-01-02</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Third Quarter 1996</Title>
        <Author>Lori A. Trawinski</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit increased $7.8 billion, to $48.0 billion, in the third quarter of 1996. The deficits on goods and services and on investment income both increased; net unilateral transfers changed little. In the capital account, net recorded capital inflows were $69.3 billion in the third quarter, $19.5 billion higher than in the second.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/bpa/1997/0197bop.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Balance of payments</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-01-08</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-01-03</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1997/0197niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-01-08</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-02-01</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Intrafirm Trade in Goods</Title>
        <Author>William J. Zeile</Author>
        <Description>Transactions between affiliated units of multinational companies (MNC's) account for a major share of U.S. international trade in goods—for more than one-third of U.S. exports in 1994 and for more than two-fifths of U.S. imports. For both exports and imports, this intrafirm trade has mainly consisted of shipments from parents to their affiliates rather than shipments to parents from their affiliates. By industry, most of the intrafirm trade of U.S. MNC's has been between U.S. manufacturing parents and their foreign manufacturing affiliates, and most of the intrafirm trade of foreign MNC's has been between U.S. wholesale trade affiliates and their foreign parent groups.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/bpa/1997/0297iid.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-02-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-02-02</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 4.7 percent in the fourth quarter of 1996 after increasing 2.1 percent in the third quarter; the acceleration was more than accounted for by a sharp turnaround in exports and by a pickup in personal consumption expenditures. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 2.5 percent after increasing 1.9 percent; the step-up was more than accounted for by an upturn in energy prices.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0297bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-02-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-02-03</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Personal Income by State and Region, Third Quarter 1996</Title>
        <Author>Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>Personal income in the Nation increased 1.4 percent in the third quarter of 1996. In all States, the increase in personal income exceeded the 0.4-percent increase in the prices paid by U.S. consumers. Nevada had the largest increase in personal income, 2.3 percent, and Alaska had the smallest increase, 0.6 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/regional/perinc/1997/0297rem.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-02-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-03-01</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Daniel Larkins, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 3.9 percent in the fourth quarter of 1996 after increasing 2.1 percent in the third quarter; the acceleration was more than accounted for by a sharp turnaround in exports and by a pickup in personal consumption expenditures. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 2.5 percent after increasing 1.9 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0397bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-03-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-03-02</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Federal Budget Estimates, Fiscal Year 1998</Title>
        <Author>Raymen G. LaBella, Michael W. Webb</Author>
        <Description>In BEA's annual &quot;translation&quot; of the administration's budget, which puts the budget's receipts and outlays on a basis that is consistent with the framework of the NIPA's, the Federal deficit on a NIPA basis decreases to $136.6 billion in fiscal year 1998 from $142.0 billion in fiscal year 1997. Before translation, the budget shows the deficit decreasing to $120.6 billion from $125.6 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1997/0397gd.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Government transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-03-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-04-01</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Real Gross Product of U.S. Companies' Majority Owned Foreign Affiliates in Manufacturing</Title>
        <Author>Raymond J. Mataloni, Jr.</Author>
        <Description>BEA has developed experimental estimates of real gross product of majority owned foreign affiliates in manufacturing for 1982–94. These estimates are more useful than the current-dollar estimates for comparisons over time or across countries because they exclude changes in value that arise from movements in prices or exchange rates. As might be expected, removing the effects of changes in prices and exchange rates produces a gross product series that is generally both slower growing and less volatile than the current-dollar series. The new, experimental estimates are largely based on a newly developed procedure that uses</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/usinvest/1997/0497iid.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-04-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-04-02</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Daniel Larkins, Ann M. Groszkiewicz</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 3.8 percent in the fourth quarter of 1996, up from a 2.1- percent increase in the third quarter. Real GNP increased 4.2 percent in the fourth quarter. Corporate profits decreased $7.1 billion, in contrast to a $5.4 billion increase in the third quarter; profits of domestic financial corporations decreased much more in the fourth quarter than in the third, and profits of domestic non-financial corporations decreased after increasing. In the fourth quarter, the Federal Government current deficit decreased $14.9 billion, to $105.9 billion, the smallest deficit since the third quarter of 1989; the State and local government surplus increased $1.7 billion, to $90.9 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0497bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-04-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-04-03</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Fourth Quarter and Year 1996</Title>
        <Author>Christopher L. Bach</Author>
        <Description>In the fourth quarter of 1996, the U.S. current-account deficit decreased $6.5 billion, to $41.4 billion; the deficits on goods and services and on investment income decreased, while net unilateral transfers increased. In the capital account, net recorded inflows were $68.0 billion in the fourth quarter, $1.7 billion lower than in the third. For the year 1996, the current-account deficit increased $16.9 billion, to $165.1 billion; the deficits on goods and services and on investment income increased, and net unilateral transfers increased. In the capital account, net recorded inflows were $218.2 billion in 1996, $101.6 billion higher than in 1995.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/bpa/1997/0497bop.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Balance of payments</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-04-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-04-04</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1997/0497niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-04-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-05-01</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Completion of the Comprehensive Revision of the National Income and Product Accounts, 1929–96</Title>
        <Author>Robert P. Parker</Author>
        <Description>The release of the following estimates marks the completion of the most recent comprehensive revision of the NIPA's: Revised NIPA estimates for 1929–58, revised estimates of reproducible tangible wealth for 1929–95, and revised and newly available NIPA estimates of selected series for 1959–96 that reflect the work undertaken to complete the 1929–58 NIPA and 1929–95 wealth estimates. For 1929–58, the growth rate of real GDP is revised up from 2.8 percent to 3.4 percent, and the average annual increase of GDP prices is revised down from 2.4 percent to 1.9 percent; these revisions largely reflect the introduction of BEA's new chain-type measures. Beginning with 1959, the revisions to the annual changes of both real GDP and GDP prices are small; national income and personal income are revised up to reflect the revisions to the wealth estimates.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0597nip5.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-05-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-05-02</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>BEA's Chain Indexes, Time Series, and Measures of Long Term Economic Growth</Title>
        <Author>J. Steven Landefeld, Robert P. Parker</Author>
        <Description>BEA's new chain-type annual-weighted indexes of real output and prices provide significantly more accurate measures for analyses of long-term economic growth and business cycles. The indexes are more accurate, but they are also computationally more difficult to use than the old fixed-weighted &quot;constant dollar&quot; estimates. When the chain-type indexes were introduced last year, BEA provided chained (1992) dollar estimates and contributions to growth tables. However, there are conceptual and empirical problems with using chained dollar estimates for analysis of periods that are far from the base period. Therefore, with the release of chain-type estimates beginning with 1929, BEA is providing additional sets of estimates to assist in long-term analyses. BEA is also considering further work to improve its chain-type measures for recent periods.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0597od.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-05-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-05-03</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Improved Estimates of Fixed Reproducible Tangible Wealth, 1929–95</Title>
        <Author>Arnold J. Katz, Shelby W. Herman</Author>
        <Description>BEA's estimates of fixed reproducible tangible wealth have been revised to incorporate the results of last year's comprehensive revision of the NIPA's. The major improvement is the introduction of a methodology that uses empirical evidence on the prices of used equipment and structures in resale markets, which has shown that depreciation for most types of assets approximates a geometric pattern. For equipment, the new methodology results in a more rapid pattern of depreciation in the early years of an asset's life and a slower pattern in the later years; for structures, the new methodology results in a slower pattern of depreciation throughout the life of an asset. In addition, the estimates of real net stocks and depreciation are improved by the introduction of chain-type indexes that allow for the eVects of changes in relative prices and in the composition of output over time.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1997/0597niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Fixed capital stock</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-05-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-05-04</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff.</Author>
        <Description>In the first quarter of 1997, real GDP increased 5.6 percent—its biggest increase in more than 9 years—up from a 3.8-percent increase in the fourth quarter of 1996. The first-quarter strength was evident in personal consumption expenditures, inventory investment, producers' durable equipment, and exports. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 2.2 percent in the first quarter after increasing 2.6 percent in the fourth.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0597bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-05-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-05-05</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Personal Income and Per Capita Personal Income by State and Region</Title>
        <Author>Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>Personal income in the Nation increased 1.3 percent in the fourth quarter of 1996 after increasing 1.4 percent in the third quarter. In the fourth quarter, Nevada had the largest increase in personal income, 2.3 percent. In the year 1996, per capita personal income in the Nation increased 4.5 percent, while prices paid by U.S. consumers increased only 2.2 percent. In all States except Alaska and Hawaii, the increase in per capita personal income exceeded the increase in U.S. prices.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/regional/perinc/1997/0597rem.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-05-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-05-06</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Summary National Income and Product Series, 1929–96</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0597nip1.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-05-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-05-07</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Revised and Newly Available NIPA Estimates, 1991–95</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0597nip2.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-05-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-06-01</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Comprehensive Revision of Gross State Product by Industry, 1977–94</Title>
        <Author>Howard L. Friedenberg, Richard M. Beemiller</Author>
        <Description>BEA's estimates of gross state product (GSP) have been updated to incorporate the results of the most recent comprehensive revision of the NIPA's, including the use of chain-type measures of real output and the new treatment of government investment. In addition, the revised estimates incorporate the results of the most recent comprehensive revision of State personal income and several major improvements in the State-level source data and estimating procedures for GSP. For 1977–94, the five States with the fastest growth in real GSP were Nevada, Arizona, New Hampshire, Florida, and Georgia.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/regional/gsp/1997/0697rea.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Gross state product</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-06-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-06-02</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Jennifer A. Bennett, Daniel Larkins, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>In the first quarter of 1997, real GDP increased 5.8 percent—its biggest increase in more than 9 years—up from a 3.8-percent increase in the fourth quarter of 1996; the price index for gross domestic purchases increased 2.2 percent after increasing 2.6 percent. Corporate profits jumped $46.7 billion, in contrast to a $7.2 billion decrease in the fourth quarter. In the first quarter, the Federal Government current deficit decreased $24.1 billion, to $81.8 billion, the smallest deficit since the third quarter of 1981; the State and local government current surplus increased $4.4 billion, to $95.3 billion. Revised estimates of the rate of return—measured as ratio of property income to the stock of net reproducible tangible assets—for domestic non-financial corporations for 1959–95 are 1-to-2 percentage points lower than the previously published estimates.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0697bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-06-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-06-03</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: New Investment in 1996 and Affiliate Operations in 1995</Title>
        <Author>Mahnaz Fahim-Nader, William J. Zeile</Author>
        <Description>In 1996, outlays by foreign investors for acquiring or establishing businesses in the United States surged to a record $80.5 billion. The industry composition of outlays in 1996 tended to be more heavily weighted with service-type industries—including finance, insurance, communication, and a number of business services—than in past years, and the outlays in manufacturing tended to be more concentrated in industries that are information related or that use advanced technologies. In 1995, most measures of the operations of U.S. affiliates of foreign companies increased. However, the rates of increase slowed in some key measures; for example, the gross product of non bank U.S. affiliates increased 4 percent in 1995 after increasing 10 percent in 1994.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/fdinvest/1997/0697iid.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-06-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-06-04</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Subject Guide: Volume 77 (1997), Numbers 1–6</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/Beawide/1997/0697sg.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-06-12</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-07-01</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>The Measurement of Depreciation in the U.S. National Income and Product Accounts</Title>
        <Author>Barbara M. Fraumeni</Author>
        <Description>As part of the recent comprehensive revision of the NIPA's, BEA introduced an improved methodology for calculating depreciation and capital stocks. This article by Barbara Fraumeni, a professor at Northeastern University and a consultant for BEA, reviews the empirical literature that supports BEA's use of geometric patterns of depreciation in the revised estimates.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1997/0797fr.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-07-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-07-02</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Revised Estimates for 1974–96</Title>
        <Author>Christopher L. Bach</Author>
        <Description>This year's annual revision of the balance of payments accounts incorporates significant improvements in the investment income, capital, and services accounts. In the investment income accounts, the estimates of income receipts incorporate the results of the first benchmark survey of the stock of U.S. portfolio investment abroad in over 50 years. In the capital accounts, estimates of the international flows of U.S. currency appear for the first time. In the services accounts, preliminary results from the first annual surveys of financial services are incorporated. On the revised basis, the U.S. current-account deficit is $148.2 billion in 1996, compared with $165.1 billion on the previously published basis; the revision is more than accounted for by an upward revision to exports of goods, services, and income.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/bpa/1997/0797bp.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Balance of payments</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-07-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-07-03</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 5.9 percent in the first quarter of 1997. Real GNP increased 5.0 percent, and real GNP on a command basis increased 5.6 percent. Corporate profits jumped $42.4 billion, as profits of both financial and non-financial domestic corporations rebounded strongly from fourth-quarter decreases.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0797bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-07-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-07-04</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>The International Investment Position of the United States in 1996</Title>
        <Author>Russell B. Scholl</Author>
        <Description>The net international investment position of the United States became more negative in 1996: On a current-cost basis, it increased $182.8 billion, to -$870.5 billion; and on a market-value basis, it increased $193.8 billion, to -$831.3 billion. The change in the position in 1996 was attributable to large net capital inflows to the United States. However, for the direct investment component of the position, U.S. assets abroad continued to exceed foreign assets in the United States.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/bpa/1997/0797iip.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Investment position</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-07-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-07-05</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Direct Investment Positions for 1996: Country and Industry Detail</Title>
        <Author>Sylvia E. Bargas</Author>
        <Description>In 1996, the U.S. direct investment position abroad valued at historical cost increased 11 percent, reflecting large capital outflows that were mainly in the form of reinvested earnings. Nearly half of the increase in the position was accounted for by Europe, mostly by the United Kingdom. The foreign direct investment position in the United States valued at historical cost increased 12 percent, reflecting large capital inflows that were mainly in the form of equity capital—both from capital contributions to existing U.S. affiliates and from acquisitions of U.S. business by foreigners. Most of the increase in the position was accounted for by Europe.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/fdinvest/1997/0797dip.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Investment position</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-07-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-07-06</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, First Quarter 1997</Title>
        <Author>Christopher L. Bach</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit increased $4.1 billion, to $41.0 billion, in the first quarter of 1997. A shift to a deficit on investment income and an increase in the deficit on goods and services were partly offset by a decrease in net unilateral transfers. In the capital account, net recorded inflows were $59.1 billion in the first quarter, $19.0 billion higher than in the fourth.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/bpa/1997/0797bop.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Balance of payments</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-07-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-07-07</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1997/0797niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-07-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-08-01</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Annual Revision of the National Income and Product Accounts: Annual Estimates, 1993–96, and Quarterly Estimates, 1993:I-1997:I</Title>
        <Author>Robert P. Parker, Eugene P. Seskin</Author>
        <Description>The revised NIPA estimates show about the same picture of overall U.S. economic activity as was shown by the previously published estimates. Over the period covered by the revisions, the growth rate of real GDP was revised up 0.1 percentage point to 2.8 percent, and the increase in the price of gross domestic purchases was unrevised at 2.3 percent. In addition to the incorporation of regular source data, this annual revision incorporates several methodological changes, including the changes in methodology that were introduced in the recent annual revision of the balance of payments accounts and a change in the weights used to compute real output and prices for recent periods.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0897niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-08-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-08-02</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 2.2 percent in the second quarter of 1997 after increasing 4.9 percent in the first quarter; the deceleration was more than accounted for by slowdowns in personal consumption expenditures and inventory investment. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 0.6 percent in the second quarter after increasing 1.9 percent in the first; the deceleration largely reflected a sharp downturn in energy prices.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0897bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-08-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-08-03</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Personal Income by State and Region, First Quarter 1997</Title>
        <Author>Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>Personal income in the Nation increased 1.7 percent in the first quarter of 1997—the largest quarterly increase since the first quarter of 1995—after increasing 1.4 percent in the fourth quarter of 1996. In all States except Delaware, the increases in personal income exceeded the 0.6-percent increase in the prices paid by U.S. consumers. Utah, Nevada, Oregon, and Kentucky had the fastest growth in personal income in the first quarter.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/regional/perinc/1997/0897rem.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-08-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-08-04</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>National Income and Product Accounts Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0897nipa.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-08-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-08-05</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Summary National Income and Product Series, 1929–96</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0897nip2.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-08-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-09-01</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Comprehensive Revision of Local Area Personal Income, 1969–95</Title>
        <Author>Wallace K. Bailey</Author>
        <Description>BEA has released revised annual estimates of personal income for local areas— counties, metropolitan areas, and BEA economic areas—for 1969–94 and new estimates for 1995. The estimates incorporate the results of the recent comprehensive revisions of the national income and product accounts and of State personal income. In general, the revisions were small; for 1994, only 3 metropolitan areas had upward revisions of more than 5.0 percent, and only 3 areas had downward revisions of more than 3.0 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/regional/perinc/1997/0997rem.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-09-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-09-02</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Daniel Larkins, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff, Ann M. Groszkiewicz</Author>
        <Description>In the second quarter of 1997, real GDP increased 3.6 percent, down from a 4.9-percent increase in the first quarter; the price index for gross domestic purchases increased 0.8 percent, down from a 1.9-percent increase. Corporate profits increased $14.9 billion in the second quarter after increasing $31.8 billion in the first. In the second quarter, the Federal Government current deficit decreased $20.7 billion, to $34.8 billion, the smallest deficit since the fourth quarter of 1979; the State and local government current surplus increased $0.6 billion, to $105.3 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0997bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-09-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-09-03</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Customer Satisfaction Report</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/beawide/1997/0997cust.pdf</URL>
        <Category>General</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-09-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-09-04</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Updated Summary NIPA Methodologies</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0997niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-09-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-09-05</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Annual NIPA Revision: Newly Available Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/0997nipa.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-09-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-09-06</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Fixed Reproducible Tangible Wealth in the United States: Revised Estimates for 1993–95 and Summary Estimates for 1925–96</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1997/0997wlth.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Fixed capital stock</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-09-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-09-07</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: Detail for Historical Cost Position and Related Capital and Income Flows, 1996</Title>
        <Author>Gregory G. Fouch, Peter J. Fox, Nancy F. Halvorson, Tracy K. Leigh, Beverly E. Palmer, Linden L. Webber, Karen E.Poffel, Sylvia E. Bargas</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/fdinvest/1997/0997fdi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-09-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-09-08</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Direct Investment Abroad: Detail for Historical Cost Position and Related Capital and Income Flows, 1996</Title>
        <Author>Mark W. New, Laura A. Downey, Javier J. Hodge, Marie K. Laddomada, Sherry Lee, Leila C. Morrison, Gary M. Solamon, Dwayne Torney, Wendy P. Warcholik, Smith W. Allnutt</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/usinvest/1997/0997usd.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-09-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-10-01</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>State Personal Income, Revised Estimates for 1958–96</Title>
        <Author>Wallace K. Bailey</Author>
        <Description>This release of revised annual estimates of State personal income for 1958–96 completes the comprehensive revision to the estimates for those years. The revised estimates incorporate the final results of the most recent comprehensive revision of the national income and product accounts (NIPA's), the 1997 annual revision of the NIPA's, the county-level estimation of the adjustment for residence, and newly available State-level source data. The revisions to the estimates of State personal income before 1993 were generally small and reflected the revisions to the national estimates. By 1996, the revisions were more widespread and more substantial, reflecting both the revisions to the national estimates and the incorporation of newly available State-level source data for all the components of personal income.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/regional/perinc/1997/1097rm.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Personal, Personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-10-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-10-02</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 3.3 percent in the second quarter of 1997 after increasing 4.9 percent in the first quarter, and the price index for gross domestic purchases increased 0.8 percent after increasing 1.9 percent. Corporate profits increased $15.5 billion in the second quarter, largely reflecting an increase in the profits of domestic non-financial corporations.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/1097bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-10-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-10-03</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Multinational Companies: Operations in 1995</Title>
        <Author>Raymond J. Mataloni, Jr.</Author>
        <Description>Growth in the overall operations of U.S. multinational companies (MNC's) continued in 1995: Worldwide gross product of U.S. parent companies and their majority-owned foreign affiliates combined increased 6 percent, employment increased 1 percent, and capital expenditures increased 8 percent. Gross product and employment grew faster for the foreign affiliates than for the parents, while capital expenditures grew at the same rate for both. However, worldwide production and productive resources of MNC's remained concentrated in the United States: U.S. parents accounted for three-fourths of the gross product, employment, and capital expenditures of U.S. MNC's, while their affiliates accounted for one-fourth.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/usinvest/1997/1097mnc.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-10-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-10-04</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Second Quarter 1997</Title>
        <Author>Douglas B. Weinberg</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit decreased to $39.0 billion in the second quarter of 1997 from $40.0 billion in the first quarter. A decrease in the deficit on goods and services more than offset increases in the deficit on investment income and in net unilateral transfers. In the capital account, net recorded capital inflows were $56.2 billion in the second quarter, down from $54.3 billion in the first.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/bpa/1997/1097bop.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Balance of payments</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-10-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-10-05</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Sales and Purchases of Private Services: U.S. Cross-Border Transactions in 1996 and Sales by Affiliates in 1995</Title>
        <Author>Michael A. Mann, Daniel J. Atherton, Laura L. Brokenbaugh, Sylvia E. Bargas</Author>
        <Description>The United States recorded another surplus on cross-border transactions in private services in 1996, when the balance rose to a record $78.1 billion and offset a significant portion of the $191.2 billion U.S. deficit on trade in goods. By country, Japan was the leading destination for exports of services, and the United Kingdom was the leading origin for imports of services. In 1995, the latest year for which data are available on services delivered through majority-owned affiliates, sales of services abroad by the foreign affiliates of U.S. companies increased 20 percent to $205.8 billion, while sales of services in the United States by the U.S. affiliates of foreign companies increased 8 percent to $167.6 billion. By country, affiliates of U.S. companies in the United Kingdom had the largest share of services sold abroad by foreign affiliates, and affiliates with ultimate beneficial owners in the United Kingdom had the largest share of services sold in the United States by U.S. affiliates.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/intserv/1997/1097srv.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, International services</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-10-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-10-06</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Annual NIPA Revision: Newly Available Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/1097nipa.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-10-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-10-07</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, 1992:IV–1997:II</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1997/1097niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-10-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-11-01</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Gross Product by Industry, 1947–96</Title>
        <Author>Sherlene K.S. Lum, Robert E. Yuskavage</Author>
        <Description>The estimates of gross product by industry have been revised to incorporate the final results of the most recent comprehensive revision of the NIPA's, the results of this year's annual revision of the NIPA's, and newly available source data. In addition, new estimates are available for 1996, which represents a speedup in the availability of estimates for the most recent complete year. For 1992–96, one-half of the 2.6-percent growth rate in real GDP was accounted for by durable goods manufacturing (0.8 percent) and by services (0.5 percent). For the total economy, the labor share of gross product declined slightly, from 58½ percent in 1992 to 58 percent in 1996, as a decline in the labor share for manufacturing was nearly offset by an increase in the labor share for non-manufacturing.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/inputout/1997/1197gpo.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Gross product by industry</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-11-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-11-02</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Benchmark Input Output Accounts for the U.S. Economy, 1992: Make, Use, and Supplementary Tables</Title>
        <Author>Ann M. Lawson</Author>
        <Description>The 1992 benchmark input-output (I-O) accounts present a detailed picture of how industries interact to provide input to and take output from each other. The 1992 I-O accounts incorporate a number of changes, including the major improvements that were introduced in the most recent comprehensive revision of the NIPA's, that enable the accounts to more accurately reflect the evolving U.S. economy and that increase the accuracy and reliability of the estimates. In addition, the publication of these accounts within a year of the release of the final results of the 1992 economic censuses represents a speedup in their availability as outlined in BEA's Strategic Plan.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/inputout/1997/1197io.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Input-output accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-11-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-11-03</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Note on Alternative Measures of Gross Product by Industry</Title>
        <Author>Robert P. Parker</Author>
        <Description>The preceding two articles present two independently derived measures of current-dollar gross product by industry for 1992. This note briefly describes the differences between the two measures and the efforts that are underway to better integrate them.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/inputout/1997/1197od.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Gross product by industry</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-11-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-11-04</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 3.5 percent in the third quarter of 1997, about the same pace as in the second quarter; personal consumption expenditures, which increased 5.7 percent, contributed the most to the third-quarter increase in GDP. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.2 percent after increasing 0.8 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/1197bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-11-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-11-05</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Motor Vehicles, Model Year 1997</Title>
        <Author>Ralph W. Morris</Author>
        <Description>In model year 1997, sales of motor vehicles totaled 15.4 million units; sales have ranged between 15.2 million and 15.5 million for the past 4 years. In 1997, sales of new trucks increased 4.6 percent to a record 7.1 million units, but sales of new cars decreased 4.6 percent to 8.3 million units.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1997/1197mv.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Motor vehicles</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-11-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-11-06</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Comparison of BEA Estimates of Personal Income and IRS Estimates of Adjusted Gross Income: New Estimates for 1995 and Revised Estimates for 1947–94</Title>
        <Author>Thae S. Park</Author>
        <Description>BEA's measure of personal income and the IRS measure of adjusted gross income—two widely used measures of household income—are reconciled through a series of adjustments for definitional and statistical differences between the two measures. This reconciliation incorporates the final results of the most recent comprehensive revision of the NIPA's, the results of this year's annual revision of the NIPA's, and information from the Statistics of Income Bulletin.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1997/1197gd.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Government transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-11-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-11-07</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Reconciliation of the U.S.­Canadian Current Account, 1995 and 1996</Title>
        <Author>Anthony J. DiLullo, Lucie Laliberté</Author>
        <Description>For both 1995 and 1996, the reconciliation of the U.S.-Canadian current account results in a U.S. current-account deficit with Canada that is somewhat larger than the deficit in the U.S.-published accounts. The annual reconciliation shows how the current-account estimates would appear if both countries used the same definitions, methodologies, and data sources.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/bpa/1997/1197bop.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Balance of payments</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-11-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-11-08</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Personal Income by State and Region, Second Quarter 1997</Title>
        <Author>Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>Personal income in the Nation increased 1.2 percent in the second quarter of 1997 after increasing 1.9 percent in the first quarter. In all States, the increases in personal income exceeded the 0.2-percent increase in prices paid by U.S. consumers. Arkansas, Arizona, Nevada, and Delaware had the fastest growth in personal income in the second quarter.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/regional/perinc/1997/1197rea.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-11-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-12-01</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Preview of Revised NIPA Estimates for 1992 From the 1992 IO Accounts</Title>
        <Author>Leon W Taub, Robert P. Parker</Author>
        <Description>The recently released 1992 benchmark input-output accounts provide &quot;preliminary revised&quot; estimates that preview the impact of incorporating these accounts in the next comprehensive revision of the NIPA's; however, these estimates do not reflect the definitional and other statistical changes that will also be incorporated as part of that revision. The revised estimate of GDP for 1992 is $10.5 billion lower, or 0.2 percent lower, than the presently published estimate; the revised estimate of gross domestic income is $11.5 billion lower, or 0.2 percent lower, than the presently published estimate.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/1297niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-12-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-12-02</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Benchmark Input Output Accounts for the U.S. Economy, 1992: Requirements Tables</Title>
        <Author>Ann M. Lawson</Author>
        <Description>The 1992 benchmark input-output (I-O) accounts present a detailed picture of how industries provide input to and take output from each other. The requirements tables in these accounts can be used to quantify the inputs that are needed by an industry to produce a dollar of output, and they can be used to trace the effects of a dollar change in the final use of a specified commodity. For example, the requirements tables can be used to analyze the relative effects of a change in the composition of personal consumption expenditures that results from a change in consumer tastes.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/inputout/1997/1297io.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Input-output accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-12-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-12-03</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Daniel Larkins, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff, Jennifer A. Bennett</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 3.3 percent in the third quarter of 1997, the same pace as in the second quarter; consumer spending and business fixed investment contributed the most to the third-quarter increase in GDP. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.3 percent after increasing 0.8 percent. Corporate profits increased $21.1 billion in the third quarter after increasing $15.5 billion in the second. In the third quarter, the Federal Government current deficit decreased $24.3 billion, to $12.5 billion, the smallest deficit since the second quarter of 1979; the State and local government current surplus increased $6.4 billion, to $111.3 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1997/1297bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-12-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-12-04</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Federal Personal Income Tax Liabilities and Payments, 1992–95</Title>
        <Author>Thae S. Park</Author>
        <Description>According to newly available BEA estimates of Federal personal income tax liabilities, liabilities exceeded payments by $5.5 billion in 1995, whereas payments exceeded liabilities by $4.9 billion in 1994. These estimates incorporate the results of the annual NIPA revision released in July and newly available tax return data from the Internal Revenue Service.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1997/1297gd.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Government transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-12-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-12-05</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>Subject Guide, Volume 77</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/beawide/1997/1297sg.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-12-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-77-12-06</ID>
        <Volume>77</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>1997</Year>
        <Title>1998 Release Dates for BEA Estimates</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/beawide/1997/1297rd.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>1997-12-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
