<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-01-01</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Final Estimates for the Third Quarter of 2003</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>The acceleration in the pace of U.S. production in the third quarter of 2003 was confirmed by the final estimates. Real GDP increased 8.2 percent, the same rate shown by the preliminary estimates released in November. The acceleration reflected strong consumer spending and an improved trade balance. Inflation was moderate: The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.8 percent after increasing 0.4 percent, partly reflecting an upturn in energy prices.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/01January/0104bsf.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-01-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/01January/0104bsa.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-01-02</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Preview of Selected Tables From the 2003 Comprehensive Revision of the National Income and Product Accounts</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>This preview presents revised annual estimates for 1999-2002 and quarterly estimates for the first quarter of 2000 through the third quarter of 2003 for selected tables from the national income and product accounts.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/01January/0104SelectedNIPATbls.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-01-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/national/nipaweb/index.asp</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-01-03</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>An Ownership-Based Framework of the U.S. Current Account, 1992-2002</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey H. Lowe</Author>
        <Description>BEA's ownership-based current account has been updated. This report presents revised estimates for 1992-2000, new detailed estimates for 2001, and new summary estimates for 2002. This framework supplements BEA's international transactions accounts by highlighting the participation of multinational companies in the international markets for goods and services through both cross-border trade and sales by local affiliates.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/01January/0104Ownership_based.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-01-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-01-04</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Third Quarter 2003</Title>
        <Author>Elena L. Nguyen, Renee M. Sauers</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit decreased $4.4 billion, to $135.0 billion, in the third quarter. The decrease was attributable to a decrease in the deficit on goods, to increases in the surpluses on services and on income, and to a decrease in net outflows for unilateral current transfers. In the financial account, net recorded inflows decreased $26.7 billion, to $123.3 billion. Both financial inflows for foreign-owned assets in the United States and financial outflows for U.S.-owned assets abroad decreased substantially, but the decrease in inflows was larger than that in outflows.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/01January/0104ITAWeb.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-01-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/international/bp_web/</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-01-05</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Errata: Selected Data for Majority-Owned Nonbank Foreign Affiliates by Country of Affiliate</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>The data now include the final estimates of research and development expenditures of majority-owned nonbank foreign affiliates, U.S. exports of goods shipped to these affiliates, and U.S. imports of goods shipped by these affiliates for 2000. These estimates replace the estimates published in the article on the operations of U.S. multinational companies in the November 2003 Survey.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/01January/0104ErrataWeb.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-01-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-02-01</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Advance Estimates for the Fourth Quarter of 2003 and for the Year 2003</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>The pace of U.S. production moderated in the fourth quarter, as real GDP increased 4.0 percent after increasing 8.2 percent in the third quarter. The deceleration mainly reflected slower growth of consumer spending. Inflation slowed: The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.0 percent after increasing 1.8 percent, mainly reflecting a downturn in energy prices. In 2003, real GDP increased 3.1 percent after increasing 2.2 percent in 2002. The step-up mainly reflected upturns in nonresidential investment and exports; consumer spending slowed, and inventory investment turned down.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/02February/0204bsf6.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-02-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/02February/0204bsa.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-02-02</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Improved Estimates of the National Income and Product Accounts for 1929-2002: Results of the Comprehensive Revision</Title>
        <Author>Eugene P. Seskin, Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>The Bureau of Economic Analysis has released the results of the 12th comprehensive revision of the NIPAs. The revised estimates incorporate a number of major improvements that are designed to better measure the ever-changing U.S. economy. The revisions to GDP and the other major NIPA aggregates and their components are described, and the revisions that are attributable to the various improvements are identified. The picture of the economy shown by the revised estimates is similar to that shown by the previously published estimates: Real GDP grew at about the same rate as in the previously published estimates, and the most recent recession and the current expansion are slightly milder than previously estimated.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/02February/0204NIPAarticle.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-02-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/02February/0204NIPA.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-02-03</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>National Income and Product Accounts Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>An extensive set of tables presents estimates from the 2003 comprehensive NIPA revision. It includes annual estimates for 2000-2003 and quarterly estimates for the second quarter of 2000 through the fourth quarter of 2003 in the selected set of tables that are published monthly. It also includes annual estimates for 1999-2002 and monthly estimates for 1999-2003 that are a part of the extended set of NIPA tables.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/02February/0204NIPA_Tables.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-02-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/national/nipaweb</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-02-04</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>GDP and Other Major NIPA Series, 1929-2003</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>A set of tables presents the historical series from the 2003 comprehensive NIPA revision. Specifically, it presents estimates of GDP and its components in current dollars, in chained dollars, and in chain-type quantity and price indexes, and estimates of national income and personal income.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/02February/0204GDP%26Other.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-02-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/national/nipaweb</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-02-05</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Annual Customer Satisfaction Survey Report for Fiscal Year 2003</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>BEA's survey received feedback in three critical areas: Customer satisfaction, product use, and Web site features.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/02February/0204Customers.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-02-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-02-06</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, 1997:I-2003:III</Title>
        <Author>Jennifer Ribarsky</Author>
        <Description>The quarterly and monthly estimates of inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios have been revised to reflect the results of the 2003 comprehensive NIPA revision.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/02February/0204ISR.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-02-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-02-07</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>State Personal Income: Third Quarter 2003</Title>
        <Author>G. Andrew Bernat, Jr.</Author>
        <Description>Personal income for the Nation grew 1.1 percent, up from 1.0 percent in the second quarter. Reflecting continued strong growth in farm earnings, 3 of the 10 fastest growing states are in the Plains region, and 2 are in the Rocky Mountain region. Earnings grew in every industry for the first time in more than 2 years and in all the states and the District of Columbia.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/02February/0204SPI.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-02-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-03-01</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Preliminary Estimates for the Fourth Quarter of 2003</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>The pace of U.S. production slowed in the fourth quarter, as real GDP increased 4.1 percent after increasing 8.2 percent in the third quarter. The deceleration mainly reflected slower growth of consumer spending and a deterioration in the trade balance. Inflation slowed: The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.1 percent after increasing 1.8 percent, mainly reflecting a downturn in energy prices.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/03March/0304bsf.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-03-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/03March/0304bsp.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-03-02</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Federal Budget Estimates for Fiscal Year 2005</Title>
        <Author>Benyam Tsehaye, Michelle Robinson</Author>
        <Description>Each year, BEA prepares an adjusted presentation of the administration's budget estimates from the Budget of the United States Government that is consistent with the framework of the NIPAs. The fiscal year relationships derived from the budget estimates are then used in preparing BEA's quarterly estimates of Federal Government current receipts and expenditures. This year, the NIPA framework reflects the results of the 2003 comprehensive NIPA revision. For fiscal year 2005, the net Federal Government saving on the NIPA basis is estimated at -$338.0 billion, compared with the deficit of $363.6 billion in the administration's budget.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/03March/0304FedBudget.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Federal budget estimates</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-03-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-03-03</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Comprehensive NIPA Revision: Newly Available Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>The Bureau of Economic Analysis continues to release the results of the 12th comprehensive revision of the NIPAs.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/03March/0304NewNIPAs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-03-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>
            Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/national/nipaweb</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-03-04</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Errata: Sources of the Revisions to Selected Income Components</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>In the article on the comprehensive NIPA revision in the 2004 February Survey, the definitional and statistical sources of the revisions to taxes on production and imports and to business current transfer payments for several years were misreported.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/03March/0304Errata.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-03-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/03March/erratata.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-03-05</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Preview of the Comprehensive Revision of the Annual Industry Accounts: Integrating the Annual Input-Output Accounts and the Gross-Domestic-Product-by-Industry Accounts</Title>
        <Author>Brian C. Moyer, Mark A. Planting, Mahnaz Fahim-Nader, Sherlene K. S. Lum</Author>
        <Description>The upcoming comprehensive revision of the annual industry accounts features the integration of these two sets of accounts. For the first time, these two sets of accounts will be released concurrently and will present fully consistent measures of gross output, intermediate inputs, and value added by industry. In addition, the annual input-output accounts for 1998-2002 will be a consistent time series.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/03March/0304IndustryAcctsV3.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Industry, Industry Accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-03-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-03-06</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>A Note on Patterns of Production and Employment by U.S. Multinational Companies</Title>
        <Author>Raymond J. Mataloni Jr.</Author>
        <Description>This note examines recent patterns and trends in the worldwide operations of U.S. multinationals with a focus on production and employment. For example, U.S. parents have consistently accounted for about three-fourths, and their majority-owned foreign affiliates for about one-fourth, of the total gross product, capital expenditures, and employment of U.S. multinationals. The note concludes with a discussion of several data and analytical considerations.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/03March/0304MNC.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-03-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-04-01</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Final Estimates for the Fourth Quarter of 2003</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Michelle Robinson</Author>
        <Description>The slower pace of U.S. production in the fourth quarter was confirmed by the final estimates of the national income and product accounts. Real GDP increased 4.1 percent after increasing 8.2 percent in the third quarter. The deceleration mainly reflected slower growth in consumer spending and a deterioration in the trade balance. Inflation slowed: The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.3 percent after increasing 1.8 percent, mainly reflecting a downturn in energy prices. Corporate profits increased $81.4 billion (7.2 percent at a quarterly rate) after increasing $101.4 billion. Net Federal Government saving, the difference between current receipts and current expenditures, increased $77.0 billion, to -$417.9 billion, and net state and local government saving increased $26.8 billion, to $39.9 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/04April/0404BSF.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-04-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/04April/BSF1.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-04-02</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Comparison of BEA Estimates of Personal Income and IRS Estimates of Adjusted Gross Income: New Estimates for 2001 and Revised Estimates for 1959-2000</Title>
        <Author>Mark A. Ledbetter</Author>
        <Description>Personal income and adjusted gross income--two widely used measures of household income--are reconciled through a series of adjustments for definitional and statistical differences between the two measures. The estimates reflect the incorporation of the results of the recent comprehensive NIPA revision and of new and updated estimates of adjusted gross income.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/04April/0404PI%26AG.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-04-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/04April/PI%26AGI.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-04-03</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, 1997:I-2003:IV</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>The quarterly and monthly estimates of inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios have been updated. In addition, the estimates of sales and ratios for the retail trade industries that were published in the February Survey have been corrected; as a result, the estimates of the sales and ratios for total manufacturing and trade industries have also been corrected.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/04April/0404ISR.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-04-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/04April/ISR.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-04-04</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Comprehensive NIPA Revision: Newly Available Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>The Bureau of Economic Analysis continues to release the results of the 12th comprehensive revision of the NIPAs.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/04April/0404NewNIPAs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-04-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/national/nipaweb</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-04-05</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Fourth Quarter 2003</Title>
        <Author>Christopher L. Bach</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit decreased $7.8 billion, to $127.5 billion. The decrease was accounted for by a large increase in the surplus on income and by an increase on the surplus on services. These increases were partly offset by increases in the deficit on goods and in net outflows for unilateral current transfers. In the financial account, net recorded financial inflows increased $75.0 billion, to $180.9 billion, as financial inflows for foreign-owned assets in the United States increased more than financial outflows for U.S.-owned assets abroad.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/04April/0404ITA4thQtr.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-04-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/international/bp_web</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-04-06</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, 2003</Title>
        <Author>Christopher L. Bach</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit increased $61.0 billion, to $541.8 billion. The increase was mainly accounted for by an increase in the deficit on goods, but an increase in net outflows for unilateral current transfers and a decrease in the surplus on services also contributed. In the financial account, net recorded financial inflows increased $51.0 billion, to $579.0 billion, as financial inflows for foreign-owned assets in the United States increased more than financial outflows for U.S.-owned assets abroad.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/04April/0404ITA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-04-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/international/bp_web</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-05-01</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Advance Estimates for the First Quarter of 2004</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 4.2 percent in the first quarter of 2004 after increasing 4.1 percent in the fourth quarter of 2003. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 3.2 percent after increasing 1.3 percent; the acceleration was partly accounted for by energy prices. Real disposable personal income increased 4.3 percent after increasing 0.5 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/05May/0504bsf.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-05-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/05May/bstables.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-05-02</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Fixed Assets and Consumer Durable Goods: Preliminary Estimates for 2002 and Revised Estimates for 1925-2001</Title>
        <Author>Paul R. Lally</Author>
        <Description>As part of the comprehensive NIPA revision, the Bureau of Economic Analysis (BEA) has released updated estimates of fixed assets and consumer durable goods. These estimates incorporate several key statistical improvements, including longer service lives for aircraft, estimates of depreciation for light trucks, and an updated depreciation schedule for autos. They also incorporate changes in classification, including government structures by function and four new components of the types of nonresidential structures. For 1925-2002, the net stock at current cost grew at an average annual rate of 6.3 percent, and the net stock at real cost grew 2.9 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/05May/0504FAD.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Fixed assets and consumer durable goods</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-05-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/national/nipaweb</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-05-03</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Comprehensive NIPA Revision: Newly Available Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>BEA continues to release the results of the 12th comprehensive revision of the NIPAs.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/05May/0504NewNIPAs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-05-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/national/nipaweb</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-05-04</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Comprehensive Revision of State Personal Income: Preliminary Estimates for 2003 and Revised Estimates for 1969-2002</Title>
        <Author>Robert L. Brown, G. Andrew Bernat, Jr., Adrienne T. Pilot</Author>
        <Description>On April 27, 2004, BEA released the results of the latest comprehensive revision of quarterly and annual estimates of state personal income that incorporates the results of the recent comprehensive NIPA revision, new data and newly available data, and improved methods for preparing the state estimates. The timing of this release represents an acceleration in the availability of state estimates that are consistent with the comprehensive NIPA revision. The revisions to state personal income are generally small and mixed in direction.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/05May/0504RevSPI.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-05-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/iTable/index_regional.cfm</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-06-01</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Preliminary Estimates for the First Quarter of 2004</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Alyssa E. Holdren</Author>
        <Description>U.S. economic activity picked up somewhat in the first quarter. Real GDP increased 4.4 percent after increasing 4.1 percent in the fourth quarter of 2003; the pickup was mainly accounted for by increases in government and consumer spending. Inflation also picked up: The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 3.3 percent after increasing 1.3 percent; the pickup partly reflected an upturn in energy prices. Corporate profits increased $14.2 billion (1.2 percent at a quarterly rate) after increasing $81.4 billion. Net Federal Government saving, the difference between current receipts and current expenditures, was -$441.1 billion, decreasing $28.9 billion from -$412.2 billion, and net state and local government saving was $23.5 billion, decreasing $16.4 billion from $39.9 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/06June/0604bsp.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-06-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/06June/bsptables.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-06-02</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Federal Personal Income Tax Liabilities and Payments: Preliminary Estimates for 2001 and Revised Estimates for 1959-2000</Title>
        <Author>Mark A. Ledbetter, Vanessa D. Lee</Author>
        <Description>BEA's estimates of liabilities and payments have been updated to incorporate the results of the comprehensive NIPA revision and the revised and newly available tax return data from the Internal Revenue Service. The differences between liabilities and payments are usually small, but in 2001, personal taxes on a liabilities basis were $142.2 billion less than taxes on a payments basis. This unusually large difference reflected the slowdown in the economy, a reduction in the volatile capital gains realizations, and the first year of the tax reductions enacted in the Economic Growth and Tax Relief Act of 2001.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/06June/0604tax.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Federal personal income tax liabilities and payments</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-06-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-06-03</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Improved Annual Industry Accounts for 1998-2003: Integrated Annual Input-Output Accounts and Gross-Domestic-Product-by-Industry Accounts</Title>
        <Author>Brian C. Moyer, Mark A. Planting, Paul V. Kern, Abigail M. Kish</Author>
        <Description>On June 17, 2004, BEA released the results of the comprehensive revision of the annual industry accounts. The integrated annual input-output (I-O) accounts and the GDP-by-industry accounts now present consistent measures of gross output, intermediate inputs, and value added by industry that are more accurate. The timing of this release marks a significant acceleration in the availability of the annual I-O accounts. In 1998-2003, the services-producing industries were the largest contributors to real GDP growth. In 2001, the slow growth in GDP reflected the positive contribution of these industries that offset the negative contribution of the goods-producing industries, and in 2002-2003, the continuing positive contributions of these industries led the economic recovery.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/06June/0604GDP_Industry.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Industry, Industry Accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-06-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/iTable/index_industry_gdpIndy.cfm</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-06-04</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Comprehensive NIPA Revision: Newly Available Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>BEA continues to release the results of the 12th comprehensive revision of the NIPAs.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/06June/0604NewNIPAs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-06-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/national/nipaweb/</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-06-05</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: New Investment in 2003</Title>
        <Author>Thomas W. Anderson</Author>
        <Description>Outlays by foreign direct investors to acquire or to establish U.S. businesses rose 11 percent, the first increase since 2000, to $60.3 billion in 2003. Outlays were boosted by substantial spending in financial industries. Despite the increase, the level of outlays was still far less than the levels in 1998-2001, when outlays for new investment ranged from $147.1 billion to $335.6 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/06June/0604FDIUS.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-06-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-06-06</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Comprehensive Revision of Local Area Personal Income: Preliminary Estimates for 2002 and Revised Estimates for 1969-2001</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey L. Newman</Author>
        <Description>On May 25, 2004, BEA released the results of the latest comprehensive revision of the annual estimates of personal income for counties, metropolitan areas, and BEA economic areas. These estimates incorporate the results of the comprehensive NIPA revision and the comprehensive revision of state personal income. The timing of this release represents an acceleration in the availability of estimates that are consistent with the comprehensive NIPA revision. The comprehensive revision to the estimates of personal income for metropolitan areas are generally small and mixed in direction.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/06June/0604LAPI.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Local area personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-06-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/iTable/index_regional.cfm</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-06-07</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Subject Guide for the January-June 2004 Issues</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/06June/0604SbjGuide.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-06-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-07-01</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Final Estimates for the First Quarter of 2004</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 3.9 percent (at an annual rate) in the first quarter of 2004 after increasing 4.1 percent in the fourth quarter of 2003; most of the major components of GDP contributed to the first-quarter increase. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 3.5 percent after increasing 1.3 percent; the pickup partly reflected an upturn in energy prices. Corporate profits increased $20.9 billion (1.7 percent at a quarterly rate) after increasing $81.4 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/07July/0704bsf.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Director's Message</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-07-22</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/07July/bsftables.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-07-02</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, First Quarter 2004</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>The quarterly and monthly estimates have been updated. The estimates of inventories for manufacturing by stage of fabrication have also been updated.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/07July/0704ISR.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Taking Account - Economic Studies</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-07-22</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-07-03</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Comprehensive NIPA Revision: Newly Available Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>BEA continues to release the results of the 12th comprehensive revision of the NIPAs.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/07July/0704NewNIPAs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-07-22</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/national/nipaweb/</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-07-04</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Multinational Companies: Operations in 2002</Title>
        <Author>Raymond J. Mataloni Jr.</Author>
        <Description>The worldwide value added in production by U.S. multinational companies decreased 0.4 percent in 2002, reflecting a decrease in production by U.S. parents that was offset by an increase in production by their majority-owned foreign affiliates. By industry, the decrease was accounted for by substantial decreases in production by U.S. parents in telecommunications services and in communication equipment manufacturing. By area, production decreased in the United States, Canada, Latin America and Other Western Hemisphere, and the Middle East, and it increased in Europe, Asia and Pacific, and Africa.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/07July/0704mnc.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-07-22</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-07-05</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>The International Investment Position of the United States at Yearend 2003</Title>
        <Author>Patricia E. Abaroa</Author>
        <Description>The net international investment position at current cost was -$2,430.7 billion; in 2002, it was -$2,233.0 billion. The -$197.7 billion increase mainly resulted from large net foreign purchases of U.S. securities that increased the value of foreign-owned assets; the increase in the value of these assets was partly offset by a substantial increase in the value of U.S.-owned assets abroad, especially U.S.-held stocks, as a result of the appreciation of most foreign currencies against the U.S. dollar.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/07July/0704_IIP.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international investment position</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-07-22</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-07-06</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Direct Investment Positions for 2003: Country and Industry Detail</Title>
        <Author>Maria Borga, Daniel R. Yorgason</Author>
        <Description>The historical-cost position of U.S. direct investment abroad (USDIA) increased significantly more than the position of foreign direct investment in the United States (FDIUS). The USDIA position increased 12 percent, slightly less than the 13-percent average annual growth in 1994-2002; the 12-percent growth mainly resulted from an increase in reinvested earnings and currency-translation adjustments. The FDIUS position increased 3 percent, substantially less than the 14-percent average annual growth in 1994-2002, reflecting the continued weakness in merger and acquisition activity. The 3-percent increase mainly resulted from equity capital inflows.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/07July/0704dip.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Direct investment positions: Country and industry detail</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-07-22</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-07-07</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Annual Revision of the U.S. International Accounts, 1989-2003</Title>
        <Author>Christopher L. Bach</Author>
        <Description>Each year, estimates in the U.S. international transactions accounts and in the U.S. international investment position accounts are revised to incorporate statistical and methodological changes and updated, regularly available source data. This year, major changes include a new methodology to prepare the estimates of U.S. Government income payments, the incorporation of the U.S. Treasury Department's new annual surveys of securities liabilities for June 2003 and June 2004, and another definitional change in the measurement of insurance services.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/07July/0704_ITArev.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-07-22</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-07-08</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>How BEA Aligns and Augments Source Data From the U.S. Treasury Department for Inclusion in the International Transactions Accounts</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>The estimates of financial-account flows in the international transactions accounts are based on data from the Treasury Department that are adjusted. The adjustments to align and augment the data are presented in this report.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/07July/0704_TreasuryITA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-07-22</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-07-09</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, First Quarter 2004</Title>
        <Author>Renee M. Sauers</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit increased $17.9 billion, to $144.9 billion. The increase was mostly accounted for by an increase in the deficit on trade in goods, but a decrease in the surplus on income and an increase in net outflows for unilateral current transfers also contributed. In the financial account, net recorded financial inflows decreased $10.4 billion, to $158.3 billion; both outflows for U.S.-owned assets abroad and inflows for foreign-owned assets in the United States increased substantially, but outflows increased more than inflows.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/07July/0704_ITAQ.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-07-22</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/international/bp_web</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-07-10</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>State Personal Income: First Quarter of 2004</Title>
        <Author>G. Andrew Bernat, Jr.</Author>
        <Description>Personal income for the Nation grew 1.4 percent, the same as in the fourth quarter of 2003, and up from 1.2 percent in the third quarter. Personal income growth accelerated in 21 states and in the District of Columbia. Earnings in all industries except natural resources and mining grew. Decreases in farm earnings contributed to decreases in personal income in three states in the Plains region and in one state in the Rocky Mountain region.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/07July/0704_SPI.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-07-22</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-08-01</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Advance Estimates for the Second Quarter of 2004</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>Economic growth slowed in the second quarter. Real GDP increased 3.0 percent after increasing 4.5 percent in the first quarter of 2004; the slowdown primarily reflected a deceleration in consumer spending. Prices increased about as much as in first quarter, as the price index for gross domestic purchases increased 3.5 percent after increasing 3.4 percent. Real disposable personal income increased 2.9 percent after increasing 3.2 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/08August/0804BSA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-08-20</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/08August/bsatables.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-08-02</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Annual Revision of the National Income and Product Accounts: Annual Estimates, 2001-2003, and Quarterly Estimates, 2001:I-2004:I</Title>
        <Author>Eugene P. Seskin, Shelly Smith</Author>
        <Description>The picture of the economy shown by the revised estimates is similar to that shown by the previously published estimates. From 2000 to 2003, real GDP grew at an average annual rate of 1.9 percent, the same as in the previously published estimates, and from the fourth quarter of 2000 to the first quarter of 2004, the average annual rate of real GDP growth is unchanged at 2.5 percent. The 2001 downturn and the subsequent recovery are slightly milder than previously estimated.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/08August/0804niparev.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-08-20</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-08-03</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>National Income and Product Accounts Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>A set of tables presents the estimates from the annual NIPA revision. It presents revised estimates for 2001-2003, for the first quarter of 2001 through the first quarter of 2004, and for January 2001 to May 2004 and advance estimates for the second quarter of 2004 and for June 2004.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/08August/0804NIPA_TABLES.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-08-20</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/national/nipaweb/</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-08-04</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>GDP and Other Major NIPA Series, 1929-2004:II</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>A set of tables presents the historical series from the annual NIPA revision. Specifically, it presents estimates of GDP and its components in current dollars, in chained dollars, and in chain-type quantity and price indexes and estimates of national income and personal income.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/08August/0804GDP%26Other.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-08-20</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/national/nipaweb/</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-08-05</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Operations of U.S. Affiliates of Foreign Companies: Preliminary Results From the 2002 Benchmark Survey</Title>
        <Author>William J. Zeile</Author>
        <Description>Reflecting developments in the U.S. economy, production and employment by majority-owned nonbank U.S. affiliates moved in divergent directions in 2002. Their current-dollar value added increased 9 percent, but their employment decreased 3 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/08August/0804FDIUS.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-08-20</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-09-01</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Preliminary Estimates for the Second Quarter of 2004</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Alyssa E. Holdren</Author>
        <Description>Economic growth slowed in the second quarter. Real GDP increased 2.8 percent after increasing 4.5 percent in the first quarter; the slowdown primarily reflected a deceleration in consumer spending. Prices increased about as much as in first quarter, as the price index for gross domestic purchases increased 3.5 percent after increasing 3.4 percent. Real disposable personal income increased 2.5 percent after increasing 2.4 percent. Corporate profits increased $1.6 billion (0.1 percent at a quarterly rate) after increasing $36.5 billion. Net Federal Government saving was -$383.0 billion, increasing $8.0 billion from -$391.0 billion, and net state and local government saving was $16.5 billion, increasing $4.7 billion from $11.8 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/09September/BSP.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-09-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/09September/bsatables.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-09-02</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Alternative Measures of Personal Saving</Title>
        <Author>Marshall B. Reinsdorf</Author>
        <Description>In the early 1980s, the NIPA measure of personal saving averaged 10.4 percent, but in 2003, it was 1.4 percent. As a result of this continuing decline, economists and policymakers are asking questions, for example, about the adequacy of saving for retirement and for funding U.S. investment requirements and about the sustainability of the current levels of consumer spending. In order to answer these questions on the saving behavior of persons and households, four alternative measures of personal saving are examined. In addition, the role of the accumulation of wealth in the financial resources of households and expanded measures of saving, such as net private saving, that could be used to fund capital investment are examined.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/09September/PersonalSavingWEB.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-09-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-09-03</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Annual NIPA Revision: Newly Available Table</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>BEA continues to release the results from the annual NIPA revision that presented revised estimates for 2001-2003.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/09September/0904NewNIPAs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-09-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/national/nipaweb/</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-09-04</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Fixed Assets and Consumer Durable Goods for 1993-2003</Title>
        <Author>Paul R. Lally</Author>
        <Description>The revised estimates for 1993-2002 and the preliminary estimates for 2003 incorporate the results of the annual NIPA revision. These estimates incorporated several improvements, including the conversion to the North American Industry Classification System, the use of the 1997 capital flow table, and the use of an updated depreciation schedule for consumer autos. In 1987-2003, the net stock at current cost grew at an average annual rate of 4.9 percent, and the net stock at real cost grew 2.6 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/09September/Fixed_Assets.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Fixed assets and consumer durable goods</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-09-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/national/nipaweb/</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-09-05</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Travel and Tourism Satellite Accounts for 1998-2003</Title>
        <Author>Peter D. Kuhbach, Mark A. Planting, Erich H. Strassner</Author>
        <Description>These improved, updated accounts reflect the recent comprehensive revision of the annual industry accounts and of the national income and product accounts. According to the updated estimates, the trends in tourism activity reflect the economic expansion in 1998-2000, the slowdown in 2001 and the events of September 11th, and the economic recovery in 2002-2003.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/09September/0904_TTSAs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Industry, Industry Accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-09-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-09-06</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: Detail for Historical-Cost Position and Related Capital and Income Flows, 2003</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey H. Lowe</Author>
        <Description>Detailed estimates of the direct investment position and international transactions by industry and by country are presented in this report. These estimates show the composition of investment by foreign companies in the United States.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/09September/0904_FDIUS.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-09-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-09-07</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Direct Investment Abroad: Detail for Historical-Cost Position and Related Capital and Income Flows, 2003</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey H. Lowe</Author>
        <Description>Detailed estimates of the direct investment position and international transactions of U.S. multinational companies by industry and by country are presented in this report. These estimates show the composition of investment abroad by U.S. companies.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/09September/0904_USDIA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-09-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/09September/usdia.zip</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-09-08</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Schedule of BEA News Releases in 2005</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/09September/8409_NewsReleaseWbe.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-09-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-10-01</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Final Estimates for the Second Quarter of 2004</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>Economic growth slowed in the second quarter. Real GDP increased 3.3 percent after increasing 4.5 percent in the first quarter; the slowdown primarily reflected a deceleration in consumer spending. Prices increased about as much as in first quarter; the price index for gross domestic purchases increased 3.5 percent after increasing 3.4 percent. Corporate profits increased $8.3 billion (0.7 percent at a quarterly rate) after increasing $36.5 billion (3.2 percent). The slowdown mainly reflected a downturn in the profits of financial corporations.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/10October/1004_BSF.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-10-20</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/10October/1004_BStables.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-10-02</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Estimates of Real Government Consumption Expenditures and Gross Investment by Function for 1959-2003</Title>
        <Author>Bruce E. Baker, Pamela A. Kelly, Brooks B. Robinson</Author>
        <Description>The inaugural estimates of real government spending by function include estimates for total government, for the Federal Government, and for state and local governments, and they are consistent with the NIPA estimates of government spending. The new estimates show that total government spending grew at an average annual rate of 2.3 percent in 1959-2003. Spending for income security grew the fastest, and spending for national defense grew the slowest.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/10October/1004rgi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-10-20</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-10-03</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Newly Available NIPA Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>BEA continues to release the results from the 2003 comprehensive revision and the 2004 annual NIPA revision.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/10October/1004_NewNIPAs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-10-20</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/national/nipaweb/</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-10-04</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, 2000:IV-2004:II</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>The estimates have been revised to incorporate the results of the 2004 annual NIPA revision.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/10October/1004ISR.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-10-20</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-10-05</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Services: Cross-Border Trade in 2003 and Sales Through Affiliates in 2002</Title>
        <Author>Maria Borga, Michael Mann</Author>
        <Description>In 2003, U.S. exports of private services increased 5 percent to $294.1 billion, and U.S. imports increased 8 percent to $228.2 billion, resulting in a surplus in trade in services for the United States. In 2002, sales of services abroad by foreign affiliates of U.S. companies decreased 5 percent to $401.1 billion mainly because of a decline in sales by affiliates in utilities. Sales by U.S. affiliates of foreign companies in the United States increased 5 percent to $386.7 billion, reflecting U.S. economic growth.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/10October/1004_IntlServ.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international services</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-10-20</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/international/intlserv.htm</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-10-06</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions: Second Quarter of 2004</Title>
        <Author>Renee M. Sauers</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit increased $19.0 billion to $166.2 billion. The increase was accounted for by a $12.8 billion increase in the deficit on goods, reflecting a surge in imports, and by a $9.5 billion decrease in the surplus on income. In contrast, the surplus on services increased $1.1 billion, and net outflows for unilateral current transfers decreased $2.2 billion. In the financial account, net recorded financial inflows increased $8.2 billion. Both outflows for U.S.-owned assets abroad and inflows for foreign-owned assets in the United States decreased substantially, but outflows decreased more than inflows.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/10October/1004_ITA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-10-20</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/international/bp_web/</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-10-07</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>State Personal Income: Second Quarter of 2004 and Revised Estimates for 2001-2004:I</Title>
        <Author>David G. Lenze</Author>
        <Description>BEA accelerated the release of the quarterly estimates of personal income so that these estimates were released at the same time as the annual estimates. Personal income for the Nation grew 1.5 percent, up from 1.2 percent in the first quarter of 2004. Personal income growth accelerated in 33 states. Earnings grew in all industries except two. Increases in farm earnings contributed to increases in personal income in Arkansas and North Dakota. In 2003, personal income for the Nation grew 3.2 percent, according to the revised estimates. Per capita personal income for the Nation was $31,459.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/10October/1004SPI.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-10-20</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-11-01</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Advance Estimates for the Third Quarter of 2004</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>Economic growth stepped up in the third quarter. Real GDP increased 3.7 percent after increasing 3.3 percent in the second quarter; the step-up mainly reflected an acceleration in consumer spending and a slowdown in imports. Inflation moderated; the price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.8 percent after increasing 3.5 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/11November/1104BSA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-11-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/11November/1104_BStables.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-11-02</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Annual NIPA Revision: Newly Available NIPA Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>BEA continues to release the results from the 2004 annual NIPA revision.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/11November/1104NewNIPAs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-11-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/national/nipaweb/</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-11-03</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Comparison of BEA Estimates of Personal Income and IRS Estimates of Adjusted Gross Income: New Estimates for 2002 and Revised Estimates for 2001</Title>
        <Author>Mark A. Ledbetter</Author>
        <Description>The estimates of personal income and of adjusted gross income--two widely used measures of household income--are reconciled in order to account for the statistical and definitional differences between the two measures. The revised estimates incorporate the results of the 2004 annual NIPA revision.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/11November/1104piagi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-11-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-11-04</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Updated Summary NIPA Methodologies</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>The updated summary of the principal source data and methods that are used to prepare the real and current-dollar estimates of GDP now reflects the improvements in methodology that were introduced as part of the 2003 comprehensive NIPA revision and the 2004 annual NIPA revision.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/11November/1104NIPAMeth.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-11-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-11-05</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Gross Domestic Product by Industry for 1987-2000: New Estimates on the North American Industry Classification System</Title>
        <Author>Robert E. Yuskavage, Yvon H. Pho</Author>
        <Description>These new estimates for 1987-97 and the previously published estimates for 1998-2000 provide the first economywide, NAICS-based view of historical industry performance and contributions to GDP growth. These estimates offer new insights into the recent changes in the structure of the economy because NAICS more clearly identifies high-tech industries, such as information and communications technology, and provides more details for the services sector.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/11November/1104GDP_by_Indy.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Industry, Industry Accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-11-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Interactive Data</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/iTable/index_industry_gdpIndy.cfm</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-11-06</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Reconciliation of the United States-Canadian Current Account for 2002 and 2003</Title>
        <Author>Patricia Abaroa, Edward Dozier, Denis Caron</Author>
        <Description>Each year, the bilateral current-account estimates of the United States are reconciled with those of Canada because of the extensive economic links between these two countries. The reconciled estimates are intended to assist analysts who use the estimates of both countries and to show how the current-account estimates would appear if both countries used common definitions, methodologies, and data sources.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/11November/1104US-Canadian.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-11-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-11-07</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>2004 Redefinition of the BEA Economic Areas</Title>
        <Author>Kenneth P. Johnson, John R. Kort</Author>
        <Description>BEA has updated the definitions of the BEA economic areas to reflect changes in economic growth and population in the regions and to incorporate the revised standards for metropolitan statistical areas and the newly recognized micropolitan areas. The number of economic areas has increased from 172 to 179.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/11November/1104Econ-Areas.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, BEA economic areas</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-11-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/newsrelarchive/2004/rea1104.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-12-01</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Preliminary Estimates for the Third Quarter of 2004</Title>
        <Author>Brian C. Moyer, Shelly Smith, David F. Sullivan, Christopher Falcone</Author>
        <Description>Economic growth picked up in the third quarter. Real GDP increased 3.9 percent after increasing 3.3 percent in the second quarter; the pickup mainly reflected a step-up in consumer spending. Inflation slowed; the price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.8 percent after increasing 3.5 percent. Real disposable personal income slowed, increasing 2.0 percent after increasing 2.8 percent. Corporate profits decreased $27.6 billion (2.4 percent at a quarterly rate) after increasing $8.3 billion. Net Federal Government saving was -$376.2 billion, increasing $3.8 billion from -$380.0 billion. Net state and local government saving was $8.5 billion, decreasing $9.8 billion from $18.3 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/12December/BSP_1204_Article_B%26W.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-12-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-12-02</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>The NIPAs and the System of National Accounts</Title>
        <Author>Charles Ian Mead, Karin E. Moses, Brent R. Moulton</Author>
        <Description>In recent years, BEA has been improving the consistency of the NIPAs with the internationally accepted set of guidelines for the compilation of national accounts in the System of National Accounts 1993 (SNA) as part of BEA's mission to produce accurate, relevant, and timely statistics, to respond to customers' needs, and to meet the challenges of measuring a changing economy. The organization and major features of the NIPAs are compared with those of the SNA.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/12December/1204_NIPA%26SNA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-12-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-12-03</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Federal Personal Income Tax Liabilities and Payments for 1959-2002</Title>
        <Author>Mark A. Ledbetter</Author>
        <Description>BEA's estimates of liabilities and payments have been updated to incorporate the results of the 2004 annual NIPA revision and the revised and newly available tax return data for 2002 from the Internal Revenue Service. For 2002, personal taxes on a liabilities basis were $31.0 billion less than taxes on a payments basis. This large difference partly reflected the retroactive provisions of the Job Creation and Worker Assistance Act of 2002 that resulted in a reduction in liabilities and in an overpayment of taxes.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/12December/PI%26Tax.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Federal personal income tax liabilities and payments</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-12-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-12-04</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Subject Guide for 2004</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>This guide lists the major articles that were published in 2004 in the Survey. It includes the articles on the comprehensive revisions of the NIPAs, of the industry accounts, and of the regional accounts.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/12December/1204SbjGuide.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-12-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-84-12-05</ID>
        <Volume>84</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2004</Year>
        <Title>Schedule of BEA News Releases in 2005</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2004/12December/8412_NewsRelease_B%26W.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>2004-12-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
