<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-01-01</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>GDP: One of the Great Inventions of the 20th Century</Title>
        <Author>J. Steven Landefeld</Author>
        <Description>At a press conference on December 7, 1999, the Department of Commerce announced that it had selected "the development of the national income and product accounts as its achievement of the century." The speakers at the conference and other government policy officials and leading academic economists took the opportunity to affirm the importance of the national accounts to economic analysis and policy making. The accounts were born out of a pressing need for economic information during the Great Depression and World War II, and they have been continually updated and improved so that they provide an accurate, timely, and relevant picture of U.S. economic activity.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/BEAWIDE/2000/0100od.pdf</URL>
        <Category>General</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-01-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-01-02</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Zvi Griliches and His Contributions to Economic Measurement</Title>
        <Author>Barbara M. Fraumeni</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0100zvi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>General</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-01-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-01-03</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Annual Input-Output Accounts of the U.S. Economy, 1996</Title>
        <Author>Sumiye O. Okubo, Ann M. Lawson, Mark A. Planting</Author>
        <Description>The 1996 input-output (I-O) accounts present a detailed picture of how industries interact to provide input to, and take output from, each other. The estimates update the 1992 benchmark I-O accounts and are consistent definitionally and statistically with the recently revised NIPA estimates. The publication of the annual 1996 I-O accounts marks the return of the annual I-O program as part of BEA's industry accounts.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/Inputout/2000/0100io.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Input-output accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-01-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-01-04</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Ralph W. Morris, Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 5.7 percent in the third quarter of 1999, according to the NIPA &quot;final&quot; estimate; the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate issued last month had shown a 5.5-percent increase. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.7 percent, the same as the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate. The &quot;revised&quot; estimate of corporate profits showed an increase of $3.7 billion (or 0.4 percent at a quarterly rate) in the third quarter; the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate had shown an increase of $8.2 billion (or 0.9 percent).</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0100bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-01-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-01-05</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Third Quarter 1999</Title>
        <Author>Harlan W. King</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit increased $9.0 billion, to $89.9 billion, in the third quarter of 1999. Most of the increase was accounted for by an increase in the deficit on goods, as imports increased twice as much as exports increased. In the financial account, net recorded inflows decreased $13.9 billion, to $105.7 billion. Inflows for foreign-owned assets in the United States and outflows for U.S.-owned assets abroad both slowed sharply, but the slowdown in inflows, which reflected a sharp dropoff in foreign acquisitions of U.S. companies, exceeded that in outflows.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/BPA/2000/0100it.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-01-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-01-06</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, 1977:I--1999:III</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/2000/0100is.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-01-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-01-07</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Errata: National Income and Product Accounts</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0100err.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-01-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-01-08</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>An Ownership-Based Disaggregation of the U.S. Current Account, 1982--97</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey H. Lowe</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/BPA/2000/0100iid.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-01-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-02-01</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Comparison of BEA Estimates of Personal Income and IRS Estimates of Adjusted Gross Income</Title>
        <Author>Thae S. Park</Author>
        <Description>The BEA estimates of personal income and the IRS estimates of adjusted gross income (AGI)---two widely used measures of household income---are reconciled through a series of adjustments for definitional differences between the two measures. This reconciliation incorporates the results of the recent comprehensive revision of the NIPA's, updates to the AGI estimates, and several improvements to the reconciliation items.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/2000/0200agi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, BEA personal income and IRS adjusted gross income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-02-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-02-02</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Accounting for Subsoil Mineral Resources</Title>
        <Author>The National Research Council - the Panel on Integrated Environmental and Economic Accounting, William D. Nordhaus, Edward C. Kokkenlenberg</Author>
        <Description>[Reprint of chapter 3 of Nature's Numbers: Expanding the National Economic Accounts to Include the Environment] Last summer, a blue-ribbon panel of the National Academy of Sciences' National Research Council completed a congressionally mandated review of BEA's prototype integrated economic and environmental accounts. As part of its promise to inform users of the results of this evaluation, BEA is reprinting chapters from the panel's final report.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/2000/0200srm.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Satellite accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-02-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-02-03</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Industrial Composition of State Earnings in 1958--98</Title>
        <Author>G. Andrew Bernat, Jr., Eric S. Repice</Author>
        <Description>The industrial composition of earnings across States has become more similar over time. This convergence primarily reflects the relatively stronger growth in services than in farming and manufacturing; services-producing industries tend to be more evenly distributed across the Nation than goods-producing industries. In 1998, the States with industrial compositions that were most similar to that of the United States were California, Washington, Arizona, Pennsylvania, and Missouri. The States that were least similar were Wyoming, Alaska, Nevada, Hawaii, and New Mexico.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/REGIONAL/perinc/2000/0200rea.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Industrial composition of State earnings</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-02-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-02-04</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>U.S. economic activity registered another strong increase in the fourth quarter of 1999, while inflation picked up somewhat. Real GDP increased 5.8 percent after increasing 5.7 percent in the third quarter. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 2.3 percent after increasing 1.7 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0200bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-02-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-02-05</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Motor Vehicles, 1999</Title>
        <Author>Ralph W. Morris</Author>
        <Description>Sales of motor vehicles surged to a record 17.4 million units in 1999 from 16.0 million units in 1998. Sales of new trucks again increased strongly, reaching a record 8.7 million units; sales of new cars also increased to 8.7 million units, following 4 consecutive years of declines.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/2000/0200mv.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Motor vehicles</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-02-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-02-06</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>State Personal Income, Third Quarter 1999</Title>
        <Author>Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>Personal income in the Nation increased 1.3 percent in the third quarter of 1999, the same pace as in the second quarter. In the third quarter, the States with the fastest growth in personal income were Nevada, Arizona, and Florida. The States with the slowest growth were North Dakota, South Dakota, and North Carolina.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/REGIONAL/perinc/2000/0200spi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-02-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-02-07</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Comprehensive NIPA Revision: Newly Available Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0200nipa.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-02-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-03-01</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Accounting for Renewable and Environmental Resources</Title>
        <Author>The National Research Council - the Panel on Integrated Environmental and Economic Accounting, William D. Nordhaus, Edward C. Kokkenlenberg</Author>
        <Description>[Reprint of chapter 4 of Nature's Numbers: Expanding the National Economic Accounts to Include the Environment] Last summer, a blue-ribbon panel of the National Academy of Sciences' National Research Council completed a congressionally mandated review of BEA's prototype integrated economic and environmental accounts. As part of its promise to inform users of the results of this evaluation, BEA is reprinting chapters from the panel's final report.\n</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/2000/0300are.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Satellite accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-03-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-03-02</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>An Examination of the Low Rates of Return of Foreign-Owned U.S. Companies</Title>
        <Author>Raymond J. Mataloni, Jr.</Author>
        <Description>In 1988-97, the average rate of return on assets (ROA) of foreign-owned nonfinancial companies, at 5.1 percent, was 2.2 percentage points below that of U.S.-owned companies; over the period, the ROA gap narrowed to about 1 percentage point in 1997. Among several factors that may help explain the lower ROA of foreign-owned companies, age and market share were found to be significant, and industry mix and shifting of profits outside the United States using transfer prices were found to be relatively insignificant. These findings are based on newly developed estimates of the rate of return for foreign-owned U.S. nonfinancial companies that are disaggregated by industry and valued in current-period prices.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/FDINVEST/2000/0300rr.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-03-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-03-03</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Daniel Larkins, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 6.9 percent in the fourth quarter of 1999, according to the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate; the &quot;advance&quot; estimate issued last month had shown a 5.8-percent increase. The upward revision reflected upward revisions to consumer spending, to State and local government spending, to exports of goods, and to private nonfarm inventory investment. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 2.3 percent in the fourth quarter, the same as the previously published increase.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0300bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-03-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-03-04</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Federal Personal Income Tax Liabilities and Payments, 1959-97</Title>
        <Author>Thae S. Park</Author>
        <Description>BEA's estimates of Federal personal income tax liabilities and payments have been revised, beginning with 1959, to incorporate the results of the recent comprehensive revision of the NIPA's and newly available tax return data from the Internal Revenue Service. Since 1992, the differences between liabilities and payments have generally been small; in 1997, payments exceeded liabilities by $2.3 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/2000/0300fpi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Federal personal income tax liabilities and payments</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-03-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-03-05</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Federal Budget Estimates, Fiscal Year 2001</Title>
        <Author>Laura M. Beall, Sean P. Keehan</Author>
        <Description>Each year, BEA prepares a &quot;translation&quot; of the administration's budget that puts the budget's receipts and outlays on a basis that is consistent with the framework of the NIPA's. For fiscal year 2001, the Federal current surplus on the NIPA basis would be $171.1 billion, compared with the surplus of $184.0 billion in the administration's budget. The budget estimate of receipts would exceed the NIPA estimate of current receipts by $2.4 billion, and the NIPA estimate of current expenditures would exceed the budget estimate of outlays by $10.5 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/2000/0300fbe.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Federal budget estimates</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-03-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-03-06</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Errata: Industrial Composition of State Earnings in 1958-98</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/REGIONAL/perinc/2000/0300errata.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Industrial composition of State earnings</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-03-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-04-01</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Improved Estimates of the National Income and Product Accounts for 1929-99: Results of the Comprehensive Revision</Title>
        <Author>Brent R. Moulton</Author>
        <Description>On March 30, 2000, as part of the comprehensive revision of the NIPA's, BEA released revised NIPA estimates for 1929-58 that incorporated the definitional and statistical changes that had been incorporated earlier into the estimates beginning with 1959. In addition, BEA released revised estimates beginning with 1959 that incorporated corrections and a previously announced methodological improvement. The revisions were not sizable enough to affect the average annual growth rate in real GDP for 1929-58 or for 1959-98, but the growth rates for individual years were revised by as much as 0.5 percentage point.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0400nipa.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-04-26</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-04-02</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Fixed Assets and Consumer Durable Goods: Estimates for 1925-98 and New NIPA Table--Changes in Net Stock of Produced Assets</Title>
        <Author>Shelby W. Herman</Author>
        <Description>As part of the comprehensive revision of the NIPA's, BEA has released new estimates of fixed assets and consumer durable goods (formerly &quot;fixed reproducible tangible wealth&quot;) for 1998 and revised estimates for 1925-97. These estimates incorporate a number of definitional and statistical improvements, including the recognition of business and government expenditures for software as fixed investment and a new pattern of depreciation for personal computers. For 1925-98, the net stock at current cost grew at an average annual rate of 6.3 percent, and the net stock at real cost grew at a rate of 2.9 percent. In addition, as part of a long-term effort to integrate the estimates of stocks and flows, BEA has introduced a new NIPA table that shows the changes in the net stock of produced assets.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/2000/0400fxacdg.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Fixed assets and consumer durable goods</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-04-26</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-04-03</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Ralph W. Morris, Daniel Larkins, Mary L. Roy</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 7.3 percent in the fourth quarter of 1999, according to the &quot;final&quot; estimate; the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate released last month had shown a 6.9-percent increase. Corporate profits increased $35.3 billion (4.0 percent at a quarterly rate) in the fourth quarter. The Federal Government current surplus decreased $21.6 billion, to $112.2 billion, and the State and local government current surplus increased $19.9 billion, to $68.8 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0400bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-04-26</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-04-04</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Fourth Quarter and Year 1999</Title>
        <Author>Christopher L. Bach</Author>
        <Description>In the fourth quarter of 1999, the U.S. current-account deficit increased $10.7 billion, to $99.8 billion; the deficit on goods and services, the deficit on income, and net unilateral current transfers all contributed to the increase. In the financial account, net recorded inflows decreased $3.4 billion, to $90.9 billion; financial inflows decreased more than financial outflows. In the year 1999, the U.S. current-account deficit increased $118.3 billion, to $338.9 billion; the increase was mostly accounted for by a sharp rise in the deficit on goods and services. In the financial account, net recorded inflows increased $168.4 billion, to $378.2 billion; financial inflows accelerated much more than financial outflows.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/BPA/2000/0400it.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-04-26</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-04-05</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/2000/0400niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-04-26</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-04-06</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>National Income and Product Accounts</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0400nipatables32.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-04-26</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-04-07</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>National Income and Product Accounts Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0400nipatables36.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-04-26</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-04-08</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>GDP and Other Major NIPA Series, 1929-99</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0400nips.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-04-26</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-05-01</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>U.S. economic activity continued to increase strongly in the first quarter of 2000, while inflation picked up. Real GDP increased 5.4 percent after increasing 7.3 percent in the fourth quarter of 1999. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 3.2 percent after increasing 2.3 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/2000/0500bsa.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-05-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-05-02</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>State and Local Government Fiscal Position in 1999</Title>
        <Author>Janet H. Kmitch, Bruce E. Baker</Author>
        <Description>In 1999, the current surplus of State and local governments--a measure of their net saving--increased $9.3 billion, to $51.0 billion, as current receipts increased more than current expenditures. &quot;Net lending or net borrowing,&quot; an alternative measure of the fiscal position, was introduced in the recent comprehensive revision of the NIPA's. This measure showed that the longer term financing requirements of governments continued to decrease; it was -$13.8 billion in 1999, compared with -$16.8 billion in 1998.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/2000/0500slp.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, State and local government fiscal position</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-05-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-05-03</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Transportation Satellite Accounts for 1996</Title>
        <Author>Bingsong Fang, Xiaoli Han, Sumiye Okubo, Ann M. Lawson</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. transportation satellite accounts (TSA's) have been updated to present estimates for 1996. Like the 1992 TSA's, the 1996 TSA's extend the input-output accounts to provide a more comprehensive picture of the role of transportation in the U.S. economy. The TSA's show that the economy produced and used $673 billion of transportation gross output in 1996, up 23 percent from 1992. The contribution of transportation activities to GDP deceased slightly from 5.0 percent in 1992 to 4.8 percent in 1996.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/Inputout/2000/0500tsa.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Satellite accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-05-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-05-04</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Errata : Fixed Assets and Consumer Durable Goods</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/National/NIPAREL/2000/0500err.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Fixed assets and consumer durable goods</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-05-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-05-05</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>NIPA Component Contributions Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/NIPA/2000/0500cct.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-05-18</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-06-01</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Note on Rates of Return for Domestic Nonfinancial Corporations: Revised Estimates for 1960-98</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/National/NIPA/2000/0600nrr.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-06-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-06-02</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Government Spending by Function: A New Presentation</Title>
        <Author>Karl Galbraith</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/National/NIPAREL/2000/0600gf.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-06-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-06-03</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Improved Estimates of Gross Product by Industry for 1947-98</Title>
        <Author>Sherlene K.S. Lum, Brian C. Moyer, Robert E. Yuskavage</Author>
        <Description>The estimates of gross product by industry have been revised to incorporate the results of the recent comprehensive revision of the NIPA's, newly available source data, and several methodological changes. The most significant element of the revision is the development of an integrated set of estimates of gross output, intermediate inputs, and gross product originating (GPO) for all industries. This result enabled the extension of the double-deflation method for computing real GPO to all industries, thereby improving the reliability of the estimates and their consistency with the NIPA estimates. The revisions did not greatly affect the growth rates for real GPO: Real GPO growth for private industries was revised up 0.3 percentage point, the same as the upward revision to real GDP.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/National/NIPAREL/2000/0600gpi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Gross domestic product by industry</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-06-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-06-04</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Comprehensive Revision of State Personal Income: Revised Estimates for 1969-98 and Preliminary Estimates for 1999</Title>
        <Author>Robert L. Brown, Kathy A. Albetski, Jeffrey L. Newman, Adrienne T. Pilot, Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>On May 17, 2000, BEA released revised estimates of State personal income for 1969-99 that incorporated the results of the most recent comprehensive revision of the NIPA's, newly available benchmark source data, and improved methods for preparing the State estimates. In general, the State estimates were revised up, reflecting several major improvements that were introduced into the national estimates. This release represents a speedup of nearly 6 months in the availability of State personal income estimates that are consistent with the recently revised NIPA estimates.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/regional/perinc/2000/0600spi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-06-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-06-05</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Daniel Larkins, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff, Mary L. Roy</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 5.4 percent in the first quarter of 2000 after in-creasing 7.3 percent in the fourth quarter of 1999; the price index for gross domestic purchases increased 3.2 percent after increasing 2.3 percent. Corporate profits increased $34.5 billion (3.8 percent at a quarterly rate) in the first quarter. The Federal Government current surplus increased $74.1 billion, to $186.3 billion, and the State and local government current surplus decreased $12.1 billion, to $56.7 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/National/NIPA/2000/0600bsP.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-06-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-06-06</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: New Investment in 1999</Title>
        <Author>Ned G. Howenstine, Rosaria Troia</Author>
        <Description>Outlays by foreign investors to acquire or establish businesses in the United States increased to a record $282.9 billion in 1999 from $215.3 billion in 1998. The exceptionally high outlays in both years reflect a worldwide boom in merger and acquisition activity, the continuing strength of the U.S. economy, and the increasing number and size of large investments.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/FDINVEST/2000/0600fdi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-06-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-06-07</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Subject Guide for Volume 80, Numbers 1-6</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/beawide/2000/0600sg.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-06-23</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-07-01</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Travel and Tourism Satellite Accounts for 1996 and 1997</Title>
        <Author>David I. Kass, Sumiye Okubo</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. travel and tourism satellite accounts (TTSA's) have been updated to present estimates for 1996 and 1997. Like the 1992 TTSA's, the 1996 and 1997 TTSA's extend the input-output accounts to present a more comprehensive picture of the impact of travel and tourism activities on the U.S. economy. According to the TTSA's, final domestic demand for travel and tourism grew at an average annual rate of 6.9 percent from 1992 to 1997, while GDP increased at an average annual rate of 5.6 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/Inputout/2000/0700tta.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Satellite accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-07-27</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-07-02</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Revised Estimates for 1982-99</Title>
        <Author>Christopher L. Bach</Author>
        <Description>This year's annual revision of the international transactions accounts incorporates improvements to the investment income and portfolio capital accounts. The estimates of investment income are revised to incorporate the final results of the U.S. Treasury Department's Benchmark Survey of U.S. Portfolio Investment Abroad as of December 31, 1997. Net U.S. purchases of foreign securities are revised to reflect improvements in the accounting for large-scale foreign acquisitions of U.S. companies and to reflect other improvements in the coverage of U.S. transactions in foreign securities. The revised estimate of the U.S. current-account deficit for 1999 is -$331.5 billion, compared with the previously published estimate of -$338.9 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/BPA/2000/0700itr.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-07-27</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-07-03</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Comprehensive Revision of Local Area Personal Income: Revised Estimates for 1969-97 and New Estimates for 1998</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey L. Newman, Kathy A. Albetski, Robert L. Brown, Adrienne T. Pilot</Author>
        <Description>On June 15, 2000, BEA released estimates of local area personal income for 1969-98 that incorporated the results of the most recent comprehensive revisions of State personal income and of the NIPA's as well as improved methods for preparing the estimates and newly available data from regular sources. In general, the local area estimates were revised up, primarily reflecting the NIPA definitional change that reclassified government employee retirement plans. This release represents a speedup of about a year in the availability of local area estimates of personal income that are consistent with the recently revised State personal income estimates and NIPA estimates.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/REGIONAL/perinc/2000/0700lap.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Local area personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-07-27</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-07-04</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Ralph W. Morris, Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 5.5 percent in the first quarter of 2000 after increasing 7.3 percent in the fourth quarter of 1999; the price index for gross domestic purchases increased 3.5 percent after increasing 2.3 percent. Corporate profits increased $46.2 billion (5.0 percent at a quarterly rate) in the first quarter.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0700bsf.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-07-27</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-07-05</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Multinational Companies: Operations in 1998</Title>
        <Author>Raymond J. Mataloni, Jr.</Author>
        <Description>Growth slowed in three key measures--gross product, employment, and capital expenditures--of the operations of U.S. multinational companies in 1998 after strong growth in 1997. The gross product of U.S. parent companies increased 2.2 percent in 1998 after increasing 6.3 percent in 1997, and the gross product of the majority-owned affiliates of U.S. companies declined 1.9 percent after increasing 4.5 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/USINVEST/2000/0700mnc.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. multinational companies</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-07-27</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-07-06</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>The International Investment Position of the United States at Yearend 1999</Title>
        <Author>Russell B. Scholl</Author>
        <Description>The net international investment position of the United States changed little in 1999: At yearend, it was -$1,082 billion on a current-cost basis and -$1,474 billion on a market-value basis. Large net financial inflows were offset by greater price appreciation in U.S.-owned assets abroad than in foreign-owned assets in the United States.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/BPA/2000/0700iip.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international investment position</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-07-27</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-07-07</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Direct Investment Positions for 1999: Country and Industry Detail</Title>
        <Author>Sylvia E. Bargas</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. direct investment position abroad valued at historical cost increased 12 percent in 1999, and the foreign direct investment position in the United States valued at historical cost increased 24 percent. The strong growth in both positions reflected the global boom in merger and acquisition activity, favorable economic conditions in the United States, Europe, and Canada, and improved economic conditions in the Asia and Pacific area.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/fdinvest/2000/0700dip.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Direct investment positions: Country and industry detail</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-07-27</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-07-08</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, First Quarter 2000</Title>
        <Author>Douglas B. Weinberg</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit increased $6.1 billion, to $102.3 billion, in the first quarter of 2000; the increase was more than accounted for by a large increase in the deficit on goods. In the financial account, net recorded inflows increased $2.0 billion, to $71.7 billion; financial inflows increased more than financial outflows.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/BPA/2000/0700ita.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-07-27</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-08-01</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Annual Revision of the National Income and Product Accounts: Annual Estimates, 1997-99, and Quarterly Estimates, 1997:I-2000:I</Title>
        <Author>Eugene P. Seskin, David F. Sullivan</Author>
        <Description>The revised NIPA estimates do not significantly alter the picture of the U.S. economy that was shown in the previously published estimates. Over the period covered by the revisions, the average annual growth rate of real GDP was revised up slightly, from 4.5 percent to 4.6 percent, and the average annual rate of increase in the price index for gross domestic purchases was unrevised at 1.5 percent. The revised estimates reflect the incorporation of regular source data and the introduction of changes in the methodology for preparing the estimates; for example, the estimates of employer contributions to group health insurance are now based on data collected in the new medical expenditure panel survey.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0800nipr.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-08-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-08-02</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Ralph W. Morris</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP continued to increase strongly in the second quarter of 2000, up 5.2 percent after a 4.8-percent increase in the first quarter. In contrast, real final sales of domestic product slowed to a 4.2-percent increase from a 6.7-percent increase. The price index for gross domestic purchases slowed to a 2.2-percent increase from a 3.8-percent increase.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0800bsa.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-08-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-08-03</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Affiliates of Foreign Companies: Operations in 1998</Title>
        <Author>William J. Zeile</Author>
        <Description>The current-dollar gross product of U.S. affiliates of foreign companies increased 7 percent in 1998, primarily reflecting record levels of new foreign investment. The U.S.-affiliate share of gross product originating in U.S. private industries edged up from 6.2 percent in 1997 to 6.3 percent in 1998. By country of ownership, the United Kingdom remained the largest investing country in 1998, and Germany overtook Japan as the second largest as a result of new acquisitions of U.S. companies.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/FDINVEST/2000/0800fdi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-08-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-08-04</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>State Personal Income, First Quarter 2000</Title>
        <Author>Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>Personal income in the Nation slowed to a 1.6-percent increase in the first quarter of 2000 from a 1.9-percent increase in the fourth quarter of 1999. In the first quarter, personal income grew the fastest in Vermont, North Carolina, Alaska, Georgia, and Florida. Personal income declined in North Dakota, Nebraska, Kansas, South Dakota, and Iowa.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/REGIONAL/perinc/2000/0800spi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-08-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-08-05</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>National Income and Product Accounts Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0800nipt.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-08-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-08-06</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>GDP and Other Major NIPA Series, 1929-2000:I</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0800gdp.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-08-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-08-07</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Errata: U.S. Travel and Tourism Satellite Accounts for 1996 and 1997</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/INPUTOUT/2000/0800tsaerr.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Satellite accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-08-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-09-01</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Daniel Larkins, Ralph W. Morris, Jennifer S. Argueta, Steven J. Andrews</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP accelerated modestly to a 5.3-percent increase in the second quarter of 2000 from a 4.8-percent increase in the first quarter; in contrast, real final sales of domestic product decelerated sharply to a 3.5-percent increase from a 6.7-percent increase. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 2.3 percent after increasing 3.8 percent. Corporate profits increased $27.7 billion (3.0 percent at a quarterly rate) in the second quarter after increasing $43.1 billion (4.8 percent) in the first. The Federal Government surplus increased $2.0 billion, to $237.8 billion, in the second quarter after increasing $92.5 billion in the first. The State and local government surplus increased $2.2 billion, to $54.2 billion, after decreasing $14.6 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0900bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-09-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-09-02</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Customer Service Report for Fiscal Year 2000</Title>
        <Author>Verna M. Learnard</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/BEAWIDE/2000/0900csr.pdf</URL>
        <Category>General</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-09-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-09-03</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Annual NIPA Revision: Newly Available Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/0900nat.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-09-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-09-04</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Fixed Assets and Consumer Durable Goods for 1925-99</Title>
        <Author>Shelby W. Herman</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/2000/0900cdg.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Fixed assets and consumer durable goods</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-09-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-09-05</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: Detail for Historical-Cost Position and Related Capital and Income Flows, 1999</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey H. Lowe</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/FDINVEST/2000/0900fdi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-09-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-09-06</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Direct Investment Abroad: Detail for Historical-Cost Position and Related Capital and Income Flows, 1999</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey H. Lowe</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/USINVEST/2000/0900usd.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-09-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-10-01</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Gross State Product by Industry, 1977-98</Title>
        <Author>Richard M. Beemiller, Clifford H. Woodruff III</Author>
        <Description>BEA's estimates of gross state product (GSP) by industry have been revised to incorporate the most recent comprehensive revisions of the NIPA's, of the national estimates of gross product by industry, and of the estimates of State personal income. In 1997-98, the State with the fastest growth in real GSP was Arizona (7.5 percent annual rate), followed by Oregon (7.2 percent) and Nevada (6.9 percent); the States with negative growth were Hawaii (-0.5 percent) and Alaska (-0.4 percent). The State with the largest share of nominal GSP in 1998 was California (12.8 percent), followed by New York (8.1 percent) and Texas (7.4 percent).</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/REGIONAL/GSP/2000/1000gsp.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Gross state product</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-10-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-10-02</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Ralph W. Morris, Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 5.6 percent in the second quarter of 2000, according to the &quot;final&quot; NIPA estimates; the upward revision of 0.3 percentage point from the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate primarily reflected a downward revision to imports of services and an upward revision to exports of services. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 2.1 percent; the downward revision of 0.2 percentage point primarily reflected downward revisions to the prices of personal consumption expenditures for services. Corporate profits increased $27.3 billion (2.9 percent at a quarterly rate) in the second quarter.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/1000bsf.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-10-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-10-03</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Second Quarter 2000</Title>
        <Author>Harlan W. King</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit increased $4.6 billion, to $106.1 billion, in the second quarter of 2000; nearly all of the increase was accounted for by an increase in the deficit on goods. In the financial account, net recorded inflows increased $91.5 billion, to $149.1 billion; financial outflows slowed substantially, while financial inflows remained strong.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/BPA/2000/1000ita.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-10-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-10-04</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Services: Cross-Border Trade in 1999 and Sales Through Affiliates in 1998</Title>
        <Author>Michael A. Mann, Laura L. Brokenbaugh, Sylvia E. Bargas</Author>
        <Description>In 1999, U.S. cross-border exports of private services increased 4 percent to $254.7 billion, and U.S. cross-border imports of these services increased 4 percent to $174.8 billion; as a result, the U.S. surplus on cross-border trade in services increased $3.3 billion, to $79.8 billion. In 1998, sales of private services abroad by foreign affiliates of U.S. companies increased 21 percent to $309.0 billion, and sales of services in the United States by U.S. affiliates of foreign companies increased 14 percent to $255.1 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/INTSERV/2000/1000is.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international services</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-10-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-10-05</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, 1996:IV-2000:II</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/2000/1000isr.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-10-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-10-06</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Annual NIPA Revision: Newly Available Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/1000nat.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-10-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-10-07</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Updated Summary NIPA Methodologies</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/1000Nsum.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-10-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-10-08</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Index to the NIPA Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/1000nipi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-10-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-10-09</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>State Personal Income, Revised Estimates for 1997-99</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey L. Newman</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/REGIONAL/perinc/2000/1000spi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-10-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-10-10</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Schedule of BEA News Releases in 2001</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/BEAWIDE/2000/1000rd.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-10-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-11-01</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris</Author>
        <Description>The growth in the U.S. economy slowed in the third quarter of 2000, while inflation remained moderate. Real GDP increased 2.7 percent, less than half as much as the average increase in the preceding four quarters; the price index for gross domestic purchases increased 2.4 percent, about the same as the average increase in the preceding four quarters.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/1100bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-11-21</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-11-02</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Comparison of BEA Estimates of Personal Income and IRS Estimates of Adjusted Gross Income: New Estimates for 1998 and Revised Estimates for 1997</Title>
        <Author>Thae S. Park</Author>
        <Description>BEA's estimates of personal income and the IRS estimates of adjusted gross income (AGI)--two widely used measures of household income--are reconciled through a series of adjustments for definitional differences between the two measures. This year's reconciliation reflects the recent annual revision of the national income and product accounts and recent updates to the AGI estimates.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/2000/1100pinagi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, BEA personal income and IRS adjusted gross income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-11-21</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-11-03</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Reconciliation of the U.S.-Canadian Current Account, 1998 and 1999</Title>
        <Author>Anthony DiLullo, Hugh Henderson</Author>
        <Description>Each year, the U.S. and Canadian current-account estimates are reconciled to show how they would appear if both countries used the same definitions, methodologies, and data sources. After the reconciliation, the U.S. current-account deficits with Canada are larger than those that are shown in the U.S.-published accounts: For 1998, the deficit on the reconciled basis is $9.6 billion, compared with the U.S.-published deficit of $4.4 billion; for 1999, the reconciled deficit is $19.5 billion, compared with the published deficit of $15.1 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/BPA/2000/1100us-can.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Reconciliation of the U.S.-Canadian current account</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-11-21</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-11-04</ID>
        <Volume>89</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>State Personal Income, Second Quarter 2000</Title>
        <Author>Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>Personal income in the Nation increased 1.7 percent in the second quarter of 2000 after increasing 1.6 percent in the first quarter. In the second quarter, personal income grew the fastest in Nevada, Delaware, and Iowa. Personal income grew the slowest in Connecticut, Arizona, North Dakota, and New Hampshire.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/REGIONAL/perinc/2000/1100spiq.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-11-21</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-12-01</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>A Note on the Impact of Hedonics and Computers on Real GDP</Title>
        <Author>J. Steven Landefeld, Bruce T. Grimm</Author>
        <Description>A review of the data on hedonic price indexes and their impact on real GDP growth shows no evidence of an overstatement in the measured decline in computer prices. The hedonic price indexes for computers produce results that are quite robust and that are virtually the same as those produced by a carefully constructed traditional price index for computers.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/BEAWIDE/2000/1200hm.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-12-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-12-02</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>R. Moran, Daniel Larkins, Ralph W. Morris, Jennifer S. Argueta, Steven J. Andrews</Author>
        <Description>The growth in the U.S. economy slowed in the third quarter of 2000, while inflation remained moderate. Real GDP increased 2.4 percent, less than half as much as the average increase in the preceding four quarters; the prices of gross domestic purchases increased 2.3 percent, about the same as the average increase in the preceding four quarters. Corporate profits increased $7.6 billion (0.8 percent at a quarterly rate) in the third quarter after increasing $27.3 billion (2.9 percent) in the second. The Federal Government current surplus increased $13.4 billion, to $254.3 billion, in the third quarter after increasing $5.1 billion in the second. The State and local government current surplus increased $4.1 billion, to $64.2 billion, after increasing $8.1 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/1200bsp.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-12-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-12-03</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Gross Domestic Product by Industry for 1997-99</Title>
        <Author>Sherlene K.S. Lum, Brian C. Moyer</Author>
        <Description>New estimates of gross domestic product by industry for 1999 and revised estimates for 1997 and 1998 incorporate the results of this year's annual revision of the NIPA's and newly available source data. According to these estimates, the long-term structural shift in the U.S. economy from goods-producing industries to services-producing industries continued. The revisions to the real growth rate of private industries were small, but the revisions to the growth rates for some of the individual industry groups were substantial.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/2000/1200gpi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Gross domestic product by industry</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-12-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-12-04</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Revised Estimates of Real Gross Product of Nonfinancial Corporate Business for 1997-2000</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPA/2000/1200gncb.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-12-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-12-05</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Federal Personal Income Tax Liabilities and Payments, 1959-98</Title>
        <Author>Thae S. Park</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/NATIONAL/NIPAREL/2000/1200fpit.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Federal personal income tax liabilities and payments</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-12-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-12-06</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Subject Guide</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/BEAWIDE/2000/1200sg.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-12-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-80-12-07</ID>
        <Volume>80</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2000</Year>
        <Title>Schedule of BEA News Releases in 2001</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/BEAWIDE/2000/1200rd.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>2000-12-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
