<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-01-01</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Improved Estimates of the National Income and Product Accounts for 1959–95: Results of the Comprehensive Revision</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>In January, BEA released revised NIPA estimates beginning with 1959 that reflect a comprehensive revision of the accounts. The comprehensive revision introduced the following major improvements to the accounts: Improved chain-type measures of real output and prices, a new treatment of government investment, a new methodology for calculating depreciation, and new and redesigned tables. For 1959–94, the revised estimates of real GDP show an average annual growth rate of 3.2 percent, 0.2 percentage point higher than the previously published estimates. For 1987–94, however, the revised growth rate of 2.3 percent is 0.1 percentage point lower than previously published.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1996/0296od.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Gross product by industry</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-02-20</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-02-01</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Improved Estimates of the National Income and Product Accounts for 1959–95: Results of the Comprehensive Revision</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>In January, BEA released revised NIPA estimates beginning with 1959 that reflect a comprehensive revision of the accounts. The comprehensive revision introduced the following major improvements to the accounts: Improved chain-type measures of real output and prices, a new treatment of government investment, a new methodology for calculating depreciation, and new and redesigned tables. For 1959–94, the revised estimates of real GDP show an average annual growth rate of 3.2 percent, 0.2 percentage point higher than the previously published estimates. For 1987–94, however, the revised growth rate of 2.3 percent is 0.1 percentage point lower than previously published.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1996/0296od.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Gross product by industry</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-02-20</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-03-01</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Differences in Foreign-Owned U.S. Manufacturing Establishments by Country of Owner</Title>
        <Author>Ned G. Howenstine, Dale P. Shannon</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. manufacturing establishments of each of the six major investing countries—Canada, France, Germany, Japan, the Netherlands, and the United Kingdom—tend to be much larger, pay higher wages, and be more productive than U.S.-owned establishments. These tendencies vary by country of owner, partly reflecting differences in the distribution of establishments by industry and partly reflecting differences within the same industries. These findings are based on an analysis of data for 1991 that were derived by linking BEA enterprise-level data on foreign direct investment in the United States with establishment-level data from the Census Bureau's annual survey of manufactures.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/fdinvest/1996/0396iid.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-03-07</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-03-02</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>Economic growth slowed markedly in the fourth quarter of 1995: Real GDP increased 0.9 percent after increasing 3.6 percent in the third quarter. Inflation remained moderate: The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 2.0 percent after increasing 1.7 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1996/0396bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Gross domestic product</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-03-07</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-03-03</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Personal Income by State and Region, Third Quarter 1995</Title>
        <Author>Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>Personal income in the Nation increased 1.2 percent in the third quarter of 1995 after increasing 1.1 percent in the second quarter. In the third quarter, Nevada and Delaware had the largest increases in personal income, 2.3 percent, and Hawaii had the smallest increase, 0.3 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/regional/perinc/1996/0396rea.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-03-07</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-04-01</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris, Claire G. Pitzer, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>Real slowed to a 0.5-percent increase in the fourth quarter of 1995 from a 3.6-percent increase in the third quarter; the price index for gross domestic purchases increased 2.1 percent after increasing 1.7 percent. Corporate profits increased $3.7 billion after jumping $53.8 billion. The Federal Government current deficit decreased to $154.9 billion, the lowest level since the first quarter of 1991, and the State and local government current surplus decreased to $88.1 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1996/0496bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Gross domestic product</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-04-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-04-02</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Fourth Quarter and Year 1995</Title>
        <Author>Christopher L. Bach</Author>
        <Description>In the fourth quarter of 1995, the U.S. current-account deficit decreased $9.2 billion, to $31.1 billion. The deficits on merchandise trade and on investment both fell sharply, while the surplus on services and net unilateral transfers changed little. For the year 1995, the current-account deficit increased $1.7 billion, to $152.9 billion. Increases in the deficits on merchandise trade and on investment income were nearly offset by an increase in the surplus on services and a reduction in net unilateral transfers.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/bpa/1996/0496bop.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Balance of payments</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-04-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-04-03</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>User's Guide to BEA Information</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>Contains updated information to help users locate the most recent and most frequently requested BEA products. The guide also includes descriptions of BEA's programs, a subject listing for BEA products, and order information and forms.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/beawide/1996/0496ug.pdf</URL>
        <Category>General</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-04-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-05-01</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>Economic growth picked up in the first quarter of 1996: Real GDP increased 2.8 percent after increasing 0.5 percent in the fourth quarter of 1995. Inflation remained moderate: The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 2.5 percent after increasing 2.1 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1996/0596bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Gross domestic product</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-05-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-05-02</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Relationship Between Personal Income and Adjusted Gross Income: New Estimates for 1993–94 and Revisions for 1959–92</Title>
        <Author>Thae S. Park</Author>
        <Description>BEA's measure of personal income and the IRS measure of adjusted gross income—two widely used measures of household income—are reconciled through a series of adjustments for definitional and statistical differences between the two measures. This reconciliation incorporates the results of the recent comprehensive revision of the NIPA's and several improvements that have been made in the estimation of the reconciliation items.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1996/0596gd.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Government transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-05-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-05-03</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Total and Per Capita Personal Income by State and Region</Title>
        <Author>Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>Personal income in the Nation increased 1.2 percent in the fourth quarter of 1995, the same rate of increase as in the third quarter. In the fourth quarter, Utah had the largest increase in personal income, 2.3 percent, and Nebraska had the smallest increase, 0.2 percent. In the year 1995, per capita personal income in the Nation increased 5.0 percent, while U.S. prices increased only 2.4 percent. In all States except North Dakota and South Dakota, the increases in per capita income exceeded the increase in U.S. prices.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/regional/perinc/1996/0596rea.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-05-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-05-04</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Selected Monthly Estimates</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1996/0596sme.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-05-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-05-05</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, 1977–95</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1996/0596niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-05-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-05-06</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>1996 Release Dates for BEA Estimates</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/beawide/1996/0596rd.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-05-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-06-01</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>BEA's Mid-Decade Strategic Plan: A Progress Report</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>BEA has made substantial progress in implementing the improvements in its national, regional, and international accounts that were proposed in last year's Mid-Decade Strategic Plan. Improvements in output measures include the introduction of a chain-type weighting scheme for calculating changes in real GDP and the incorporation of quality-adjusted prices of exports and imports of semiconductors. Improvements in measures of investment and saving include the adoption of the treatment of government purchases of structures and equipment as investment, and the introduction of a new methodology for calculating depreciation. Improvements in the coverage of international transactions include conducting the first benchmark survey of international trade in financial services and redesigning BEA's surveys to collect detailed data on multinational companies' international trade and services.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/beawide/1996/0696od.pdf</URL>
        <Category>General</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-06-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-06-02</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Metropolitan Area and BEA Economic Area Projections of Economic Activity and Population to the Year 2005</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>According to BEA's regional projections to 2005, the 20 metropolitan areas with the fastest projected growth in employment are all located in California, elsewhere in the West, or in Florida. In contrast, most of the 20 metropolitan areas with the slowest projected growth in employment are located in, or near, the Great Lakes and Mideast regions.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/regional/proj/1996/0696rea.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Projections</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-06-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-06-03</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Daniel Larkins, Ralph W. Morris, Claire G. Pitzer, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 2.3 percent in the first quarter of 1996, up from a 0.5-percent increase in the fourth quarter of 1995. Corporate profits increased $24.2 billion, up from an increase of $3.7 billion. The Federal Government current deficit edged up to $155.7 billion, and the State and local government surplus decreased to $86.6 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1996/0696bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Gross domestic product</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-06-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-06-04</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Local Area Personal Income, 1992–94</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>Seven of the ten metropolitan areas with the highest per capita personal income in 1994 are located in the New York-New Jersey-Long Island consolidated metropolitan statistical area. The 10 areas with the lowest per capita personal income are generally located in the Southeast or Southwest regions.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/regional/perinc/1996/0696rem.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-06-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-06-05</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Selected Monthly Estimates</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1996/0696sme.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-06-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-06-06</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Errata: Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1996/0696err.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-06-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-06-07</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Subject Guide: Volume 76 1996, Numbers 1–6</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/beawide/1996/0696sg.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-06-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-07-01</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Revised Estimates for 1986–95</Title>
        <Author>Christopher L. Bach</Author>
        <Description>This year's annual revision of the balance of payments accounts features major improvements in the coverage of both the services markets and the capital markets. In the services markets, coverage is extended and improved through the incorporation of the results of BEA's first benchmark survey of international trade in financial services; in the capital markets, coverage is improved through the incorporation of the results of a special survey of selected foreign financial assets. In addition, the accuracy of the estimates of personal remittances of the foreign-born population of the United States is improved through the incorporation of newly available data from the Census Bureau, the Immigration and Naturalization Service, and the Department of Labor.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/bpa/1996/0796bp.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Balance of payments</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-07-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-07-02</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 2.2 percent in the first quarter of 1996. Real GNP increased 2.5 percent, and real GNP on a command basis also increased 2.5 percent. Corporate profits increased $33.4 billion; profits of both financial and non-financial domestic corporations rebounded from fourth-quarter decreases.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1996/0796bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Gross domestic product</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-07-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-07-03</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>The International Investment Position of the United States in 1995</Title>
        <Author>Russell B. Scholl</Author>
        <Description>The net international investment position of the United States became more negative in 1995: On a current-cost basis, it fell $233.9 billion, to -$814.0 billion; and on a market-value basis, it fell $281.2 billion, to -$773.7 billion. The change in the position was attributable to large net capital inflows and to larger price appreciation in U.S. securities than in foreign securities.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/INTERNAT/BPA/1996/0796iip.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Investment position</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-07-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-07-04</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Direct Investment Positions on a Historical-Cost Basis: Country and Industry Detail for 1995 and Changes in Geographic Composition Since 1982</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey H. Lowe, Sylvia E. Bargas</Author>
        <Description>In 1995, the U.S. direct investment position abroad valued at historical cost increased 15 percent, and the foreign direct investment position in the United States increased 11 percent. From 1982 to 1995, the shares of the U.S. direct investment position abroad accounted for by Europe, Asia and Pacific, and Latin America and Other Western Hemisphere increased, while the share accounted for by Canada decreased; the shares of the foreign direct investment position in the United States accounted for by Asia and Pacific increased, while the shares accounted for by most other areas decreased.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/usinvest/1996/0796dip.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Investment position</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-07-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-07-05</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, First Quarter 1996</Title>
        <Author>Lori A. Trawinski</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit increased $5.2 billion, to $35.6 billion, in the first quarter of 1996. An increase in the deficit on goods and services and higher net unilateral transfers more than offset a decrease in the deficit on investment income.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/bpa/1996/0796bop.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Balance of payments</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-07-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-07-06</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: New Investment in 1995 and Affiliate Operations in 1994</Title>
        <Author>Mahnaz Fahim-Nader, William J. Zeile</Author>
        <Description>In 1995, outlays by foreign investors for acquiring and establishing U.S. businesses increased for the third consecutive year; however, they remained well below the levels in 1988–90, when investments from Japan were much higher. In 1994, most measures of the operations of U.S. affiliates of foreign companies increased; for example, the gross product of nonbank U.S. affiliates increased 12 percent, and their share of U.S. private-industry gross product increased to 6.2 percent from 6.0 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/fdinvest/1996/0796iid.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-07-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-07-07</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Selected Monthly Estimates</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1996/0796sme.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-07-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-07-08</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1996/0796niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-07-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-08-01</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Annual Revision of the National Income and Product Accounts: Annual Estimates, 1993–95, and Quarterly Estimates, 1993:I–1996:I</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>The revisions to the major aggregate NIPA measures of product, income, and prices that resulted from this year's annual revision were small. For example, the annual growth rate of real GDP was revised up 0.1 percentage point to 2.3 percent for 1993 and was unrevised at 3.5 percent for 1994 and 2.0 percent for 1995. This year's revision was limited to the updating of the annual weights used in the calculation of the chain-type measures of real output and prices, the incorporation of the results of this year's annual revision of the balance of payments accounts, and the incorporation of newly available data on wages and salaries from the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1996/0896niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-08-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-08-02</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Improved Estimates of Gross Product by Industry, 1959–94</Title>
        <Author>Robert E. Yuskavage</Author>
        <Description>BEA's estimates of gross product by industry have been revised, beginning with 1959 for the current-dollar estimates and with 1977 for the real estimates, to incorporate the results of the recent comprehensive revision of the NIPA's and several statistical improvements specific to the GPO estimates. For 1977–94, the growth rates of real gross product by industry ranged from 4.9 percent for wholesale trade to 0.9 percent for mining. For 1959–94, the share of current-dollar GDP accounted for by private services-producing industries increased from 48.8 percent to 62.0 percent, while the share accounted for by private goods-producing industries declined from 38.8 percent to 24.2 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1996/0896gpo.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-08-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-08-03</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>Economic growth picked up in the second quarter of 1996: Real GDP increased 4.2 percent after increasing 2.0 percent in the first quarter. Inflation remained moderate: The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 2.0 percent after increasing 2.3 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1996/0896bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Gross domestic product</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-08-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-08-04</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Federal Personal Income Tax Liabilities and Payments, 1959–94</Title>
        <Author>Thae S. Park</Author>
        <Description>BEA's estimates of Federal personal income tax liabilities and payments have been revised, beginning with 1959, to incorporate the results of the recent comprehensive revision of the NIPA's, as well as newly available tax return information. As is typical for most years, taxpayer payments of Federal income taxes for 1994 exceeded their tax liabilities by $5.3 billion; the excess in payments for 1994 was largely attributable to deferred payments of 1993 liabilities.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1996/0896re.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Government transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-08-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-08-05</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Personal Income by State and Region, First Quarter 1996</Title>
        <Author>Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>Personal income in the Nation increased 1.2 percent in the first quarter of 1996, the same rate of increase as in the fourth quarter of 1995. In the first quarter, personal income increased in all but two States: In Delaware, personal income was unchanged, and in Michigan, it declined. Of the 13 fastest growing States, 9 were in the western United States; Idaho had the fastest growth.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/regional/perinc/1996/0896rea.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-08-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-08-06</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Selected Monthly Estimates</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1996/0896sme.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-08-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-09-01</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Pollution Abatement and Control Expenditures, 1972–94</Title>
        <Author>Christine R. Vogan</Author>
        <Description>Real spending for pollution abatement and control (PAC) increased 7.3 percent in 1994 after increasing 2.5 percent in 1993. Spending increased for all major types; the largest increase was for air PAC (12.4 percent). Real spending for pollution abatement (PA), the largest component of PAC, increased 7.6 percent in 1994. Spending increased substantially across all major sectors of the economy; the largest increase was for personal consumption PA (11.8 percent). During 1972–94, real PAC spending increased at an average annual rate of 3.6 percent. By type, the fastest growth was in solid waste PAC spending (6.3 percent).</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1996/0996eed.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Pollution abatement and control</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-09-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-09-02</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Daniel Larkins, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff, Michael W. Webb</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 4.8 percent in the second quarter of 1996 after increasing 2.0 percent in the first quarter; the step-up was largely accounted for by an upturn in inventory investment and a pickup in government spending. Corporate profits increased $8.7 billion in the second quarter after increasing $33.3 billion in the first. As a result of larger increases in receipts than in expenditures, the Federal Government current deficit decreased $24.2 billion, to $131.0 billion, and the State and local government current surplus increased $10.0 billion, to $101.0 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1996/0996bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Gross domestic product</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-09-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-09-03</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>State and Local Government Fiscal Position, 1995</Title>
        <Author>Florence H. Campi</Author>
        <Description>The current surplus of State and local governments decreased $4.7 billion, to $95.0 billion, in 1995. Receipts decelerated slightly, reflecting decelerations in all components except personal income taxes. Current expenditures accelerated, largely reflecting accelerations in consumption expenditures and in transfer payments for medical care. For 1996, available information suggests an increase of about $8–$14 billion in the current surplus of State and local governments.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1996/0996gd.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Government transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-09-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date>5/26/1998</Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-09-04</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Selected Monthly Estimates</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1996/0996sme.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-09-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-09-05</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Customer Satisfaction Report</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/beawide/1996/0996cust.pdf</URL>
        <Category>General</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-09-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-09-06</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: Detail for Historical-Cost Position and Related Capital and Income Flows, 1995</Title>
        <Author>Gregory G. Fouch, Peter J. Fox, Nancy F. Halvorson, Tracy K. Leigh, Beverly E. Palmer, Linden L. Webber. D. Richard Mauery, Karen Sellami</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/fdinvest/1996/0996fdi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-09-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-09-07</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Direct Investment Abroad: Detail for Historical-Cost Position and Related Capital and Income Flows, 1995</Title>
        <Author>Mark W. New, Laura A. Downey, Marie K. Laddomada, Sherry Lee, Leila C. Morrison, William A. Reese, Gary M. Solamon, Dwayne Torney, Wendy P. Warcholik, Smith W. Allnutt</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/usinvest/1996/0996usd.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-09-11</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-10-01</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>The International Monetary Fund's New Standards for Economic Statistics</Title>
        <Author>John B. McLenaghan</Author>
        <Description>In April 1996, the International Monetary Fund issued new standards for data dissemination for member countries. The standards are aimed at encouraging countries to take steps to meet the need for better statistics on four broad fronts: Coverage, periodicity, and timeliness; access by the public; integrity; and quality. By voluntary subscription to the standard, a country makes public its commitment to the standards' requirements for the dissemination of data considered essential for the comprehension of economic performance. The United States is among the countries to date that have agreed to comply with the new standards.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/beawide/1996/1096imf.pdf</URL>
        <Category>General</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-10-08</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-10-02</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Comprehensive Revision of State Personal Income, 1969–95</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>In late September, BEA released the results of the comprehensive revision of the annual estimates of State personal income and disposable personal income for 1969–95. The revised State estimates incorporate the recent comprehensive NIPA revision, improvements in the source data and in the methods used to estimate specific components of State personal income, and newly available data from regular sources. For most States, personal income was revised up for most years. However, for most States, the effects of the revisions on the long-term growth rates of personal income and on the rankings of per capita personal income were small.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/regional/perinc/1996/1096rem.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-10-08</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-10-03</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 4.7 percent in the second quarter of 1996, up from a 2.0-percent increase in the first quarter. Real GNP increased 4.3 percent in the second quarter. Corporate profits increased $10.7 billion in the second quarter after increasing $33.3 billion in the first; the slowdown was largely accounted for by profits of domestic financial corporations.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1996/1096bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-10-08</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-10-04</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Second Quarter 1996</Title>
        <Author>Douglas B.Weinberg</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit increased $3.9 billion, to $38.8 billion, in the second quarter of 1996. An increase in the deficit on goods and services and a shift to a deficit on investment income more than offset lower net unilateral transfers.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/bpa/1996/1096bop.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Balance of payments</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-10-08</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-10-05</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Selected Monthly Estimates</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1996/1096sme.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-10-08</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-10-06</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, 1994:I–1996:II</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1996/1096niw.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-10-08</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-11-01</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff</Author>
        <Description>Economic growth slowed in the third quarter of 1996: Real GDP increased 2.2 percent after increasing 4.7 percent in the second quarter. Inflation remained moderate: The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.8 percent after increasing 2.1 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1996/1196bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Gross domestic product</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-11-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-11-02</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Motor Vehicles, Model Year 1996</Title>
        <Author>Ralph W. Morris</Author>
        <Description>In model year 1996, motor vehicle sales increased to 15.5 million units, the highest level in 8 years. Sales of new trucks advanced to another record high, but sales of new cars declined for the second year in a row.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1996/1196mv.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Motor vehicles</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-11-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-11-03</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Reconciliation of the U.S.-Canadian Current Account, 1994 and 1995</Title>
        <Author>Anthony J. DiLullo, Lucie Laliberté</Author>
        <Description>The reconciliation of the U.S.-Canadian current account—which reflects how the current-account estimates would appear if both countries used common definitions, methodologies, and data sources—shows a U.S. current-account deficit with Canada for both 1994 and 1995 that is somewhat larger than the deficit shown in the U.S.-published estimates. The annual reconciliation is undertaken because of extensive economic links between the two countries and the need to explain differences in the published Canadian and U.S. estimates of the bilateral current account. The reconciliation process results in greater accuracy of the published estimates and in increased efficiency in producing these estimates.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/bpa/1996/1196bop.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Reconciliation and other special tables</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-11-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-11-04</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Sales and Purchases of Private Services: U.S. Cross-Border Transactions in 1995 and Sales by Affiliates in 1994</Title>
        <Author>Michael A. Mann, Daniel J. Atherton, Laura L. Brokenbaugh, Sylvia E. Bargas</Author>
        <Description>U.S. international sales and purchases of private services consist of cross-border trade between U.S. and foreign residents and of services delivered to international markets through affiliates of multinational companies. In 1995, U.S. cross-border sales of services to foreigners increased slightly faster than U.S. cross-border purchases of services from foreigners; the fastest growing category for both exports and imports of these services was royalties and license fees. In 1994, the latest year for which data are available on services delivered through affiliates, U.S. purchases of services from majority-owned U.S. affiliates of foreign companies increased faster than sales abroad by majority-owned foreign affiliates of U.S. companies.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/intserv/1996/1196srv.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, International services</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-11-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-11-05</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Selected Monthly Estimates</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/niparel/1996/1196sme.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-11-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-11-06</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>State Personal Income, 1990:I–1996:II</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/regional/perinc/1996/1196rem.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-11-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-11-07</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>1997 Release Dates for BEA Estimates</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/beawide/1996/1196rd.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-11-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-12-01</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Operations of U.S. Multinational Companies: Preliminary Results From the 1994 Benchmark Survey</Title>
        <Author>Raymond J. Mataloni, Jr., Mahnaz Fahim-Nader</Author>
        <Description>The overseas operations of U.S. multinational companies (MNC's) remain concentrated in a small number of large, high-income economies, and most of their overseas production is for sale in local markets rather than for export back to the United States; thus, the location of overseas production by U.S. MNC's appears to be determined more by access to markets than by access to low-wage labor or to natural resources. U.S. MNC's continue to play a large, though somewhat diminished, role in U.S. international trade in goods. These findings are based on preliminary results from BEA's latest benchmark survey of U.S. direct investment abroad, which covers 1994.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/internat/usinvest/1996/1296iid.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-12-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-12-02</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation</Title>
        <Author>Larry R. Moran, Ralph W. Morris, Deborah Y. Sieff, Ann M. Groszkiewicz</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 2.0 percent in the third quarter of 1996 after increasing 4.7 percent in the second quarter; the slowdown was mainly accounted for by a slowdown in personal consumption expenditures and by a downturn in government spending. Corporate profits decreased $1.1 billion in the third quarter after increasing $10.7 billion in the second. The Federal Government current deficit decreased $6.7 billion, to $120.3 billion, and the State and local government current surplus decreased $11.9 billion, to $89.1 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/national/nipa/1996/1296bs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Gross domestic product</Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-12-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-12-03</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>Subject Guide, Volume 76 (1996)</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/beawide/1996/1296sg.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-12-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-76-12-04</ID>
        <Volume>76</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>1996</Year>
        <Title>1997 Release Dates for BEA Estimates</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/beawide/1996/1296rd.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>1996-12-10</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
