<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-01-01</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Reliability of GDP and Related NIPA Estimates</Title>
        <Author>Dennis J. Fixler, Bruce T. Grimm</Author>
        <Description>A recent study by BEA found that the quarterly estimates of real GDP are reliable indicators of whether the economy is expanding or contracting, whether the economy is accelerating or decelerating, and whether the economy is growing at rates above, near, or below the long-term trend. The estimates were also found to be good indicators of cyclical peaks and troughs. In addition, the study found that the revisions by quarter differ substantially (for example, the average revision to the third-quarter estimates differs noticeably from that to the fourth-quarter estimates) and that the revisions due to seasonal factors tend to at least partly offset the revisions due to other causes.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/01January/0102ReliableNIPAs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-01-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/01january/0102rely.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-01-02</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Final Estimates for the Third Quarter of 2001</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Frederick von Batchelder</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP declined 1.3 percent in the third quarter of 2001, according to the &quot;final&quot; NIPA estimate, after four quarters of subpar growth. The &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate issued a month earlier had shown a 1.1-percent decline. The downward revision was primarily accounted for by downward revisions to State and local government gross investment in structures, exports of services, and personal consumption expenditures for services. Corporate profits decreased $62.8 billion (8.3 percent at a quarterly rate); a substantial portion of the decrease reflected a reduction in the profits of insurance carriers as a result of the payment of insurance benefits associated with the terrorist attacks of September 11th.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/01January/BSF0102.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-01-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/01january/0102bsf.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-01-03</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Third Quarter 2001</Title>
        <Author>Douglas B. Weinberg</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit decreased $12.6 billion, to $95.0 billion, in the third quarter of 2001. The decrease was accounted for by a large increase in the surplus on services and a decrease in the deficit on goods.The deficit on income was virtually unchanged, and net outflows for unilateral current transfers increased. In the financial account, net recorded inflows decreased $117.7 billion, to $36.7 billion, as financial inflows for foreign-owned assets in the United States decreased much more than financial outflows for U.S.-owned assets abroad.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/01January/ITAIII0102.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-01-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-01-04</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>1</Issue>
        <Month>January</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, 2001:III</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/01January/IS0102.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-01-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Data in this article are included in the underlying detail file in the NIPA Monthly Update</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/agency/uguide1.htm#0171</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-02-01</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>A Tribute to Robert Nathan</Title>
        <Author>Arnold J. Katz</Author>
        <Description>Monthly message from BEA Director Steve Landefeld</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/02%20February/0202Tribute.pdf</URL>
        <Category>General</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-02-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title></Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL></Supp2_URL>
        <Supp3_Title></Supp3_Title>
        <Supp3_URL></Supp3_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-02-02</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>BEA's Industry Accounts</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description>BEA's industry accounts present a variety of economic statistics that provide detailed information on the flows of goods and services to industries for the production of gross output, on the contributions by private industries and government to the Nation's gross domestic product, and on the activities of specific sectors of the economy.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/02%20February/0202Industry%20accts.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Industry, Industry Accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-02-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Input/Output Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/02%20February/io1201.xls</Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title>GDP by Industry Tables</Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/02%20February/GDPxI.xls</Supp2_URL>
        <Supp3_Title>Travel and Tourism</Supp3_Title>
        <Supp3_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/02%20February/ttsa.xls</Supp3_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-02-03</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Advance Estimates for the Fourth Quarter of 2001</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Frederick von Batchelder</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased slightly in the fourth quarter of 2001 after decreasing in the third quarter. Spending by consumers and by government strengthened, while business investment in fixed assets and in inventories declined more than in the third quarter. Prices paid by U.S. residents registered a small increase after a slight decrease in the third quarter. For the year 2001, real GDP slowed to a 1.1-percent increase from a 4.1-percent increase in 2000, and gross domestic purchases prices slowed to a 1.7-percent increase from a 2.6-percent increase.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/02%20February/0202BSA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-02-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables 1-5, Table A</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/02%20February/0202bsa.xls</Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title></Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL></Supp2_URL>
        <Supp3_Title></Supp3_Title>
        <Supp3_URL></Supp3_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-02-04</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>2</Issue>
        <Month>February</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Personal Income by State: Third Quarter 2001</Title>
        <Author>G. Andrew Bernat, Jr.</Author>
        <Description>Reflecting the continued slowdown in personal income for the Nation, personal income increased less than 1.0 percent in 33 States in the third quarter of 2001. Personal income decreased 0.2 percent in Washington and 0.1 percent in Delaware, and it grew only 0.1 percent in Nevada and 0.2 percent in Connecticut, New Jersey, and Michigan. Iowa, Nebraska, Maine, Wyoming, and New Mexico had the fastest growth in personal income.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/02%20February/0202SPIQIII.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-02-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables A-D, Tables 1-2</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/02%20February/0202spiQIII.xls</Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title></Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL></Supp2_URL>
        <Supp3_Title></Supp3_Title>
        <Supp3_URL></Supp3_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-03-01</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Operations of U.S. Multinational Companies: Preliminary Results From the 1999 Benchmark Survey</Title>
        <Author>Raymond J. Mataloni, Jr., Daniel R.Yorgason</Author>
        <Description>During the 1990s, the operations of U.S. multinational companies (MNC's) expanded at roughly the same pace as the U.S. economy and the worldwide economy. About three-fourths of the production by U.S. MNC's took place in the United States, and about one-fourth, abroad. Europe remained the major location for production abroad by U.S. MNC's, but the most rapid growth was in Asia and Pacific and in Latin America. Manufacturing remained the most important industry for U.S. MNC production, but the most rapid growth was in services, utilities, and retail trade. U.S. MNC's continued to play a large, though somewhat diminished, role in U.S. international trade in goods. Almost nine-tenths of the sales by foreign affiliates of U.S. MNC's were to foreign, mainly local, markets rather than to the United States.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/03March/0302USDIA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-03-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables 1-24.2</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/03March/0302usdia.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-03-02</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Preliminary Estimates for the Fourth Quarter of 2001</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Frederick von Batchelder</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 1.4 percent in the fourth quarter of 2001, according to the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate, after decreasing 1.3 percent in the third quarter. The &quot;advance&quot; estimate issued last month had shown a 0.2-percent increase. The upward revision was largely attributable to a downward revision to imports (which are subtracted in calculating GDP) and an upward revision to consumer spending. In addition, government spending, fixed investment, inventory investment, and exports were revised up. The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 0.4 percent in the fourth quarter after decreasing 0.1 percent in the third. The &quot;advance&quot; estimate had also shown a 0.4-percent increase.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/03March/0302BSP.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-03-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables 1-10</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/03March/0302bsa.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-03-03</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>3</Issue>
        <Month>March</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Federal Budget Estimates, Fiscal Year 2003</Title>
        <Author>Claire G. Pitzer,Shelly Smith</Author>
        <Description>Each year, BEA prepares an adjusted presentation of the administration's budget estimates that is consistent with the framework of the NIPA's. For fiscal year 2003, the Federal current deficit on the NIPA basis is estimated at $78.1 billion, compared with a deficit of $80.2 billion in the administration's budget. The NIPA estimate of current receipts exceeds the budget estimate of receipts by $32.0 billion, and the NIPA estimate of current expenditures exceeds the budget estimate of expenditures by $30.0 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/03March/0302FedBudget.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Federal budget estimates</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-03-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables 1-11</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/03March/0302budget.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-04-01</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Alternative Measures of Personal Saving</Title>
        <Author>Maria G. Perozek, Marshall B. Reinsdorf</Author>
        <Description>The two-decade downtrend in the NIPA measure of the personal saving rate has raised questions about the adequacy of savings to fund capital accumulation or the retirement of the baby boom generation. To provide background for addressing these questions, alternative measures of personal saving are presented that exclude defined-benefit pension plans, treat consumer durable goods as investment, remove the effects of inflation from nominal interest income and outlays, or remove capital gains taxes from personal tax payments. In addition, concerns about the funding of capital accumulation should be viewed within the broader context of national saving, which includes saving by the business and government sectors as well as the household sector. Concerns about retirement preparedness should be viewed within the broader context of household wealth.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/04April/0402PersonalSaving.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-04-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables 1-3</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/04April/0402personalsaving.xls</Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title></Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL></Supp2_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-04-02</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Final Estimates for the Fourth Quarter of 2001</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Frederick von Batchelder, Shelly Smith</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 1.7 percent in the fourth quarter of 2001, according to the &quot;final&quot; estimate; the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate issued last month had shown a 1.3-percent increase. The upward revision was largely attributable to an upward revision to exports and a downward revision to imports (which are subtracted in calculating GDP). Corporate profits increased $125.0 billion (17.9 percent at a quarterly rate) in the fourth quarter after decreasing $62.8 billion (-8.3 percent) in the third. The fiscal position of the Federal Government shifted to a current surplus of $97.4 billion from a current deficit of $13.6 billion, and the State and local government current surplus increased to $24.8 billion from $1.9 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/04April/0402BSF.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-04-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables 1-6, Table A</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/04April/0402bsf.xls</Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title></Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL></Supp2_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-04-03</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Fourth Quarter and Year 2001</Title>
        <Author>Christopher L. Bach</Author>
        <Description>In the fourth quarter of 2001, the U.S. current-account deficit edged up $0.3 billion, to $98.8 billion. Decreases in the deficit on goods and the deficit on income were offset by a decrease in the surplus on services and an increase in net outflows for unilateral current transfers. In the financial account, net recorded inflows increased $117.0 billion, to $157.3 billion, as financial inflows for foreign-owned assets in the United States increased more than financial outflows for U.S.-owned assets abroad. In the year 2001, the U.S. current-account deficit decreased $27.2 billion, to $417.4 billion. Most of the decrease was accounted for by a decrease in the deficit on goods, but an increase in the surplus on services and a decrease in net outflows for unilateral transfers also contributed. In contrast, the deficit on income increased. In the financial account, net recorded financial inflows increased $12.6 billion, to $455.9 billion. Financial outflows for U.S.-owned assets abroad decreased more than financial inflows for foreign-owned assets in the United States.\n</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/04April/0402ITA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-04-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables A-S</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/04April/0402ITA.xls</Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title>CSV files containing data for Tables 1-10 can be downloaded from the International Transactions data base</Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL>http://bea.gov/bea/international/bp_web/</Supp2_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-04-04</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, 2001:IV</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/04April/0402InventorySales.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-04-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables 1.b-4.b</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/04April/0402InventorySales.xls</Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title></Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL></Supp2_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-04-05</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>4</Issue>
        <Month>April</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>An Ownership-Based Framework of the U.S. Current Account, 1989-99</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey H. Lowe</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/04April/0402CurrentAcct.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-04-17</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Table 1</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/04April/0402currentacct.xls</Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title></Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL></Supp2_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-05-01</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>BEA's Strategic Plan for 2001-2005</Title>
        <Author>J. Steven Landefeld</Author>
        <Description>BEA's strategic plan outlines the major focus of the Bureau's work over the next several years. The plan incorporates suggestions and comments from BEA's customers, staff, and partner statistical agencies. In November 2001, a panel of experts that included members of the Administration, other Federal Government agencies, and the private sector provided their opinions and insights on potential expansions and improvements to the accounts. Abstracts of their comments are reprinted along with a table that summarizes the new initiatives of the plan and shows the milestones for completion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/05May/0502StratPLAN.pdf</URL>
        <Category>General</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-05-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-05-02</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Advance Estimates for the First Quarter of 2002</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Frederick von Batchelder</Author>
        <Description>The pace of U.S. production picked up sharply in the first quarter of 2002: Real GDP increased 5.8 percent after increasing 1.7 percent in the fourth quarter of 2001. More than half of the first-quarter increase was accounted for by a substantial slowdown in the rate of liquidation of private inventories. Inflation remained low.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/05May/0502BSA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-05-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables 1-6, Table A</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/05May/0502bsa.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-05-03</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>State Per Capita Personal Income and State Personal Income, 2001</Title>
        <Author>Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>Growth in per capita personal income slowed in 46 States and the District of Columbia in 2001. The States with the sharpest slowdowns were New Hampshire, California, Massachusetts, and Colorado. In contrast, growth picked up in New Mexico, Louisiana, and Alabama. Connecticut again topped the Nation in per capita personal income, at $41,930, while Mississippi again trailed, at $21,643.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/05May/0502spi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-05-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-05-04</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>5</Issue>
        <Month>May</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Local Area Personal Income, 1998-2000</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey L. Newman</Author>
        <Description>Newly released estimates of metropolitan area personal income show that San Jose, CA, again had the fastest growth in personal income in 2000, at 21.0 percent. Anniston, AL, had the slowest growth, at -0.2 percent. San Francisco, CA, again had the highest per capita personal income, at $57,414, while McAllen-Edinburg-Mission, TX, again had the lowest, at $13,344. Newly released estimates of personal income by county show that Edgecombe County, NC, which rebounded from flooding caused by Hurricane Floyd in 1999, had the fastest growth in personal income, at 24.8 percent. Calhoun County, AL, had the slowest growth, at -0.2 percent. New York County (Manhattan), NY, again had the highest per capita personal income, at $90,901, while Loup County, NE, again had the lowest, at $6,606.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/05May/0502LAPI.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Local area personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-05-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-06-01</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Gross Domestic Product by Industry: A Progress Report on Accelerated Estimates</Title>
        <Author>Robert E. Yuskavage</Author>
        <Description>BEA has developed a prototype methodology for preparing estimates of GDP by industry on an accelerated schedule. The accelerated estimates would be released in April, 4 months after the end of the reference year and 7 months ahead of the release of the regular annual estimates in November. As part of this research, BEA has provided illustrative estimates for 2001 of current-dollar GDP by industry. These estimates are more limited in scope than the regularly published estimates, but research indicates that they are reasonably successful in indicating the direction of change in an industry's growth, whether the growth is accelerating or decelerating, and how the growth compares with that of other industries. BEA is seeking feedback from users on the proposed methodologies for preparing the estimates, on the appropriate level of industry detail, and on the tradeoff between accuracy and timeliness.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/06June/0602GDPbyIndy.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Industry, Industry Accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-06-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables A-G</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/06June/0602GDPbyINDY.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-06-02</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Selected Issues in the Measurement of U.S. International Services</Title>
        <Author>Obie G. Whichard, Maria Borga</Author>
        <Description>The rapid growth of services transactions in world markets has made it increasingly important that trade in services be reflected in the statistics in a complete and economically meaningful way. Five categories of services--insurance, wholesale and retail trade, finance, construction, and utilities--are among the most difficult to define and measure. For each of these services, BEA has identified key measurement issues and has explored possible actions to address these issues. For example, in cross-border trade in insurance services, a catastrophe that results in a substantial jump in claims will lead to a drop in the current-dollar value of insurance services as presently measured, but this drop is unrelated to the actual level of the services provided. A possible action to address this issue would be to measure insurance services as premiums less average or expected claims rather than as premiums less actual claims.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/06June/0602intlservices.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international services</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-06-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables 2-4</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/06June/0602intlservices.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-06-03</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Preliminary Estimates for the First Quarter of 2002</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Frederick von Batchelder, Janet Kmitch</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 5.6 percent in the first quarter of 2002, according to the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate, after increasing 1.7 percent in the fourth quarter of 2001. The &quot;advance&quot; estimate issued last month had shown an increase of 5.8 percent. Corporate profits increased 0.5 percent in the first quarter after increasing 17.9 percent in the fourth (quarterly rates). The Federal Government current surplus or deficit shifted to a deficit of $64.4 billion in the first quarter from a surplus of $97.4 billion in the fourth. The State and local government current surplus decreased to $10.4 billion from $24.8 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/06June/0602BSP.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-06-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables 1-12, Table A</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/06June/0602bsa.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-06-04</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: New Investment in 2001</Title>
        <Author>Thomas W. Anderson</Author>
        <Description>Outlays by foreign direct investors to acquire or establish businesses in the United States dropped sharply to $132.9 billion in 2001 from an exceptionally high level of $335.6 billion in 2000. The dropoff reflected a substantial decrease in the share of outlays that was accounted for by very large transactions. Outlays fell in all the major industry groups and from almost all the major investing countries.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/06June/0602FDIUS.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-06-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables 1-7.2</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/06June/0602fdius.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-06-05</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Gross State Product by Industry, 1998-2000</Title>
        <Author>Sharon D. Panek, George K. Downey</Author>
        <Description>In 2000, the States with the fastest growth in real gross state product were located in the western and northeastern areas of the Nation. In Idaho, Oregon, California, and Arizona, growth was particularly robust in high-tech manufacturing, and in Colorado, growth was strong in business services and communication. In Rhode Island, New Hampshire, Massachusetts, New Jersey, and New York, growth was strong in finance, insurance, and real estate and in services.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/06June/0602GSP.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, Gross state product by industry</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-06-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Appendices A-B</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/06June/0602GSPapA_B.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-06-06</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Errata: BEA's Strategic Plan for 2001-2005</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/06June/0602Errata.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-06-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-06-07</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>6</Issue>
        <Month>June</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Subject Guide for the January-June 2002 Issues</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/06June/0602SbjGuide.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-06-13</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-07-01</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Annual Revision of the U.S. International Accounts, 1993–2001</Title>
        <Author>Christopher L. Bach</Author>
        <Description>Each year, the estimates in the U.S. international transactions accounts and the U.S. international investment position accounts are revised to incorporate statistical and methodological changes and regularly available source data. The year's annual revision featured the incorporation of results from the March 2000 U.S. Treasury Department's Benchmark Survey of Foreign Portfolio Investment in the United States. The incorporation of these results led to substantial downward revisions to the estimates of foreign holdings of U.S. securities for 1995-2000 in the U.S. international investment position accounts. It also led to substantial downward revisions to the related income payments and net financial inflows for foreign-owned assets in the United States for 1995-2001 in the U.S. international transactions accounts. In addition, receipts and payments for &quot;other&quot; private services are revised to incorporate results from BEA's Benchmark Survey of Selected Services for 2001.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/07July/0702%20ITARevEst.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-07-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables 1-3</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/07July/0702%20ITARevEst.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-07-02</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Final Estimates for the First Quarter of 2002</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Frederick von Batchelder</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 6.1 percent in the first quarter of 2002, up from a 1.7-percent increase in the fourth quarter of 2001. The &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate for the first quarter issued last month had shown a 5.6-percent increase. A downward revision to imports (which are subtracted in the calculation of GDP) and an upward revision to nonresidential investment in equipment and software more than offset a downward revision to exports. Corporate profits increased $5.8 billion (0.7 percent at a quarterly rate) in the first quarter after increasing $125.0 billion (17.9 percent) in the fourth.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/07July/0702BSF.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-07-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables 1-5</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/07July/0702bsf.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-07-03</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>The International Investment Position of the United States at Yearend 2001</Title>
        <Author>Elena L. Nguyen</Author>
        <Description>In 2001, the net international investment position of the United States became more negative, whether measured on a current-cost basis or on a market-value basis. The net position at current cost was -$1,948.1 billion at yearend 2001, compared with -$1,350.8 billion (revised) at yearend 2000. The net position for yearend 2000 was revised from the previously published estimate of -$1,842.7 billion, primarily reflecting the incorporation of results from the March 2000 U.S. Treasury Department's Benchmark Survey of Foreign Portfolio Investment in the United States as part of the annual revision of the U.S. international accounts.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/07July/0702IntINVEST.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, International investment position of the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-07-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables 1-2</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/07July/intINVEST.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-07-04</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Direct Investment Positions for 2001: Country and Industry Detail</Title>
        <Author>Maria Borga, Daniel R. Yorgason</Author>
        <Description>In 2001, growth slowed in the historical-cost positions of U.S. direct investment abroad (USDIA) and of foreign direct investment in the United States (FDIUS), reflecting slowdowns in both U.S. and foreign economic growth. The USDIA position grew 7 percent, down from 10 percent in 2000; the FDIUS position grew 9 percent, down sharply from 27 percent in 2000. The economic slowdowns contributed to a worldwide drop in merger and acquisition activity, which included a slowdown in cross-border activity, and to depressed earnings, which reduced reinvested earnings, of both U.S. and foreign affiliates.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/07July/0702dip.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Direct investment positions: Country and industry detail</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-07-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables 1-3.2</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/07July/0702dip.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-07-05</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, First Quarter 2002</Title>
        <Author>Douglas B. Weinberg</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit increased $17.4 billion, to $112.5 billion, in the first quarter of 2002. The increase was primarily accounted for by an increase in the deficit on goods and by a shift in the balance on income from a surplus to a deficit. In the financial account, net recorded inflows decreased $51.3 billion, to $99.4 billion. Financial inflows for foreign-owned assets in the United States and financial outflows for U.S.-owned assets abroad both decreased substantially, but the decrease in financial inflows was larger.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/07July/0702ITA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-07-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>CSV files containing data for Tables 1-10 can be downloaded from the International Transactions database</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/bea/international/bp_web/</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-07-06</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>7</Issue>
        <Month>July</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, 2002:I</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/07July/0702RealInventories.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-07-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables 1b - 4b</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/07July/0702RealInventories.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-08-01</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Annual Revision of the National Income and Product Accounts: Annual Estimates, 1999-2001, and Quarterly Estimates, 1999:I-2002:I</Title>
        <Author>Eugene P. Seskin, Stephanie H. McCulla</Author>
        <Description>The revised estimates show weaker economic growth than that shown by the previously published estimates, particularly in 2001. Real GDP now shows declines in the first three quarters of 2001; in the previous estimates, it had shown a decline only in the third quarter. Over the period covered by the revisions, the average annual growth rate of real GDP was revised down from 2.8 percent to 2.4 percent; the largest downward revisions were in investment in equipment and software and in personal consumption expenditures for services. The revised estimates reflect the incorporation of newly available and revised regular source data and of changes in methodology, including the introduction of several new price indexes. In addition, a change in the methodology and the revision schedule for the quarterly estimates of wages and salaries will allow the earlier incorporation of more comprehensive source data.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/08August/0802AnnualRevision.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-08-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/08August/0802AnnualRevision.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-08-02</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>A Preview of the 1997 Benchmark Input-Output Accounts: New Detailed and Summary Industries</Title>
        <Author>Ann M. Lawson, Karen J. Horowitz</Author>
        <Description>In the upcoming 1997 benchmark input-output accounts, BEA will present the detailed and summary industries on the basis of the 1997 North American Industry Classification System.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/08August/0802_I-O_Benchmark.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Industry, Input-output accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-08-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/08August/0802_I-O_Benchmark.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-08-03</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Advance Estimates for the Second Quarter of 2002</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Frederick von Batchelder</Author>
        <Description>The pace of U.S. production slowed in the second quarter of 2002: Real GDP increased 1.1 percent after increasing 5.0 percent in the first quarter. The deceleration was mainly accounted for by slowdowns in inventory investment, consumer spending, and government spending. Inflation picked up in the second quarter: Prices of gross domestic purchases increased 2.1 percent after increasing 1.2 percent. The pickup was more than accounted for by a sharp upturn in energy prices.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/08August/BSA0802.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-08-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/08August/BSA0802.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-08-04</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Affiliates of Foreign Companies: Operations in 2000</Title>
        <Author>William J. Zeile</Author>
        <Description>Largely as a result of record levels of new foreign investment, the current-dollar gross product of U.S. nonbank affiliates of foreign companies increased 14 percent in 2000, up from increases of 8 percent in 1998 and 9 percent in 1999. The U.S.-affiliate share of GDP in U.S. private industries rose to a record 7.0 percent from 6.5 percent in 1999. By country of ownership, several large acquisitions helped push the British-owned affiliates' share of the gross product of all affiliates to more than 20 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/08August/USAffiliates.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-08-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/08August/0802USAffiliates.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-08-05</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Personal Income by State, First Quarter 2002</Title>
        <Author>Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>In about three-fifths of the States, personal income increased in the first quarter of 2002 after decreasing in the fourth quarter of 2001, and in nearly all of the remaining States, personal income increased more in the first quarter than in the fourth. Part of the strength in the first quarter was accounted for by the annual cost-of-living adjustments to social security program benefits and by other special factors. Nevada and North Dakota had the sharpest turnarounds in personal income, and Wyoming was the only State in which personal income decelerated.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/08August/PersonalIncome0802.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-08-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-08-06</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>National Income and Product Accounts Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/08August/0802NIPA_Tables.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-08-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-08-07</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>8</Issue>
        <Month>August</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>GDP and Other Major NIPA Series, 1929-2002:I</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/08August/0802GDP_%26Other_Major_NIPAs..pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-08-19</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-09-01</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Preliminary Estimates for the Second Quarter of 2002</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Frederick von Batchelder, Janet Kmitch</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 1.1 percent in the second quarter of 2002, according to the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate, after increasing 5.0 percent in the first quarter. The advance estimate issued last month had also indicated a 1.1-percent increase. Corporate profits decreased 1.7 percent in the second quarter, the same as in the first (quarterly rates). The current deficit of the Federal Government increased $41.6 billion, to $185.1 billion, in the second quarter. In contrast, the current deficit of State and local governments decreased $8.5 billion, to $43.2 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/09September/0902BSP.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-09-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/09September/0902BSP.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-09-02</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Note on the Profitability of Domestic Nonfinancial Corporations, 1960-2001</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins</Author>
        <Description>The profitability of domestic nonfinancial corporations, as measured by property income's before-tax rate of return on capital, dropped from 7.7 percent in 2000 to 6.9 percent in 2001. The revised estimates of the rates of return for 1999 and 2000 and the new estimates for 2001 incorporate the results of the recent annual revision of the NIPA's.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/09September/0902CorpProfit.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-09-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/09September/0902CorpProfit.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-09-03</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Annual NIPA Revision: Newly Available Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/09September/0902Newnipatables.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-09-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-09-04</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Fixed Assets and Consumer Durable Goods for 1925-2001</Title>
        <Author>Paul R. Lally</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/09September/0902FixedAssets.pdf</URL>
        <Category>General</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-09-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-09-05</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: Detail for Historical-Cost Position and Related Capital and Income Flows, 2001</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey H. Lowe</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/09September/0902FDIUS.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, Foreign direct investment in the United States</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-09-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/09September/0902FDIUS.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-09-06</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>9</Issue>
        <Month>September</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Direct Investment Abroad: Detail for Historical-Cost Position and Related Capital and Income Flows, 2001</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey H. Lowe</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/09September/0902USDIA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-09-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/09September/0902USDIA.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-10-01</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>State Personal Income: Revised Estimates for 1999-2001</Title>
        <Author>Jeffrey L. Newman</Author>
        <Description>The annual estimates of State personal income for 1999-2001 have been revised to incorporate the results of the recent annual revision of the NIPA's and newly available State-level source data. In general, the revisions were small and upward for all 3 years; in contrast, the NIPA estimate of personal income for 2001 had been revised down substantially. The difference primarily reflected the timing of the incorporation of Bureau of Labor Statistics tabulations of wages and salaries for 2001. In 2001, personal income grew the fastest in New Mexico, and it grew the slowest in Michigan.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/10October/SPI1002.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-10-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title></Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL></Supp2_URL>
        <Supp3_Title></Supp3_Title>
        <Supp3_URL></Supp3_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-10-02</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Final Estimates for the Second Quarter of 2002</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Frederick von Batchelder</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP slowed to a 1.3-percent increase in the second quarter of 2002, according to the &quot;final&quot; estimate, from a 5.0-percent increase in the first quarter; the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate issued a month ago had shown a 1.1-percent increase. The primary contributor to the upward revision to GDP was an upward revision to exports of services. Corporate profits decreased $12.6 billion (1.6 percent at a quarterly rate) in the second quarter after decreasing $13.8 billion (1.7 percent) in the first.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/10October/BSF1002.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-10-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/10October/BSF1002.xls</Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title></Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL></Supp2_URL>
        <Supp3_Title></Supp3_Title>
        <Supp3_URL></Supp3_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-10-03</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Transactions, Second Quarter 2002</Title>
        <Author>Patricia E. Abaroa, Elena L. Nguyen</Author>
        <Description>The U.S. current-account deficit increased $17.5 billion, to $130.0 billion, in the second quarter of 2002. The increase was primarily accounted for by an increase in the deficit on goods, as imports increased more than exports. In the financial account, net recorded inflows decreased $7.2 billion, to $80.4 billion. Financial outflows for U.S.-owned assets abroad and financial inflows for foreign-owned assets in the United States both increased substantially, but the increase in financial outflows was larger.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/10October/1002ITA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-10-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title></Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL></Supp2_URL>
        <Supp3_Title></Supp3_Title>
        <Supp3_URL></Supp3_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-10-04</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>U.S. International Services: Cross-Border Trade in 2001 and Sales Through Affiliates in 2000</Title>
        <Author>Maria Borga, Michael Mann</Author>
        <Description>In 2001, U.S. exports of private services decreased 4 percent, to $266.2 billion, and U.S. imports of private services decreased 5 percent, to $192.3 billion. The decreases in both exports and imports reflected the worldwide slowdown in economic growth and the effects of the terrorist attacks of September 11th. In 2000, the most recent year for which data are available, sales of private services abroad through foreign affiliates of U.S. companies increased 11 percent, to $392.8 billion, and sales of private services in the United States through U.S. affiliates of foreign companies increased 18 percent, to $346.7 billion. These increases reflected the strong worldwide economy in 2000 and the continued worldwide boom in merger and acquisition activity.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/10October/1002InServ.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international services</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-10-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/10October/1002InServ.xls</Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title>Article without the tables</Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/10October/1002InServicesArticle.pdf</Supp2_URL>
        <Supp3_Title>Tables in PDF format</Supp3_Title>
        <Supp3_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/10October/1002InServTables.pdf</Supp3_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-10-05</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Real Inventories, Sales, and Inventory-Sales Ratios for Manufacturing and Trade, 1998:IV-2002:II</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/10October/1002isr.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Inventories, sales, and inventory-sales ratios for manufacturing and trade</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-10-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/10October/1002isr.xls</Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title></Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL></Supp2_URL>
        <Supp3_Title></Supp3_Title>
        <Supp3_URL></Supp3_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-10-06</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Customer Service Report for Fiscal Year 2002</Title>
        <Author>Verna Learnard</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/10October/CSR.pdf</URL>
        <Category>General</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-10-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title></Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL></Supp2_URL>
        <Supp3_Title></Supp3_Title>
        <Supp3_URL></Supp3_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-10-07</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Annual NIPA Revision: Newly Available Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/10October/1002newnipas.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-10-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title></Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL></Supp2_URL>
        <Supp3_Title></Supp3_Title>
        <Supp3_URL></Supp3_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-10-08</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Updated Summary NIPA Methodologies</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/10October/1002UpdatedMeth.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-10-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title></Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL></Supp2_URL>
        <Supp3_Title></Supp3_Title>
        <Supp3_URL></Supp3_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-10-09</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>10</Issue>
        <Month>October</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Schedule of BEA News Releases in 2003</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/10October/Releasedates2003.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-10-15</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
        <Supp2_Title></Supp2_Title>
        <Supp2_URL></Supp2_URL>
        <Supp3_Title></Supp3_Title>
        <Supp3_URL></Supp3_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-11-01</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Note on the Upcoming Comprehensive Revision of the National Income and Product Accounts</Title>
        <Author>Brent R. Moulton</Author>
        <Description>Next year, BEA will be preparing a comprehensive revision of the NIPA's. The major areas of work include instituting a new processing system; evaluating and implementing changes in definitions, methodology, and presentation; and improving consistency with other accounts and with international standards.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/11November/1102NIPA_Note.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-11-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-11-02</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Gross Domestic Product by Industry for 1999-2001</Title>
        <Author>Robert J. McCahill, Brian C. Moyer</Author>
        <Description>In 2001, the U.S. economy grew only slightly after growing at an average annual rate of 4.0 percent in 1995-2000. The slowdown reflected a downturn in private goods-producing industries and a deceleration in private services-producing industries. However, robust growth continued in a number of services and manufacturing industries, partly reflecting decreases in unit labor costs and unit capital costs as a result of increasing productivity. The new estimates of GDP by industry for 2001 and the revised estimates for 1999 and 2000 incorporate the results of this year's annual revision of the NIPA's and newly available source data.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/11November/1102GDPbyIndustry.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Industry, Industry Accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-11-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Description of this product</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/agency/uguide1.htm#0302</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-11-03</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Advance Estimates for the Third Quarter of 2002</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Frederick von Batchelder</Author>
        <Description>The pace of U.S. production picked up in the third quarter of 2002: Real GDP increased 3.1 percent after increasing 1.3 percent in the second quarter. Most of the pickup was attributable to consumer spending, which was boosted in the third quarter by a surge in auto and truck purchases. U.S. inflation moderated: The price index for gross domestic purchases increased 1.4 percent after increasing 2.3 percent.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/11November/1102BSA.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-11-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/11November/1102bsa.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-11-04</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Comparison of BEA Estimates of Personal Income and IRS Estimates of Adjusted Gross Income: New Estimates for 2000 and Revised Estimates for 1999</Title>
        <Author>Thae S. Park</Author>
        <Description>BEA's estimates of personal income and the IRS estimates of adjusted gross income (AGI)--two widely used measures of household income--are reconciled through a series of adjustments for definitional and statistical differences between the two measures. This year's reconciliation reflects the recent annual revision of the NIPA's and recent updates to the AGI estimates.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/11November/1102irs&agi.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-11-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/11November/1102irs%26agi.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-11-05</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Reconciliation of the U.S.-Canadian Current Account, 2000 and 2001</Title>
        <Author>Anthony DiLullo, Denis Caron</Author>
        <Description>Each year, the U.S. and Canadian current-account estimates are reconciled using a common set of definitions, methodologies, and data sources. On the reconciled basis, the U.S. current-account deficits with Canada are larger than those shown in the U.S.-published accounts. For 2000, the deficit on the reconciled basis is $40.4 billion, compared with the U.S.-published deficit of $30.5 billion. For 2001, the reconciled deficit is $40.0 billion, compared with the published deficit of $26.5 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/11November/1102USCanadian.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. international transactions</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-11-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-11-06</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Personal Income by State, Second Quarter 2002</Title>
        <Author>Duke Tran</Author>
        <Description>Personal income for the Nation increased 1.3 percent in the second quarter of 2002, about the same as in the first quarter. The growth in personal income slowed in 35 States and picked up in only 14 States, but the 14 States included the large States of California, New York, and Texas. Nevada led the Nation in personal income growth in the second quarter, and North Dakota was the only State in which personal income declined.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/11November/1102SPI.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Regional, State personal income</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-11-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-11-07</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Updated NIPA Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/11November/1102UpdatedNIPAs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-11-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-11-08</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>11</Issue>
        <Month>November</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Federal Personal Income Tax Liabilities and Payments, 1959-2000</Title>
        <Author>Thae S. Park</Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/11November/1102fedtax.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, Federal personal income tax liabilities and payments</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-11-14</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/11November/1102fedtax.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-12-01</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Benchmark Input-Output Accounts of the United States, 1997</Title>
        <Author>Ann M. Lawson, Kurt S. Bersani, Mahnaz Fahim-Nader, Jiemin Guo</Author>
        <Description>The 1997 benchmark input-output (I-O) accounts present a detailed picture of the interactions among industries that combine to produce the Nation's GDP. A major change introduced in the 1997 I-O accounts is the incorporation of the North American Industry Classification System (NAICS), which provides a new treatment of the service activities of central administrative offices and other types of auxiliaries and a more detailed presentation of the increasingly important service industries. The 1997 accounts feature I-O tables that are more consistent with the GDP-by-industry accounts and the gross state product accounts and with other industry data that are based on NAICS.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/12December/1202I-OAccounts2.pdf</URL>
        <Category>Industry, Input-output accounts</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-12-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-12-02</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Business Situation: Preliminary Estimates for the Third Quarter of 2002</Title>
        <Author>Daniel Larkins, Raymen G. Labella</Author>
        <Description>Real GDP increased 4.0 percent in the third quarter, according to the &quot;preliminary&quot; estimate, a sizable upward revision from the 3.1-percent increase shown in the &quot;advance&quot; estimate issued last month. However, both estimates indicated that economic growth stepped up from the 1.3-percent increase in the second quarter. Corporate profits decreased 1.8 percent (quarterly rate), about the same decrease as in the two preceding quarters. The current deficit of the Federal Government was unchanged, at $190.3 billion, and the current deficit of State and local governments grew to $51.8 billion.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/12December/1202BSP.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-12-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/12December/1202BSP.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-12-03</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>U.S. Multinational Companies: Operations in 2000</Title>
        <Author>Raymond J. Mataloni, Jr.</Author>
        <Description>The worldwide gross product of U.S. multinational companies increased 8.7 percent in 2000. The strong growth was evident in the operations of both U.S. parents and their majority-owned foreign affiliates. The growth in the operations of the affiliates was fueled both by expansions of existing affiliates and by acquisitions and establishments of new affiliates. By industry, the strongest growth was in petroleum-related activities. By area, the sharpest increases were in Africa and the Middle East.</Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/12December/1202multinational.pdf</URL>
        <Category>International, U.S. direct investment abroad</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-12-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title>Tables</Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/12December/1202multinational.xls</Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-12-04</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Updated NIPA Tables</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/12December/1202UpdatedNIPAs.pdf</URL>
        <Category>National, National income and product accounts (NIPAs)</Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-12-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-12-05</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Subject Guide for 2002</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/12December/1202SbjGuide.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-12-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
    <row>
        <ID>SCB-82-12-06</ID>
        <Volume>82</Volume>
        <Issue>12</Issue>
        <Month>December</Month>
        <Year>2002</Year>
        <Title>Schedule of BEA News Releases in 2003</Title>
        <Author></Author>
        <Description></Description>
        <URL>http://bea.gov/scb/pdf/2002/12December/1202RD.pdf</URL>
        <Category></Category>
        <Publication_Date>2002-12-16</Publication_Date>
        <Modified_Date></Modified_Date>
        <Supp1_Title></Supp1_Title>
        <Supp1_URL></Supp1_URL>
    </row>
</rows>
